[crowd cheering]
[cheering continues]
[whistle blows]
[announcer 1]
Twelve seconds on the clock.
Third down with 52 yards
to the end zone.
[announcer 2] Yeah, Chuck,
they're about five yards shy
from being
within field goal range.
I really think they're gonna need
a Hail Mary to make this play.
[Chuck]
And here's the hike.
Boy wonder quarterback
Casey Rhodes got the ball.
Landon Morris
has shut down Ben Roy.
Rhodes is running it!
He's running it!
And the crowd is loving it!
And Rhodes is making a mockery
of Atlanta's defense!
Jo won Briggs
is gaining on Rhodes.
[crowd exclaiming] [Chuck]
Rhodes is gonna get up. He's going!
- Oh! Whoa, whoa!
- [announcer 2] Yeah.
[Chuck] Oh, Jo won Briggs
sacked Rhodes on the two-yard line.
[announcer 2] We are not made
to bend that way.
[Chuck] Oh, that's
devastating, Dave, for Rhodes.
All play-off hopes are gone
in one savage tackle.
- [Dave] Well, you know, Chuck, that's football.
- [Chuck] That's football.
Hey, you guys gotta move.
You're blocking us in.
What the hell?
Nathanial Wilson!
You live at 1403 Angel Avenue
with your wife and daughter.
Open the truck and forget
that I know where you live.
Don't think about your job.
Think about your fucking family!
Nathanial!
[robber 1] Don't do it,
don't do it.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
Move. Give me the keys!
Go!
[grunting]
Get on your knees.
Hands behind your head.
Do it!
[panting]
[robber]
Thirty seconds to go.
[robber 2] Twenty-nine, 28...
Fifteen, 14...
Twelve, 11, ten,
nine, eight, seven...
He's running!
You mother...
- [grunts]
- [robber 2] ...two, one.
[robber 1]
Time's up. Let's move!
[panting]
[sirens wailing]
[vehicles approaching]
[robber 2]
Come on, come on, come on.
[tires screech]
[officers clamoring]
Check the alley.
[radio clicks]
Knight, get your ass
downtown now!
Let's go.
[keys rattling]
[door opens]
[robber 1] Drop your keys!
Whoa! You can have the car.
Get the fuck outta here!
[grunting]
Let's go! [robber 2 sighs]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
[sirens approaching]
Are you fucking kidding me?
I got it. I got it.
- You're up, Mike.
- [Mike] I'm on it.
[gun clicks]
Let's go!
Mike, let's go!
Don't leave anyone behind.
Let's go!
[robber 3]
Oh, for fuck's sake!
[robber 1] Where are you going?
Fuck!
[robber 2] I'm going.
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
[siren wails]
[tires screech]
[siren stops]
Let's go!
[Mike chuckles]
Come here, piggies!
[gunfire]
Yo, where are you going?
The car's this way.
Police! Freeze!
Drop your weap...
Get down! Shit!
Hey, man.
What's all that cowboy
shit, man? Stick to the plan!
I'm playing to win.
Ah, fuck.
- [groans]
- You should've said "Please."
Fuck you, buddy.
No, thanks.
[pants]
I'll get 'em this time.
On three, you ready?
On three, you move. One...
- Two.
- Three. Go!
[grunts]
- I got one.
- Let's get outta here.
Hey... Get the fucking car.
Let's go. What the fuck?
After you.
Knight.
[groans]
Come on. Let's go!
[tires screeching]
On your mark!
All right, get in the car.
Let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
[engine revving]
Help me, James.
[tires screech, squeal]
Watch out, watch out!
[tires screech]
[partner groaning]
Knight, help me.
[siren approaching]
[siren stops]
[ambulance door slams]
[people chattering]
[plane engine whirring]
Casey, can we talk about
what happened?
I didn't sign up
to shoot cops, man.
The whole FBI
is probably chasing us by now.
It was us or them.
That cop did his job,
we did ours.
We did it better on the day.
For what? A couple grand?
Uh, six, seven, eight, minus
Winna's cut. So, that's, uh, 134K.
134?
That make it okay
to shoot cops then?
[chuckles]
No, but I mean, it's 134.
[chuckles] Should we
just head to Vegas?
Have a cocktail.
[chuckles] I'm down.
Yo.
So, what in the actual fuck
was that about?
You told me to take care of it,
so I took care of it.
Besides, you're the one
who shot the fucking cop.
Because I was cleaning up
your fucking mess.
You keep telling yourself that.
You told me to do something,
and I fucking did it.
I mean, that was better than a fucking
Pick 6 on a Sunday fucking afternoon.
That's not the point of it.
Whoa, whoa. What's your point?
You not only
put my life in danger,
you tried to screw over
our fucking teammates.
Do you think I don't have
your fucking back?
Huh?
Is that what you're saying?
You're the one coming to me,
"Oh, my knee is busted.
Oh, shit.
Give me some fucking pills.
Oh, come practice with me so I
can make a fucking comeback.
Oh, my life is over." Huh?
Who had your fucking back then?
You asked me to go,
and I fucking go.
Fuck you, Casey.
You know I'm not in this
for the money.
[engine whirring]
[staff chattering]
[nurse 1] Move, move.
[nurse 2] Coming through.
Everybody,
please get out of the way.
[people chattering]
[machine beeping]
[respirator hissing]
[phone vibrating]
Hey. Yeah, we made it.
Your fuckin' plane was late.
Well, Mercer went off.
Yeah, we'll be at LaGuardia
in four hours.
No, fuck LA.
Oh, fuck Mercer.
I'm never working
with him again.
Bye.
[car horns honking]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[door opens, closes]
[Mike] Whoo!
Yeah. All right, I'll get
Mercer's cut to him.
[Casey] Thank you.
138K. This is Winna's cut.
Hey, Case.
I know the last time,
it went to shit.
But I've been working
on something.
I watch this guy on
YouTube, super legit.
And guess what?
I copied him.
And I was thinking,
for next time...
[Casey] The fuck are you
talking about, man?
Hold that thought.
[chuckles, exhales]
Easy. Easy, easy, easy.
Easy.
What the...
A fucking pipe bomb?
[exhales]
Get that out of here right now.
If we need a distraction,
we could use it.
Then we'll have Homeland Security
on your asses for, like, the end of time.
You built this?
From scratch, bro.
That guy from YouTube,
he could teach a toddler
to make one of these things.
That's terrifying.
[Casey] Yeah.
Yeah, it kind of is terrifying.
Whoa. You want me
to get rid of it?
Yes! Obviously. I can't even
believe this is a real conversation.
Let's stash it, you know,
for an emergency.
You're both insane.
I'm just thinking ahead.
Like Cap taught me, right, Case?
[chuckles]
[hands slap]
Okay, goodbye.
[Mike] Come on. You're a little bit
impressed. Where are you going?
Out.
Sykes.
Wait, wait, wait, Sykes.
I'm having a little
get-together tomorrow night.
Couple of people. If you
wanna come by, just come by.
Maybe.
Bye.
What's her deal?
Bye, Sykes.
Bye!
She's right, you know?
You are insane.
No, but I love it.
My man.
[clears throat]
[exhales] Now...
[Casey chuckles]
How'd you do this?
[chuckles]
I'm actually glad you asked.
[glasses clinking]
[chuckles]
How do you do that?
Lots of practice.
How can you be
at the wrong place
at the right time all the time?
These guys were spraying
and praying.
It was 50/50 that they would
have hit you or Fitz.
One day, your luck is going
to run out, cowboy.
I should have done it alone.
[exhales]
He'll pull through.
Listen,
we are outgunned, outpaced.
The only way to catch
this crew is in the act.
You got a theory?
Yeah.
Those guys are smart, trained.
I mean, all they stole
is just a bit of cash
and an old deck
of baseball training cards.
Smart people don't rob banks.
Yeah, true that.
This crew is tight.
And they move like a team.
Hmm.
Yeah, but...
Athletes.
The guard said he got
truck stick trying to escape.
That tracks.
You know,
the rest of the team think
that I'm crazier than you
for thinking like this,
but hear me out.
Those guys are not from here.
One of the witnesses said that
they speak with a New York accent.
So?
Have you heard
of phantom planes?
The Phantom?
The one in the purple suit
with the dog?
[chuckles]
I'm talking about planes.
Phantom planes.
They fly around the country
with no manifests, no record.
They go from one city to
the next one, pick up people.
Now, there are a couple of jobs
around the country that fits the MO.
The Miami Credit Union
two months ago.
The Fenway Currency Exchange.
The Austin crypto hit.
The FAA logs tail numbers.
There was only one plane
that was in the same city
as all those jobs.
The plane is registered
to a New York shell company
that goes by... by Winna.
Winna?
[phone ringing]
Shit.
You know him?
Mm-hmm. He's a bookie.
Hmm.
That's not our jurisdiction.
But I can make a call
and get some information.
Where the fuck you going?
New York.
Fuck.
[car horns honking in distance]
[chattering on TV]
[child] I want to be
a Paw Patrol officer.
[scoffs] We got no pigs
in this house.
They're not pigs.
They're dogs.
Do pigs have paws?
No, they don't have paws.
They got those, uh...
Babe, what do pigs have?
Hooves?
Hooves! Hooves.
Yeah, they got those hooves.
What about a Gyptian mummy?
Gyp... Egyptian.
Come on, say that.
E-gyp-tian.
Egyptian.
Gyptian.
[laughs] That's close enough.
Okay. Hey, we'll pick out
a costume once I get back.
All right? Love you.
You got another thing there.
Give me a headbutt. [grunts]
Love ya.
Love you too.
Bye.
You going on a grocery run?
[keys rattle] Oh, let's
just get takeout, yeah?
I read too much grease
is bad for kids.
Okay, groceries it is.
You got cash?
Uh, no. The foreman owes me
a check. I'm gonna go pick it up.
Where?
Where are you going?
The site. I'm gonna go
get it at the job site.
The one by Broadway?
Yeah.
The construction job?
Yes. The construction job.
Hmm. That's strange,
'cause there isn't a construction
going on on that block.
Yeah, it's right by it.
I drove by yesterday,
'cause Clara wanted to see
her dad at work. Jesus Christ.
I want to know where the
father of my child is going.
Is that... Is that so
wrong? I'm working.
On what?
On providing for this family.
Casey, you can't provide for this
family if you're in a fucking jail cell.
Oh, no. I can't provide for this family
with a nine-to-five, darling. Okay?
That's not enough. Right?
Hmm.
Look, I'm not asking for much.
Oh, that's bullshit.
Bullshit?
Bullshit!
[Casey] Yeah!
You love that old lifestyle.
You married a quarterback
who can't play football anymore.
Okay? Poor woman, having
to slum it with a has-been.
But this is what you got.
This is the real world, okay?
I bust my ass for you,
and I am here.
You're here?
Yes, I'm here.
You think you're here?
No, you're not fucking here.
Half the time,
you're on pain pills.
You're like a fucking zombie.
And I-I understand.
I see what you
put your body through,
but you're a fucking
drug addict, Casey.
That's nice.
It's the truth.
Hey, darling. Hey.
Hi, hey. I'm sorry...
Ugh.
It's okay.
...that Daddy's screaming.
Did you ever call
Coach Cogburn back?
Um, no. I'm not working
for $18 an hour. All right?
Then Daddy would have to work for 90
hours a day... and that's not possible...
So I could provide for you.
To provide for me?
Yeah. Yeah,
you know what I mean.
[chuckles]
You know what I mean.
Yeah, yeah.
Come here, okay?
Hey, I...
[groans]
I love you. I'm sorry.
I just...
I love you, okay?
No. You love getting
under my skin.
It's true.
Hi!
Hi.
[chuckles]
Look, I really just
don't need anything more
than what we have right here.
Okay?
[imitates static]
You watch your mama
while I'm gone. Okay.
Okay?
[chuckles] We'll pick
out some costumes.
We'll pick 'em
when I get back. All right.
Okay.
Go eat your
sandwich, okay? Okay.
Okay.
[door closes]
[dog barking in distance]
[engine starts]
[birds chirping]
[crowd cheering on radio]
[Casey clears throat]
How's the knee, sausage?
[chuckles]
Uh, it's pretty awful,
but thank you for asking.
You know, I got some Tiger Balm
if you wanna, uh, rub me up.
You'd like that?
Oh, I really, really would.
Hmm.
You know the rules.
Help goes around back, okay?
Your breath, man,
it's disgusting.
[golfer] Arch your back.
Loosen your grip.
And when you're ready,
just take a swing.
Nice!
[ball rattles]
So you think you're funny?
Not... Not really.
Get out of here.
It's business time.
- Yeah, uh, golf? Not really your sport.
- Oh.
Have you ever considered,
uh, power walking?
Oh, so you are funny.
Brigga, punch him.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[Casey groans]
[sniffles, stomps]
- Did you do it yet?
- Now that's out of the way, tell me all about it.
Um, how'd it go?
[Casey] Uh... [chuckles]
- It was nothing but a good time, man.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Exciting.
You got the money?
I got the money.
Here you go, every cent.
Brigga.
Tell me more. Right?
Show me the dailies,
as they say. Go.
[laughs]
Better than any touchdown.
That's what I'm talking about. A
man who's passionate about his work.
All right, real talk now.
Coach and the captain.
I did see the fireworks.
Yeah, we got it done.
No.
No, what you got was heat.
The cops want both our heads now
for lighting up that detective.
- Yeah? So what? Who cares?
- So what?
Hazard of the job.
Oh, hazard of the job?
- Yeah, hazard of the job. You have some rats on the force.
- What of it?
So what's their take?
Anyone ID us? Not that I heard.
But if you can stand the heat,
I might have another job
for you.
[exhales]
Yeah.
Come on, take it.
[paper unfolding]
[chuckles]
Come on.
Nah.
They say it'll sell
for $1.2 million.
$1.2 million.
That's extraordinary, right?
Think about it.
If you can get that,
that's like 200K each
for you and your crew.
250.
250 times five, do the math.
I should just buy
the thing myself. 220.
[Casey] I'm not working with
Mercer. Three-man team this time.
It's not my problem.
All right.
All right?
Yeah. Get the money ready.
Get the fuck out of here.
All right.
All right, go.
Bring back the girl.
[club music playing in distance]
[people chuckling]
[Casey] Yeah, I'm just finishing up
here, and I'll be home in a little bit.
No, that's okay.
Perfect.
Bye.
[partyers chattering]
[club music playing]
[laughs]
Come on.
Not now.
All right.
[glasses clink]
[partyers chattering, laughing]
Hey.
What's up, Dave?
How you doing?
[bottle thuds]
Hey, champ. What's
up, brother? Hey, man.
What the fuck is this?
What, I can't have a party?
How the fuck does a guy
who got dropped by the Mets
and hauls scrap
at his dad's junkyard
pay for a party like this, huh?
First rule, right?
Don't flash your fucking cash.
What did you do... What did you do
with your cash? Thanks for asking.
I'm saving it, so I can get the
fuck out of this neighborhood
and buy new friends.
Dude, I don't want you
to go to jail.
All right, all right.
But we're here. It's a party.
Enjoy it, man. Have a beer.
You're freaking me out.
Jesus.
Hi, Ms. Kandinsky.
What did Winna say?
Um...
Winna said we did good work.
And that we maybe have
some heat for the cop thing.
[clears throat]
But the cop didn't die,
so, you know,
it should blow over.
That come from his rat?
No. They didn't ID
any of us and they won't
as long as we keep our mouths
shut and don't throw fucking parties.
Uh, but I got
some good news. Hey.
Hi there.
Uh, Winna's got another gig
lined up for us. Oh, come on.
I'm in. Why do you want to
keep working with this guy?
'Cause he's given us
five gigs in five months.
Uh, he's got a jet to fly us
anywhere, take any heist anytime.
And did I mention the part
that we're getting 220?
Whoa, 220?
220.
What about the fucking cop? Enough
with the fucking cop. Please, okay?
He didn't die, right?
He's okay.
Gonna get paid.
It's gonna be fine.
Yeah. maybe... maybe
we did him a favor.
Okay, maybe not a favor, but...
[clears throat]
That guy was doing his job.
So were we, okay?
Suddenly, you're a bank
robber with a heart of gold?
Casey pulled the trigger,
but we're all still guilty.
Just wanna let you know that.
You're all fucked.
You're all so fucked.
So go see a priest and
confess. Just not at my party.
Look, Sykes, if you've just gone up
and grown a conscience, that's fine.
You can walk.
I'm not gonna stop you.
But I want you.
Shut the fuck up and just
tell me what the score is.
[sighs]
[Casey] Check this out.
- [Sykes] Oh, come on.
- [Casey chuckles]
Here.
Oh, shit.
[chuckles]
No, we're gonna
die. For real. Fuck off.
No. One-of-a-kind
collector's item
that sells at an auction.
Guys, um, we do this job, right?
We're gonna have a nice
little deposit for our pensions.
Come on. I've seen it.
I got it all in my head.
I know all the angles.
We can do this.
I'm gonna pass
unless I have my team.
What about Mercer?
Fuck Mercer, okay?
I got one fucking cowboy right
here. I don't know about Mercer.
Fine.
I'm in.
Let's go steal Wayne
Gretzky. Have a salami.
Fuck you.
Fuck off.
[exhales] You couldn't
afford a heater?
[chuckles]
[instructor] Every move should
improve your position or hurt the enemy.
This is a battlefield. And
never forget why you're fighting.
Now, the knight.
The knight is the most
dangerous piece on the board.
The knight can strike
when you least expect it.
The knight moves in ways
most people won't understand.
[phone ringing]
Now, what the hell? How the fuck
did you... Where the fuck is my security?
Where's Brigga?
I hope I'm not, uh,
interrupting.
Detective, you're a long way
from home, you know that?
- Who are you?
- San go.
Oh, gesundheit.
Welcome to my humble fortress.
Nice place for a bookie.
[Winna] Thanks.
Yeah, we say if there's
a sport with a winner,
then there's also a loser
that was willing to bet on it.
- We need a word.
- You need a word? I got a word.
"Lawyer."
Lawyer?
I got four more words.
"Speak to my lawyer."
As you can see, I'm in
the middle of a lesson here.
Do you know who this is? This is
the youngest chess master in history.
[Knight] Well, good for him.
Hey, this is my home.
All right?
Show some respect.
I apologize for these clowns.
Hey, kid, go learn a real sport.
Sit.
Now, detectives, talk to me.
What can I do you for?
We know all about you, Winna.
Kicked out of Goldman Sachs
for insider trading.
Got a sweetheart deal
with the judge.
You were a CI
for the local PD and feds.
Oh, so you found
my Wikipedia page, did you?
And I'm glad to see the government's
finally hiring guys who can read.
So tell me, if I turn
your pockets inside out,
what am I going to find?
I don't know.
What will you find?
Perhaps a lawsuit for
breaching my civil liberties?
Really?
Yeah.
[Knight]
You know a lot of ex-pros.
Make some scratch.
Yep.
[San go exhales] I'd like a
couple of them for a messy job.
A messy drug job.
You know anything
about that? No.
Not to the best
of my recollection.
Think real hard.
And what's in it for me?
Christmas dinner at my place.
Oh, yeah?
I think I'll pass.
Well, better
than the alternative.
And what's that?
You have dinner at his.
You know, call ahead next time.
I'll make sure
the gates are locked.
If you're covering for them,
I'll find out.
Now, is that a threat,
Detective?
Got a lot of property here.
Lot of places
to get lost, disappear.
Lot of places.
We're done.
Get out.
[San go exhales]
[Knight] Wait here.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
What do you got?
What do I got?
What about the truck heist?
I don't know anything about it,
but if I did know something about it...
I would look at Casey Rhodes.
Casey Rhodes?
Yeah, look to him.
[laughs]
Yeah, where can I find him?
I'm not gonna do your
fucking job for you, buddy.
And I shouldn't have to explain
why this can't come back to Winna.
- [phone ringing]
- [Brigga] Don't forget.
You still owe him.
[ringing continues]
Is that a fact?
[ringing stops]
Yeah. It's a fact.
Now get the fuck outta here.
Yo, you got my stuff?
Yeah.
Any news on the next one?
Uh, nothing yet.
I'll let you know.
No serial numbers.
Complete virgin.
Not for long.
Yes.
All right. Let's get the fuck
outta here, yeah? Sure.
[San go] Casey Rhodes.
- Give that to...
- I'm not going back to jail, man.
You're not gonna...
If they had anything on us...
Lose it behind
your fucking back.
[Mercer] Can I help you?
[San go] Can I see some ID?
You know,
I think I left it at home.
What about you? Do you,
uh... Do you have your ID?
Yeah, I think
I left mine at home too.
I know who you are.
Casey Rhodes.
And?
Rookie of the year.
Drafted by the Chargers.
That's a really good memory,
pops.
Numbers are good?
[Knight] Astronomical.
The next Tom Brady.
Lost a lot of money.
Went bankrupt.
[San go]
Oh, I've heard about you.
Didn't you get banned
for shaving points?
Yeah, you want
a fuckin' autograph?
Get in the fucking car.
Let's go.
- Knight.
- [gunfire]
[tires screeching]
[Fitz] Knight, help me.
[phone ringing]
Yeah, you want
a fuckin' autograph?
[San go] Knight, you okay?
[ringing stops]
I was talking about you,
not to you.
[San go] Okay, now we have
a mutual friend. Winna.
Uh, Winna.
Hmm. You guys...
You know Winna?
It's a small world.
Maybe we could all grab some
brunch or something sometime.
Really nice.
[San go] That's real cute.
What's your current address?
Me?
Uh, you got a pen?
Okay. It's, uh,
just on the corner
of, uh, "Speak to my"
and "Fuckin' lawyer."
[Casey laughs]
[Mercer] It's a new suburb.
You're friends
with Winna, obviously.
He must train his dogs
really well.
Woof.
Stay safe out there.
Be seeing you.
You too.
[radio chatter]
[phone rings in distance]
Captain. Captain Shea.
Detective San go.
Mmm.
Thanks for taking the time.
Where's your partner?
He's not my partner.
What can I do for you,
Detective?
We're here as a gesture
of goodwill.
I was wondering if we
could share information.
You're out of your jurisdiction.
Captain, we have a cop who
is right now fighting for his life.
Detective Knight had some leads
regarding some old friend of his.
Andrew Winna.
Old friend?
Yeah, he might have
been a bookie or CI.
Just an old friend of Knight.
Does he know him
or "he knew him"?
Knight might be
rough around the edges,
but he's a good cop.
Mm-hmm.
Got anything concrete?
Winna's head of security,
Brigga.
He played football
with Casey Rhodes.
I guess they had a falling out,
because he implicated Casey
and his crew in the heist.
They cover their tracks
very well.
Hit the target
and disappear like ghosts.
Look, Detective,
I know your captain.
She vouched for you,
but not your partner.
She sent me his file.
It is the opinion
of the department
that if James Knight
wasn't hunting bank robbers,
he'd be robbing banks.
He's a thug with a badge.
If they strike again,
I'll give you clearance.
But stay out of our way.
Welcome to New York, Detective.
Have fun being a
tourist in my city. Mmm.
[sniffs]
[sighs]
[dog barking in distance]
[crowd noise on TV]
That was in! Get the fuck
out of the way. That was in!
What are you, blind?
Who the fuck is that ref, huh?
He's a dead man,
that's who he is.
You guys are good at what you do, all
right? You both work for me now, okay?
25%, your take. No cutting
or I take it out in blood.
I'm kidding, but not really.
What?
It's Knight.
What the fuck does he want?
Give me that phone.
What the fuck are you doing?
Why are you rolling on me
with that jamoke, huh?
We have an understanding,
Detective.
Stay away, or else.
[Knight]
They got him on life support.
Oh, okay. Well, hazard of the
job. Send him some flowers.
Who shot him?
How the fuck would I know
who shot some guy
in your dirty little city?
We spoke to him.
Yeah, Casey Rhodes.
And his buddy.
They're both stand-up guys.
We both agreed not to ask questions
that we don't want answers to.
If I get the evidence
that Rhodes shot Fitz...
Uh-uh. Watch that tone,
Detective.
I could always call IA and let
them know about our little chat.
We threatening
each other now? No.
No, we are not.
Now, listen to me.
Back off from Rhodes and Mercer.
If I find out you had
anything to do with this...
Oh, so much plot and excitement.
Listen to me. No more
empty threats, Detective.
I can take you out
whenever I want,
wherever I want, okay?
If you don't believe me, I'd
love to give you a demonstration.
Fitz is still in the ICU, right?
One call from me,
I'll have him moved
to the morgue. Bye.
[scoffs]
[Brigga laughs]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[vehicle approaching]
[door opens]
[Sykes] And the good news?
[door closes]
Uh, you're late.
How 'bout getting a fucking
watch? You find the blueprints?
Yeah. But I did some digging
on those cops that paid you a visit.
Anything good?
Yeah. So first up, we have
Detective God win Frensaw San go.
Analyst with the CIA
for seven years.
He settled down in LA,
made detective in a year.
In a year?
[Sykes] Yeah.
That's good. What about
the other guy? The bald guy.
The other bald one?
Uh-huh.
[Sykes] So that's Detective
James Edward Knight.
He served in the marines,
got out after a tour,
met his wife and had a kid.
Guess where.
In the back of his car?
No, dumb-ass. Newark.
This says here that he
made detective in two years.
And then here's where it gets,
like, super interesting.
Nine years ago, Knight is
transferred to Los Angeles.
Why?
[Sykes] This all starts with
a guy named Jerry Leach,
an ex-con who the cops liked for killing a
bank manager during an armed robbery.
Fast forward a few years later,
IA investigated Knight's
involvement in an off-duty shooting.
The victim, Jerry Leach.
And who was
the unlucky bank manager?
Knight's old man,
William Knight.
But here's the craziest part. Guess who the
last person to see Jerry Leach alive was?
Winna?
[Sykes] Yeah.
Winna was a CI.
He must have tipped off Knight
to Leach's whereabouts
in exchange
for owning Knight a favor.
Witnesses claimed
they didn't see anything,
the IA always leaning
towards Knight.
They made a deal to send him
out west just to get rid of him.
Since then, Knight had
caught some big cases.
But he got divorced and seems
to have some disciplinary hearing
at least once a year.
Boo-hoo.
I don't think we should
get between these guys,
especially with this Knight guy
wanting Casey's head.
If they had anything on us,
we'd be in cuffs right now, right?
So we proceed.
Blueprints.
[Sykes] Right.
So the good news is,
there are plenty of exit points.
All right, which means there's plenty
of places for us to get caught, right?
Right.
[Casey] From the top.
7:07, red carpet ends.
Okay, 7:09, one of us enters
through the lobby, dressed as a server.
- 7:25, the auction begins.
- 7:30, we cut the lights.
7:31, the snatch goes down.
7:32, we all meet
at the getaway car.
And by 7:33, we're all dead
or rich as fuck.
[chuckles]
Fuck yeah.
Now the last thing
we have to decide,
which one of us makes the grab?
[Casey] All right, Mike.
You're first up. Let's go.
All right. [exhales]
[Casey] On you.
Here we go.
[Casey]
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
[breathing heavily]
[timer beeps]
[Casey] No.
- [Mike] How was that?
- [Casey] No, horrible. Again.
[Sykes] Alarm will sound
as soon as you snatch it.
You got 30 seconds
to get to the getaway car.
Well, if this was real surface,
things would be different.
Yeah, no shit.
If you can execute here, you have
no excuse to screw it up on the day.
[sighs] All right.
Let's go.
[exhales]
[Casey] Nice.
Go, go, go, go.
[breathing heavily]
[Casey groans]
[timer beeps]
[pants]
- No.
- Nothing?
[Sykes]
No. Not even close.
- All right, move aside. I'm up.
- [pants] Come on.
[Mike breathing heavily]
All right, ready?
Go!
Yeah!
[Sykes] Come on, come on,
come on, come on. Come and get it.
Hit the corner.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Ow! Ow, fuck!
[Sykes] Go, go, go, go, go.
Ugh.
[timer beeps]
No. Time.
We gotta get this.
Mike!
[Casey] Come on! [Sykes]
All right. Take a breath.
Ready? And go!
[barrel thuds]
Come on, come on, come
on, come. Go, go, go, go.
[panting]
Come on.
[Sykes] Time.
Ugh!
How was that?
- No.
- [exclaims]
God.
We gotta get this.
You're up.
Okay.
Thought you'd never ask.
Quickly.
[Mike] We're fucked.
Ready?
Ready.
[Casey] Go.
[panting]
Whoa, whoa. Hopefully...
[exhales]
[Sykes] How'd I do?
How did you do that?
Anticipate the turns.
You're right.
We got too much muscle.
Okay, nobody ever said that.
- You think you're up for this?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Set. [sniffles]
Do it blindfolded.
[all chuckle]
[crowd cheering on TV]
[machine beeping]
[PA chatter, faint]
[nurses chattering]
[car horns honking in distance]
[guests chattering]
[camera shutters clicking]
[host] Our auction
will begin shortly.
Please start to find your way
to your seats.
[engine revving]
[exhales]
How do I look?
Like Tom Cruise
wants his mask back.
Let's go with that.
Let's go.
[guests chattering]
[shutters clicking]
[host] The auction will begin
in two minutes. Two minutes.
Please, everyone,
take your seats.
[gavel raps]
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
I am Maxwell Wyatt.
Tonight, you may walk home
with a piece of sports history.
Without further ado,
our first item.
1,000, 1,000.
For 10,000.
$10,000.
Do I have $25,000?
Who the fuck is that?
[whirs]
How are we lookin'?
I am fan-fucking-tastic.
Now shut up
and let me do my job.
[Mike] Copy.
Thank you.
Jesus.
Hey, I was actually
just looking to make some...
Shut your mouth and turn around.
Hands where I can see 'em.
Okay.
NYPD. You're under arrest.
Yeah, east wing,
we got a party crash...
[both grunting]
Rhodes, Mike, this place is
crowded with undercover cops.
Ah, they're probably just
moonlighting as security, right?
Here for the cash handout
and seafood buffet.
Proceed as planned.
[elevator bell dings]
[exhales]
Hey, gorgeous.
Fancy seeing you here.
Can I help you? Oh, cut the
charade. Nobody can hear us.
So how's the big mission going?
You ready to make the big swipe, huh?
Okay, use your head.
Someone could ID us later on.
See, that's why
I like you, Sykes.
You're as smart as you're hot.
How about we find
a little corner somewhere
and we can, uh, you know,
have a little talk?
Okay, we're here
to steal that card.
I know. And a little
action before the big action
won't hurt nobody, right?
[chuckles] Oh.
Oh, you were dead serious.
What the fuck
did you just say to me?
Okay, real talk.
You're a bourgie, rich asshole
acting like you have a wild side.
You give Casey some jobs, so
you feel like you're part of a team,
but I bet you were never
picked for any sports team.
You're nothing more than
just another dick in a suit
who's never had to work
a day in his life.
Now that we've cleared that up,
let's keep it
fucking professional
and stay the fuck
out of our way.
Gerald May wood.
You have a wife and two kids and live
at 506 Oakley Drive in Monterey Park.
Now, do as I say, and the
guy parked outside your house
won't turn into the guy
who goes inside your house.
Now, wipe the cameras
for the last hour.
There you go.
Stand up
and walk to that room.
I'm gonna lock you in it.
[Maxwell] The centerpiece
item of the evening.
A 1979 Wayne Gretzky rookie card
from before his time
with the Oilers.
Bidding will start
at $1 million.
Do I have one million?
One million over there.
Do I have 1.1?
1.1, anyone? 1.1.
1.2? 1.2? 1.2.
Do I have 1.5? 1.5.
Do I have 1.8? 1.8? 1.8.
Do I have two? Two million?
Two million. Two million.
2.1?
Once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
2.1.2.1?
2.2? 2.2? 2.2.
Going once, twice, sold.
[chuckles]
Well, that was exciting.
Moving to position now.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
[all murmuring]
Everyone, stay calm.
[guests screaming, clamoring]
[Maxwell] Stop her.
[alarm blaring]
Oop. Shit.
[officer]
Hey. Hey, stop there.
Get the card. No one can leave
until we search all of them.
[guests screaming]
Lock down the building.
What the fuck are you doing?
[alarm blaring continues]
Hey, Sykes, they're coming
down the stairwell.
Ah, shit.
[panting]
[grunts]
The fuck, Sykes? We good?
We gotta go.
Mike, can you hear her?
[Mike]
Not since she swiped the card.
Sykes? Fuck.
So much for getting out
in 30 seconds.
[exhales] Shit.
Shit.
Uh, hello. [clears throat]
This is your captain speaking.
I have a very special message
for a very important person.
And that message is:
"Left, right, right, left."
[Mike] Got my toy in the
truck if we need it, Case.
[Casey] No fucking way.
She's got this.
Come on. Shit.
Come on, Sykes. Come on.
[panting]
[Mike]
Case, we gotta leave now.
[guests screaming]
[guard] There she is.
[tires screeching]
[officer 1] Freeze.
[officer 2] Hands up.
[radio chatter]
[panting]
[Mike] Come on. Move.
We gotta go!
Come on!
Let's go!
Yo, where's Sykes?
Come on.
[sirens wailing in distance]
Let's go! Come on!
Let's go, buddy.
[engine starts]
We have to get out, for
fuck's sake. [tires screech]
[sirens wailing]
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
We needed Mercer.
Rather him than fucking Sykes!
[radio chatter]
[grunts]
Case, we have to
go back for her.
It's gonna be okay.
Just stick to the plan.
[panting]
Here you go.
Come on, come on, come on.
[engine starts]
[officer]
They wiped the counters.
There's fingerprints everywhere.
This is open and shut.
Yo, check it. We got fucking Dave
Chapelle and Patrick Stewart over here.
[officer 2] I can't believe the
captain's letting them tag along.
Watch your back. Yep.
There you go.
What was stolen?
Uh, some one-of-a-kind
sport card.
Some shit like that.
Sold at 2.2 million.
The woman we picked up
didn't say a word.
She didn't have it with her.
It must still be in here.
[Winna] Officers.
Hey.
I remember you.
- Some night, huh?
- Yeah, walk the scene.
Yeah, see what you see.
I love that guy.
If you're involved,
I won't cover for you.
I was just here
for the auction, sir.
[quietly] Shut up.
Nice badge.
Thanks.
However, my escort tonight
has already left,
so, uh,
I'm gonna need a new one.
That's where you come in.
So why don't you walk me out?
No.
No?
You ain't the only friend
I got in the department.
So, tell you what.
You do this for me, and, uh...
Fuck off.
Oh, "fuck off."
Yeah.
That's a no too, right?
Walk me through that line,
Detective.
I said no.
No.
You don't get to say no.
You seem to have forgotten
a phone call we had earlier,
so let me remind you.
Fitz, God bless him, is alive,
but only as long as I allow.
You shouldn't have come back,
Detective.
But since you're here,
I'm calling in that favor.
[phone ringing]
[camera shutter clicks]
Now walk.
Let's go.
[Knight] He's clear.
After you.
[elevator bell dings]
What the hell
just happened here?
Did you search him?
S-So you just let him go?
Just like that?
You know what?
Something is going on there.
- He's got something on you.
- On me?
You're a fucking disgrace now.
You don't deserve this badge.
I'm going to report you.
[train horn blaring]
[Casey] You're fine.
Fuck, man.
We gotta go back and get her.
I'm gonna call Winna.
Okay?
He's got cops in his pockets.
He'll know what to do.
Winna only cares about himself.
He doesn't give a fuck about us.
Exactly. What's good for
us is good for everybody.
Sykes isn't gonna give us up.
Hey, you know that. Right?
It's in everybody's best
interest to get her free.
Now, flip the plates, burn everything,
stick to the fucking plan, baby.
Let's go. You got it.
[exhales] [Winna] Hey, Casey,
my friend. How you doing?
Hey, before you say anything,
no, okay?
Sykes isn't gonna give us up.
Are you sure about that?
The fuck is that
supposed to mean?
It means I got people
in the system. Yeah.
Don't ask. If you think she's
gonna be a problem, just say so.
I can make it so she ain't.
No, no, okay?
She's part of the team.
Look, okay, I get it.
You're right. Fine.
Just forget anything I said,
all right?
Listen, good news,
we got the card.
But bad news is, well,
Sykes handed it off to me,
which was smart in the moment.
But to get out myself, I kind
of had to pass it off to a cop.
And now, I have no idea
where this cop is.
But don't worry about that.
All is well. All will be well.
We'll just track him down
and we'll get the card.
Hello?
[Winna] We are going
to be rich, my friend.
I told you, I got your back.
You have nothing to worry about.
Life is good. We're on top of
the world. I will speak to you soon.
Hello?
All right. Sounds good.
[line clicks]
[exhales]
Ho!
Hey, Mike!
[laughs]
Whoo!
[gunshot]
Yo, Mike.
[gunfire]
What the fuck is that?
[Mike] Case!
Fuck!
[groans]
[glass shattering]
Fuck.
Uh-uh.
[grunts]
[screams]
[both grunting]
[straining]
Die!
[exhales]
[panting]
[gun clicking]
[breathing heavily]
Okay, you're out of ammo.
This should be some fun.
[device beeps]
Hey, Mike!
Mike!
[groans]
You all right, buddy?
You fucking piece of shit.
Yo, I know this guy.
He's security for Winna.
Yo, Mikey?
You okay?
I'll get you to the hospital,
all right?
Okay, Mikey, look.
Hey, Mikey.
Hey, Mike! Mike!
Hey, buddy, you're okay.
You're okay.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
You're all right, buddy.
We're gonna get you to the
hospital. You're gonna be all right.
Hey, Mikey.
Oh, fuck. Mike!
[pants]
[breathing heavily]
[engine starts]
[wife] You think you're here?
- [phone dialing]
- [line ringing]
Come on, pick up. Pick up.
Hi.
Hey, baby.
Hi. Hi.
Lily, I need you to leave the
house, get Clara and get to a hotel.
What? What is... What...
Casey, what are you talking about?
Something fucked-up happened.
What did you do?
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
Hey, I need you to leave
the house right now, okay?
What did you do, Casey?
I don't have time to explain.
Just leave the house.
Jesus! I can't believe it.
Did you hurt someone?
No, it's not that.
Leave the house, Lily! Go!
[call ends]
Hell...
[fist thuds]
God!
Fuck. Fuck.
[line ringing]
[line clicks]
Mercer.
It's Rhodes. I need to meet.
[people chattering]
[knock on door]
We need to talk.
[door closes]
So, from the top.
Is Knight dirty?
[sighs]
I don't know. Maybe.
We think Winna's involved
in these heists?
Well, it's not a coincidence
that he was there.
[sighs]
How many cases has Knight
tanked for Winna?
Honestly, none.
[chuckles]
I think it was just a case of
"Looking the other way"
situation, you know?
But Knight doesn't let
anything slide, ever.
He's too proud.
Fitzgerald.
Who?
His partner. The one
who got shot by Rhodes.
Bet you Winna
threatened his life.
That explains it.
A bad guy said
he'd hurt his friend?
He is a cop.
He knows better than to let a
perp leave the scene of a heist.
And not just any perp.
FBI, CIA, ATF
all have open cases on Winna.
He's a slimy, rich
asshole bastard.
He's been sliding out of each and every
investigation, throwing his money around.
He is the cause of
what's wrong with this city.
He even used to be a CI and
played the force to eliminate his rivals.
You think we don't know
about Winna?
We have been on his ass
for years!
And two city cops from LA
walk in here
and think they're
gonna handle this shit,
fuckin' up
the whole entire case?
The woman, she said something?
Not a word.
Listen.
I can get her to speak.
Give me five minutes.
Be lucky you are not
in the cell next to her.
Knight goes anywhere
near this case or Winna,
I will have him
in a cell so long
it will rot
his fucking head off.
Get out of my office.
[exhales]
[San go sighs]
[horn honks]
[glasses clinking]
[people chattering]
[San go] You're a fucking disgrace
now. You don't deserve this badge.
Something is going on there.
He's got something on you.
[no audible dialogue]
[gunshot]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[beeps]
Hey, it's your favorite CI
Winna.
Just letting you know, Leach
will be coming by any second.
And, uh, don't forget,
Detective, you owe me.
[body thuds]
[exhales]
[phone ringing]
[phone vibrating]
[vibrating continues]
[ringing fades]
[Winna]
How's my favorite detective?
Yeah, what's it to you?
Oh, let's meet.
I think we should meet.
- [phone beeps]
- [line clicks]
[exhales, sniffs]
[breathing heavily]
[typing on phone]
Hey, baby.
[Lily] Hi, Casey.
You guys at the hotel?
Uh, no.
What do you mean?
We're not at the hotel.
No, no, no, no. Hey, no. No. I
need you... I need you to trust me.
This is insane.
Baby, I need you to trust me.
I need you to get your shit, get
Clara and get to a hotel right now.
No, I don't want to do that.
No!
You're being paranoid.
No, I'm not. I promise you.
You are being paranoid.
I'm not being paranoid, okay?
People are after me. You're
not safe. [Lily chuckles]
You're not safe. Well, I feel safe.
And I don't... I'm over this. I'm done.
You... Fuck.
[exhales]
[breathing heavily]
Oh, fuck.
Ah, fuck.
[exhales] Fuck.
They shot Mike.
And Sykes is locked up somewhere,
man. It's absolutely fucked.
[exhales]
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Hmm?
Can you try to have a heart?
I'm here, aren't I?
I mean, there,
that's some good news.
Man, you've always had a
fucked-up definition of good.
Man, if you're feeling
the heat, get...
You know, go to Mexico
or something.
Mexico, and then what?
Well, live.
Be free.
Not go to fucking jail.
Winna tried to wipe me out, man.
You have anything on you?
Jesus, man.
[pills rattling]
Just slow down, buddy.
[chewing pills]
Do you feel better?
Okay.
All right, so what's the play?
[exhales]
Well, Winna's not gonna stop
until I'm dead.
Probably. [chuckles]
So I gotta figure out a way
to get close to him.
And then what?
The fuck you think?
No, come on, bro.
You're not a fucking killer.
You've been a grumpy little
bitch ever since you shot that cop.
Man, fuck you.
Man, you're talking
about premeditated murder.
Not this fluffy little
self-defense shit.
You got to walk up to him,
put a gun to his fucking head
and pull the trigger.
Come on, Casey,
you're not that guy.
I know how we can get
close to him.
The card is
in a cop's desk, right?
So, we sneak into...
Sneak... [laughing]
We just gotta sneak
into a police station.
Fuck, right.
[sighs]
No, no, no, no, no.
One of us can.
[chuckles]
One of us can. Okay?
Just like a fucking
football play, brother.
I fucking fake left,
you go right.
[pops lips]
You say I do,
I'll fucking do it.
Dude, I can't let you... I can't ask
you to do that. I mean, come on.
I'll create a diversion,
get the cops to follow me.
All you gotta do is find
a way to get in there.
And guess what, baby?
It's fucking Halloween.
It is Halloween.
One time a year you can wear
a mask anywhere you want.
No...
Get creative.
It'd be fun.
[teller machine beeping]
Hey!
What's up?
Jesus Christ.
How are those Scots-Irish
genes treating you now?
Worse than the English.
Yeah.
You woke me up.
[scoffs]
All right, come on, pal.
It's still raining, isn't it?
[sighs] I'm losing my mind
trying to figure this out.
Nikki Sykes.
Ex-Olympic gymnast.
Finished fourth at Rio.
And then she got banned
for life from the sport.
For coming in fourth?
No.
For selling medical records
of her fellow Olympians.
They couldn't prove it.
Apparently, the buyer is a
guy who allegedly worked for...
Let me guess.
Winna.
That's right.
Mm-hmm.
Sykes hasn't said a word.
But these days, the metadata
on phones do all the talking.
So I got a buddy of mine at NSA,
you know, to QTap her phone.
Just to see what kind
of cluster of friends
she's chatting with
consistently.
Who else?
Mike Rochester.
Went to the same college as
Rhodes and got drafted by the Mets.
Mm-hmm.
And then only played
for one year, because...
Mm-hmm... he was partying
too much. They cut him.
Well, he's dead now.
They found his body in
his uncle's junkyard. Oh.
I guess Rhodes wanted
one less share to go around.
Yeah, that doesn't track.
[sighs]
They're not gonna
leave anybody behind.
What if it was Winna?
He knows heat is coming his way,
so he tried to merc them,
but screws the hit.
He-He knows that Mercer
and Rhodes won't go quietly.
Odds are pretty good.
I mean, they'll choose death
before they go to prison.
Mm-hmm. I think it's a
bet that Winna will take.
Has the card turned up?
No.
What about the DA?
Can you tie them
to the robberies?
The security guard
from the arena,
he thinks he can ID
Rhode's voice.
Circumstantial.
Nah, come on, man.
No witnesses.
Come on. Everyone
can see that it's them.
Rhodes executed both jobs
like it was straight
out of Belichick's playbook.
Why don't you call Bill up?
Maybe he's moonlighting.
Come on, don't be pithy.
You don't have
a shred of evidence.
These guys made a living
fighting over a pigskin.
I mean, it's not a big stretch
from being an ex-football
player... Mm-hmm.
...to becoming a bank robber.
Mm-hmm.
This was fun.
[inhales, exhales]
That's it?
[sniffs] You know,
I was thinking.
What if we try your way?
You know, like,
we go old school on them.
Just try to shake a few cages
and see what falls out.
Are you wearing a wire?
[chuckles] Come on,
you must be kidding.
Do you have something
on you now?
I just want to close this book on
these fuckers and just go back home.
I hate New York.
No, I don't.
Well, I do.
They can get to Fitz anytime.
I can't run that risk.
[chuckles]
If Fitz was in your shoes,
wouldn't you want him doing
everything in his power to stop Winna?
[horns honking]
[people chattering]
[pedestrians chattering]
[gun clicks]
[screams]
[all screaming]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[all screaming]
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
[grunts] - All right, everybody
stay on the fucking ground.
We're gonna make this
real quick. It's a bank robbery.
As you probably know,
load this fucking bag right now!
You! All against
the fucking wall.
Pull out your phones
and dial 911!
Okay. Now you call and say
to the New York police,
"Hello, we are being robbed
by the big, bad wolf.
And we're scared,
scared little piggies!"
You're gonna dial it!
Dial 911!
Thank you.
Send everybody who can,
every fucking piggy in the NYPD,
you send my fucking way.
[phone vibrates]
211 in progress.
[sighs]
[San go]
What don't we try your way?
He knows that Mercer
and Rhodes won't go quietly.
Nice badge.
I think we should meet.
And thank you very much.
You're very fast. Very efficient!
Okay, thank you very much!
Happy Halloween!
And have a wonderful,
wonderful day.
Don't stay up too late, piggies.
[siren wailing]
[officer] There he is!
[gun clicks]
[gunfire]
[sirens wailing]
[officer] Hold back, hold back.
Pull back! Pull back!
[panting]
[radio chatter]
[officer]
We have you surrounded.
Drop your weapon.
Come out with your hands up.
[gunfire]
[grunts]
Shit! Stay down, stay down!
[gagging]
Where's your partner?
[breathes heavily] Shoot me.
Where is Rhodes?
[Mercer] Shoot me.
Do it. Do it!
[Mercer] You pussy.
[grunting]
[officers chattering]
[radio clicks]
To all units,
be on the lookout
for one Casey Rhodes.
Male, Caucasian, in his 30s.
He's armed and dangerous.
[inhales, exhales]
[bell tolls]
Hi, I'm here
to pick up the, uh...
[officer]
Whatever. Go on in.
[door buzzes]
[lock clicks]
[sighs]
I can't see in this thing.
Good to see you.
You looking for something?
Ah, fuck!
[officers chattering]
Hop in. Are you, uh,
trying to be funny?
No, not at all.
[groans]
[Casey] Where are we going?
[engine starts] [louder]
Where are we going?
[car accelerates]
What, are you gonna drive me
somewhere and shoot me in the head?
What kind of cop are y...
[banging on trunk]
[panting]
Oh, fuck!
Uh... [panting]
[chuckles]
They treat you like royalty.
[crowd cheering]
Did you know that, Knight?
You know that.
You get the money, the fame.
The women.
And then the moment
you think you deserve it...
[bangs fist]
...boom, they take it away.
And all those people
you thought loved you,
they disappear too,
until all you're left with
is migraines and a fucked knee!
[whistle blows]
And a confused family
who just wants the old you back.
[pants]
I just want it to end.
I mean, you get it, don't you?
You're always trying
to be normal.
But you're not normal.
You don't even know
what normal is,
so you... you do
what they trained you to do.
You... You... You keep moving.
You go faster. You jump higher.
You hit harder.
Always chasing.
Winna knew that!
Are you even listening to me?
Are you listening to me?
They threatened my family.
Winna's gonna send Brigga
after them.
And I know... I know if I...
If I have this card,
I can get close to him.
And if I can get close to him,
I... I can make sure that he
never hurts anybody ever again.
I don't want my daughter
to grow up without her father.
I mean, she's...
She's my... She's my world.
And I did all of this for her.
I mean,
that's not completely true.
I did a lot of it for me.
I did a lot of it for me, man.
I just...
[bangs fist]
Fuck.
You fucking idiot.
Yeah,
it fucking serves me right.
[engine roaring]
[car door closes]
Oh, God. Damn it. Fuck.
[panting]
Winna.
You know Winna's got guards
everywhere, right?
So?
All right, give me a gun.
[gun clicks]
Give me a fucking gun.
Please?
[bird calling]
Ah!
[grunts, body thuds]
[pants]
Knight is here.
- [gunfire over radio]
- [guard grunts]
[Winna] You were right. We
should have gotten more guards.
[gunshot]
[static hums]
- [doorbell rings]
- [Winna] Goddamn. Rhodes too?
That means the cops
aren't far behind.
[exhales]
Will you just kill the guy?
Please?
Now?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Where's the card?
The cash first.
I got your cash.
[grunts]
[both straining]
[bullets clattering]
[Brigga grunting]
Kill the cop.
Move on the family.
[grunts]
[both grunt]
[panting]
[bullets clatter on floor]
Fuck.
I gotta do everything myself.
[gun clicks]
[Brigga panting]
Get out of the way.
[Brigga straining]
[Brigga grunting]
Motherfucker.
Hey!
[grunting]
[straining]
Wish he'd have wrote.
[both straining]
Fuck!
How's the knee?
[screams, grunts]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[both grunting]
Guards!
[panting]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[strains]
Trick or treat, motherfucker!
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
[Brigga straining]
[two gunshots]
[grunting]
I wanted this for a long time.
Fuck.
[gunshot]
[grunts, groans]
[body thuds]
[breathes heavily]
[footsteps receding]
[exhales]
[sirens wailing]
[officer] Sir, we found
Knight. Rhodes ran off.
Uh, what do you want us
to do about Knight, sir?
Take him.
[radio clicks]
Don't move. Hold it.
[officer 2] Cuff him.
[radio chatter]
[officer 1] We got him.
[officers chattering]
[knock on door]
Trick or treat.
[candy rattles]
The other house had
full-size candy bars.
Oh, thank you.
[chuckles]
Come on.
[exhales]
You having fun?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
[chuckles]
Wait.
[sirens wailing in distance]
- Hey. Hey.
- Casey?
No, no.
- [officer] Hands up.
- No.
[officer] Hands up!
Oh, my God.
No, sweetie. No. No.
You got the right
to remain silent. Easy.
Stop hurting my dad!
Oh, my God.
Don't do anything to my dad!
[Casey] I'm sorry, baby. I'm so sorry!
I'll find a way
to make this right!