Further cleaned, corrected, & timing
re-adjusted for YIFY release by Tronar
Lucky ring on.
I feel so much safer.
We're coming in hot.
Hold on.
Let's go.
What's the hold up?
Nothing, we're on our way.
Let's go.
Your dude's trippin'.
Stay on the wall, beware.
- Hey, forget this maniac.
- I'm not leaving him.
Doc!
You're just gonna roll up on me huh?
After 8 damn years.
What's up with that?
You're in a black ops prison that
doesn't officially exist.
I just got the location from a guy named Church.
An agency spook.
Excuse me?
Agency's official relax.
Thank you for this, man.
What a waste of life!
You make one damn mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
It was stupid. You'd done that to me,
I would've chopped you into pieces.
You would've tried.
Hey, you want to thank the guys?
The guys?
Where are our guys?
- Hammer, Guzman...
- Gone.
They've gone?
Yeah.
Damn!
Heard you killed more people than the plague!
How 'bout that?
That why they called you "Doctor Death"?
Used to be a medic.
But that was a long time ago.
So why'd you get locked away?
Tax evasion.
So you're all that's left of The Expendables?
We're it.
We started out with 5...
built up to 22
I see Barney still hanging the tags up there.
See that jingling sounds the tags make,
that's a reminder that our brothers are still here.
Somewhere.
Come on viking.
Give me an old school of your blade.
Or else you might find your tags up there.
Jingling too.
Jingling... jingling jingling.
Sharpen it when you're done.
I think your friend is a little off.
Come on Christmas, he's been in
a hole for eight years.
How'd he get so lucky!
He tried pulling it off
his half-assed political...
assassination for a few bucks
in this place called Swaziland.
And he blew it.
Self destructive?
Yes something like that.
But in all those years he's a good medic.
Well, I don't need a checkup.
- Why are you so sarcastic?
- You're vague.
- Vague?
- Secrets, idiot.
I mean why do you take me off
half way round the planet?
To save this medical genius,
as you describe.
For what?
- He's an Expendable.
- Oh my god.
Come on.
He's an Expendable.
So he's one of the flock?
Let me tell you something...
If you were incarcerated for years,
I'd come and save you.
Thanks hero!
But I doubt it.
And I know you'd do the same for me.
Truthfully?
You'd let me rot?
Exactly.
Hey, Doc.
What's your name?
Christmas.
Is that real?
Authentic.
Is that real too?
Oh no, I uh... spend 3 hours every morning
putting this on with a black biro.
This is real.
Authentic.
Original.
Look at that.
Balance is a little off.
You uh, a knife man?
Best, ever
I'm the knife before Christmas.
Ain't that right Barney?
If you say so.
Probably freestyling with a blade while
you're still sucking on your daddy's titty...
trying to learn how to eat with a spoon.
Yeah.
You know that little secret you were
keeping there, Mr. Vaguo?
Just stay out of my brain.
I'm gonna tell you.
I can't wait to get home.
Eat some good food...
Put on some fine threads...
Break up my 49' Pontiac...
Keep that baby until the engine blows up...
You didn't tell him did you?
Tell me what?
We're not going home.
We're stopping at a
dealer named Victor Menz...
delivering a shipment
of thermobaric bombs.
Ow, come on man.
That shit is hellfire.
Hey, it's routine stuff.
You know why don't you just
pick me up on your way back.
We're a man short.
Well, you know, I'd love
to party with you boys.
But, uh, I don't have my shit.
That's my shit!
It is your shit.
Doc, have you thanked the guys,
helping you out?
Say something.
Uh, listen up...
It's been a long time since I had
a reason to say thank you...
So I just want..
Oh, you know I...
- He's getting his rhythm.
- Just want to say.
Thank you.
Sincerity is overwhelming.
I think I'm gonna weep.
You know what? Enough.
Do not be sarcastic.
That was great, Doc.
You haven't had to talk for a long time.
You got the gift.
It's like riding a bike.
I liked Churchill's best.
I think I made my point.
- I've moved you too.
- Stunning.
Doc, great to have you back.
No better place to be, yeah.
About time you boys showed up.
Nice boat.
Thanks ladies, built it myself.
Got three more just like it patrolling the harbor.
Two man ground teams every 400m.
Good work.
Just cause you can fly a plane
don't make you smarter than me.
Sure it does.
So you're the reason I've been
stuck down here in this shithole.
Shithole?
Brother you have no idea.
Oh yeah, hahahaha.
What the hell is that?
This bitch will solve all your problems.
Yeah, maybe for 10 seconds...
- before he blows his wad.
- So now you got that problem too?
You walked into that one.
Come on, look alive, look alive.
Good luck.
It was all under control.
Yeah, that's what it looked like.
Where you've been?
I had a doctors' appointment.
Catch up with you boys later.
What's he got?
Watch your overhead.
Doc, go.
Ooh sadly, the man attacked me with a knife.
He's good.
Maybe to you.
You might want to see this.
See what?
I'll show you.
Damn!
He's really good.
Say it again and I'll shoot you.
Get in.
Where's the bomb?
It'll be here.
Barney, looks like the target is right on time.
There's Menz, let's take 'em out fast.
Barney, I'm gonna put you down.
It can't be.
What can't be?
We're gonna shoot these guys or what?
What's the hold up?
He's dead.
Who's dead?
Stonebanks.
Come on, get in.
Come on, move!
Go go go!
Come on!
Time to mow the lawn!
I told you
10 seconds.
Hang on.
Found you a ride.
Time to go.
Come on.
Go go go!
- How much we're getting paid for this?
- Not enough.
Go right.
You're not gonna fit.
Always negative.
I'm getting carsick.
Hang on, Doc.
Get out.
Come on.
Caesar.
We're coming your way, where are you?
In this filthy river, behind you.
Try to stay as close as you can.
Make room for Caeser.
Move your ass in.
Who's that?
A huge black guy on a boat.
Hold it, hold it, you got it going.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Pull over.
Incoming!
Move!
We got you man, come on!
Maybe this'll bring you luck.
Is he gonna make it?
I don't know.
Who did this?
Stonebanks.
I thought you killed him.
So did I.
He shot Caeser to get back at me.
Yeah, I'm getting out of this business.
And so should you.
Not yet.
Hey.
If you need any help with
Stonebanks...
I'm supposed to meet a guy named Church.
I know who you are.
So who are you?
Operations officer Drummer.
You don't have to worry about Church anymore.
He's um, he's out of the picture
Jesus, Ross.
What a mess!
We gave you everything.
Target, opportunity, all the intel you could ask for.
And you got decimated.
And my target walked away.
Am I wrong huh?
Am I missing something?
Yeah, sure you said the target's name was Victor Menz.
- And?
- It was wrong.
His real name was Conrad Stonebanks.
We knew him only as Victor Menz.
Arms dealer, made billions selling to every
psycho warlord in Africa and the Middle East.
His own mercenary army is personally responsible...
for the torturing and killing...
two of the best men I ever knew, friends.
I don't give a shit what his name is.
I don't like him.
I want him as bad as you do.
This happened on my watch.
You fucked up, and I'm wearing it
I'll find him.
Again.
You have one more shot.
Nice to finally meet you Barney.
Your men are shot to shit, what are
you gonna do for a team.
Don't worry about it.
I'll handle it.
Relax.
You're gonna give yourself a stroke.
What's with these guys!
Do you mind?
Do you think when the artist
painted this, he ever
thought it would go for
such a ridiculous price?
I mean what is this? Just some paint, brushes,
some cheap canvas, what's the big deal?
It's shit.
What do you want for it?
Three million.
Done.
You know...
It's very hard for me to say this...
but at one time, you guys were the best.
Maybe still are.
But nothing lasts forever.
Hard as it is to hear.
We're not the future anymore.
Unfortunately for us.
We're part of the past.
You.. arr.. you going somewhere with this?
As I see it.
If we keep this life up...
The only way this thing ends...
for all of us
is in a hole in the ground and no-one givin' a shit.
Now, if that's the
way I'm supposed
to go out, I can live with that.
For me.
But what I can't live with.
And I won't live with...
is taking you with me.
What are you saying?
That's our call.
I'm changing things now.
You.
Me.
All of us.
It's over.
We're done.
Done? You break me out...
Cut me loose?
You'll survive.
You all will.
You live your lives while you can.
Where are you going, Barney?
Hey you think you just pulled the plug and that's it?
- Just did.
- Yeah?
Well it doesn't work that way.
What?
We've been through the mud...
the shit and the blood.
And I've saved your arse more times than I can count.
You owe me a shot at the sonofabitch
that took Caeser down.
We're not doing that.
When I joined,
I joined for the whole ride.
I know you did.
Rides over.
Bonaparte.
Sorry to hear about Caeser.
I hope he pulls through, he's a
good one, the good ones are rare.
Yeah.
Well, here we are again.
What do you need?
New team.
Retired the old ones.
Welcome to the 21st century.
How many guys you looking for?
Young, hungry, willing to take a bullet.
I'm going after Stonebanks.
Stonebanks.
Let's see, you're not the
only one slipping a notch.
Stonebanks is dead my friend mortus dei.
No, he's not.
That is not good.
If he was half of what he used to be,
four or five ain't gonna cut it.
You're gonna need fifty.
We gotta move fast, no time.
If I got to do it fast then I can't guarantee the best.
Just give me something that don't give a damn.
What?
Is this a one way ticket?
Could be.
Fine.
I got a line on a few head cases.
Couple of these guys'll probably
end up shooting themselves.
Wait.
What about these guys?
They anything?
These guys are pussies.
Goes by Thorn, expert hacker.
Ground pilot.
Did 18 months for hacking into
Seattle central operating system.
Shut down the whole city for 3 days.
Why the hell would he do that?
Because he can.
What?
I'm not looking for an office worker.
Oh! that's not him.
That's him.
Another one with a death wish.
You two got a lot in common.
I could do that.
You know what?
I'm gonna come around and say it.
I belong on you.
- You can't do that.
- No.
I'd want a special rate on that one.
Yeah, yeah, that's the pecker.
Always on the damn road going
someplace you don't give a damn about.
Beats standing still.
Yeah, I got two ex-wives...
and three kids who've lost my number who'd disagree.
- Hey did you turn off the autopilot?
- I didn't touch the autopilot.
Gimme the booze.
Are we off course?
Where the hell are we?
Hang on a second.
Is that the Big Dipper?
Yeah, we gotta turn around.
Next candidate is an expert in field
craft and close quarters combat.
Luna.
Hi.
Young lady, meet a friend of mine. Barney Ross.
Barney Ross, Luna. Luna, Barney Ross.
- How you're doing?
- Nice to meet you Mr. Ross.
Gentlemen if you'd follow me,
I have your table waiting.
Come on.
Live a little.
So Luna how are things?
You know, gets old.
- What did I do?
- You wanna go, bro?
Would you guys excuse me...
All right so what are we doing here?
Have a drink.
Where's your candidate?
Right there in the red dress about
to chop those guys in half.
- The hostess?
- Not the hostess.
She's the bouncer.
I could do that.
You want to slip on a dress and give it a shot.
Men.
She's good.
You oughta see her without heels.
When was your last checkup?
I don't know, a while back.
High cholesterol, plaque, all that stuff.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Yeah.
Except with me.
They found a lump on my lung.
Very dark, they said.
Why shouldn't I see that coming?
Well, what do you do?
I try to make as much money as I can,
fast as I can.
For those kids, you know.
The ones I don't talk to.
Make some kind of a good impression
on them, before I'm gone.
Sad, isn't it?
Yeah, it is sad. I'm sorry.
Nah, that's all bullshit, I'm fine.
Just checking you're still human.
Had you going there now didn't I?
Yeah, you did goddammit.
That can never happen again.
I'll never trust you again.
Next kid's a bit of a dark horse.
Just came across my desk. I don't
like throwing in a wildcard.
But this guy's creds were too good to pass up.
Anybody seen Felipe?
Yo Felipe.
Looks good Bonaparte.
Yeah, not bad.
Finally got it right.
Damn!
Felipe Silva!
Meet Barney Ross.
Galgo.
Galgo, you sent me another fake resume.
Mr. Ross, I can do what you need, whatever you need.
I am healthier than I look, stronger than I look...
Faster than I look.
Actually, shit, you were born in 1984?
Of course not.
But I feel like that I was born in 1984.
Do not waste your time, Barney we're leaving.
Mr. Ross, Mr. Ross, Mr. Ross.
Please.
It's like uh, it's like I have discovered..
the fountain of youth.
I mean, not.. 'The fountain of youth'.
Ponce de Leon discovered that one.
Um by the way...
Another great Spaniard, like myself.
Mr. Ross.
Age is just a state of mind.
You're only old, when you surrender...
When you give up, and I haven't, not yet.
- Galgo, this shit has got to stop.
- I gotta go.
This is the third time this month.
Seriously, move on.
What's this guy's story?
Actually I feel a little sorry for him.
His last team dropped him.
Back in the day, you couldn't catch him.
- Very fast, maybe even faster than you.
- No way.
Oh! maybe.
But, what am I gonna say.
It's a young man's game.
I need a job!
All I know what to do is killing people
And I do that very well.
Damn! Dammit!
- What's the story on this guy?
- Found him at DARPA.
- DARPA?
- Sounds like a town in North Africa.
Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency.
Where they send the brightest military
minds to develop next-gen weapons.
Google it.
I'm not looking for weapons nerd.
Ah, then you've come to the right place.
Yo Marlito.
Mars I like you to meet Barney Ross.
As shooters go, Mars is as gifted as they get.
Whatever you say.
What do you say?
What I've got here is an X-25 assault rifle.
Laser range, 25mm high explosive air burst rounds.
Can be programmed to detonate
over or behind the target.
He'll do.
Final candidate, John Smilee.
Guy's got the most teeth in the industry.
A lot of skills, Marines, special operator.
- But there is, an issue.
- What issue?
Yeah, classic authority problem.
There's a couple more swimming around in there too.
Sorry Barney for wasting your time like this.
He's not the guy I thought he was.
No.
I want to meet him.
John.
Meet Barney Ross.
Didn't do much to impress out there today did you?
You called me, I didn't call you.
Think you'd die for the money?
Maybe you like getting your ass
kicked in front of strangers.
What do you guys want from me?
You running from something?
I don't know you.
But I know you.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
How's that?
Maybe he thinks you got potential and
we're short on time. That about right?
That's about it.
What's your problem?
Your problem is you're rolling around
in the dirt for chump change.
I hear you lost a few friends in the desert.
They bought it, and you didn't.
And you wear the guilt.
I've been there.
He's been there.
We all lived it.
Well you don't know me.
I know the type.
Bonaparte, you're right.
You did waste my time.
Hey...
You didn't waste your time.
If you're going after Stonebanks,
we might want to talk about financials now.
Normally it's just 10%, but..
I figured with Stonebanks in the equation
I might want to get my fee... possibly now.
I mean, not that you're not good for it,
just, if you don't mind.
I don't mind.
It sounds like you don't have too much faith in me.
I don't.
How was your vacation?
Ready to go to work?
You find him yet?
He's in Bucharest putting together
a deal with some Albanian mobster.
You got 36 hours, that's your window.
After that he's back off the grid.
Satellite map...
Coordinates for where he'll be.
Interesting guy.
Your friend Stonebanks.
You're not gonna like this but...
They want him alive.
Are you kidding me?
They want to try him at The Hague...
for war crimes.
You're gonna give this guy a chance in court?
It's not my decision.
- No, it never is.
- That's the way it's gotta be.
Great.
Agency's got a local safehouse.
You're gonna need it.
Don't trash the place.
I heard you got a job.
That's right.
Who the hell are they?
They're with me.
And we're not?
Gunner I had told you everything
I had to tell you back at the bar.
And stop drinking so much.
You want to get yourself killed...
with those youngsters.
Do us all a favor and get the hell out of here.
Wheels up in 10.
If your guys wanted to fight,
why didn't they just get married?
You seriously smoking next to aviation fuel?
Amateur.
Amateur assholes.
Who you calling asshole, grandpa?
Grandpa's about to crush your windpipe.
What is this? Is this your toy?
Boy?
You want to dance big guy?
Hey! It's just a job.
Come on, let's go.
Bunch of ass has been's still trying to be hard.
You're young and you're dumb.
Jingling jingling.
Keep it.
You're gonna need it.
Never thought you would call in that favor.
I'm also not happy about it.
Got a minute?
What do you need?
Tell me more about this guy we're going after.
It doesn't matter, you were hired to do a job.
How about answering why we're doing this job?
I owe you a salary that's it.
Why are we going after Stonebanks?
You have a hard time taking orders don't you?
If I don't know what they are, yeah.
I know you don't give a damn about us.
I get that.
But just tell me why you want
to take out this guy so bad.
Thirty seconds to drop.
Copy that.
Let's go.
I can take care of myself.
Twenty seconds to drop.
Ten seconds...
We're on.
This guy's got more muscle than a cartel king.
Maybe he's overcompensating for something.
What you're drinking down there, Barney?
Is that like vanilla latte or something?
Stay sharp.
Move.
You have to think about this again Mr. Menz.
I promise you this won't happen again.
- Move the car.
- I'm talking to you!
Nice driving Mars.
Good performance.
Yeah, too good.
Any closer and I'd beat his ass.
I believe her.
Got 'em.
Oh man, this guy's protected better than the president.
Yeah, and his crib's like a 5-star fortress.
Listen we're not taking him there.
I bet the hotel is full of guests.
So where do we hit them?
At the meet.
We'll hit him from all four sides.
Hit him hard.
OK, um, so...
Our plan is to what? Kick down the
door and start spraying bullets?
It's a great plan...
If it's 1985.
And what's that supposed to mean?
You heard me.
You got a better plan?
Much better.
Let's hear it.
Thorn, you're up.
OK, I'm the plan.
This better be good.
First I hack the security grid main server, boom.
Bypass the motion detector lasers
and biometric sensors, pow.
Override the surveillance videos
and CCTV systems, ba-bam.
And we are in.
It's child play.
Just like that?
Just like that.
Exactly, like that.
You better be right.
Ba-bam.
Let's go.
So why'd you let your team go?
If you stick around long enough
you're gonna buy it. It was time.
They didn't seem too happy about it.
If you're looking to go the family route,
it's the wrong job for you.
There are different kinds of family.
And when my life is on the line.
That's my family fighting with me.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Right on time.
Ladies first.
Go ahead then, Thorn.
Will you shut up and get in the sewer.
And ladies and gentlemen, we
officially have eyes in the sky.
Copy that.
Let's do this.
Thought you'd never ask.
Good to go.
Good luck boys.
Woah! Shit!
What's the problem?
The buyer, they're early.
Threat just doubled.
You're early.
What do you think?
It's OK.
When Cain slew his brother.
God banished him from civilization.
But before that he placed a mark on him.
It was a felon's brand, but...
to protect him from roving hunters.
Customs does not X-ray artwork.
It ruins the oils.
Very good.
There you have it.
Gabil.
My pleasure.
As always.
Can you access nuclear weapons?
I might.
But generally I find people are a
little too emotional for ownership.
And I'd hate you killing all my
other customers by accident.
Or on purpose.
In position.
Set.
I pay you what you want.
Let me think about it.
We're on.
Stonebanks is moving, watch it.
Like little mice...
Try again.
Open sesame.
Go go go.
Move.
Go.
Barney Ross says hello.
Nice job.
Trench, you copy?
I'm waiting.
Package is secured.
Hurry up.
It's boring.
Why don't you just a bullet in
his head and be done with it.
Hey, you said we were taking him in.
Good morning.
Are these your students?
Hey kids, what'd you learn tonight huh?
What happened to the old crew?
Oh that's right.
They stuck their noses into other
people's worlds and got fatally injured.
Now they're The Deletables.
Hey, you hear that kids?
Take note cause that's what
you're doing right now.
Let me shut his mouth.
You're talking pretty tough to a guy who's
incapacitated, which is good for you.
Is it?
Why don't you cut me loose and I'll open your
meat shirt and show you your own heart.
Hey Barney.
Why don't the two of us just end this?
What do you say?
Mix it up, either you snapping
my spine or me snapping yours.
You know, make it snappy.
He thinks I'm joking.
I'm not joking.
You should see me when I'm angry.
You'd be very impressed.
And very dead.
So, come on pal.
Anything you want to get off your chest.
Come on, lay it out.
I'm a good listener.
You're gonna take me back to the has been crew?
Carve me up around a fire.
Very tribal.
When we stop, I wanna break every bone in your body.
And drop what's left at The Hague.
The Hague. I finally made the big-time.
I'm a war criminal.
Keep laughing.
Do you think,
that you can just deliver me like a package?
We were close once.
See we started this whole
Expendables thing together, see?
Look I've got the marks.
They're a bit faded but, we had a falling out.
You went dark.
It's a dark business Barney,
don't pretend you're not in it.
The baddest survive, those are
the rules, I didn't make them up.
You see Barney here was content
to work for the small end money.
As an employee.
Now being boss is more lucrative but that's
a concept that somehow eluded you.
Plus you got that pesky moral conscience.
God that stuff gets in the way.
He thinks he's the good guy.
Keep talking while you can.
Sure, you got a conscience that makes you weak.
Success, real success...
is being willing to do the things
that other people are not.
Not everyone's as sick as you.
Oh, but you are.
Did you kill anyone today Barne?
Blow any shit up?
How bout you kids? Kill anyone?
Before you all start grabbing bricks
to stone me at The Hague.
You might want to check your own hands for blood.
But I digress. Where was I?
Yes, business is booming right?
A chopper here, a missile there, guns.
Whatever, when suddenly
a competitor.
If you can call Uncle Sam a competitor.
Hires my own team. Barney and
the whole gang to whack me.
Things got ugly real fast and a lot of people got dead.
Three former brothers in arms.
- Shut your mouth.
- Three Expendables.
Our brothers, men we ate with,
fought with, bled with, dead!
He puts three slugs into my chest.
Thank God...
for body armor, even I thought I was dead.
And then he boogies out with the casualties, all dead!
Because you couldn't
stay out of my business!
Shut your mouth!
Go on, do it!
- Go on!
- It's what he wants.
It's hard to fathom.
I can't believe you forgot.
What?
That it's hard to beat an enemy when
he's living inside your own head.
You see you tie me up.
Like an animal.
Leave me to the slaughter.
You humiliate me. Disgrace me.
Now when the time comes to kill you.
And it will. I will not use a weapon.
I will use my hands.
Because I want you to feel the
way that I feel right now...
cause we were brothers.
What's that?
It's a GPS tracker.
How about that?
Hold it.
We may need them.
I need a body, find him.
What happened?
We found a shitstorm.
It's gonna getting worse.
This came in for you, 10 minutes ago.
Hey Barney.
My search party's dead so
I'm taking it you're still with us.
Now you should've killed
me when you had the chance
cause that's your last
window, and it's gone.
Now, I got something to show you here.
Lida, Harpo, Groucho, Gummo, and Chica.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Hey, give her a little squeeze, there.
Personally, I'd chalk it up to collateral
damage, but I don't give a fuck.
But, I know you.
- 48 hours and they're gone for good.
- You want them?
Come get them.
What are you gonna do?
Wow, looking a little strung out there kids.
This is what you get for being pawns
in Barney's moral chess game.
That one looks a little slack.
You know I feel most bad for you.
I don't give a shit how you feel.
I do, I have a daughter.
I have feelings, anyway.
You know, when the CIA, I, er
presume that's who you're working for.
The CIA, am I right?
I bet you don't even know who you're working for.
But for Barney?
Do you know who he's working for?
Does he know who he's working... I...
It gets very confusing.
Anyway, when the CIA wanted
guys doing the dangerous work...
in the dangerous places...
they called us. When they didn't
want to get their hands dirty...
they called us.
Yup, we cleared every hotspot they had.
We bumped the bad guys so that the
good guys could roll in looking like heroes.
We killed a lot.
But we saved more lives...
than you can possibly imagine.
Then the boys on the hill
wanting no loose ends.
Tried to bury me.
I was an American.
Working for America.
Was.
They'd eat their own children.
The lesson here is...
Never do business with the government.
I'm gonna save you that heartache.
You never will.
So you're getting your old team?
Nah, I've burned that bridge.
You know your pride is gonna get you killed.
Better me than them.
- So you're really gonna go back?
- Yeah.
- Alone?
You're an idiot.
Thanks for showing up.
I guess our favors are done.
But you're still an idiot.
How the hell did you find me?
People talk.
I hear things.
You got a mission...
I can help.
My name is Galgo.
Let me fill you in.
I am good, very good.
At warfare.
You know good memory, afraid of nothing.
I want to be your friend.
I don't need a friend.
Yes, you do.
Everybody does.
I don't have any friends
That's why I know.
Besides my friendship issues,
what I really need now is something to do.
Well, not just anything but...
what I was born to do.
Best bet, this is a one way trip.
Excuse me sir, but...
one way trip...
is better than no way...
which is the way I live now.
Help me with the crate.
I'm sorry.
On the plane, Gogo.
On the plane, yes. But Gogo no Gogo, Galgo.
- Galgo.
- Gogo sounds like a Parisian hooker.
I am the bridegroom of death.
The lyrics of a Spanish legion old songs.
That we used to sing when
we're on a mission in Croatia.
That's where I met Mingo.
The best point man ever.
Some kind of savant. You don't know
ambush this guy couldn't sniff. And under fire...
the coolest cat ever.
Just pure ice in his veins.
We were pinned down once like two bullets left.
I looked over...
Not one bead of sweat.
Yeah.
Can I help you up there?
You're a mechanic now?
Of course I am a mechanic.
I am whatever you need me to be, sir.
OK. Then just be quiet.
Yes, sir.
Tiger,
This sniper I knew.
I mean, this guy got it all figured out.
Wind speed, temperature...
Barometric pressure.
But you know what he said was the most important?
No.
Patience.
Really?
Yes, he said that.
This thing smells good, what is that?
Kerosene? Gasoline?
Aviation fuel.
It's good.
The best team member ever, his name was Torres.
Holy shit!
You wouldn't believe what this guy was capable to do.
Un...bel...ievable.
I'm telling you, man.
- Galgo?
- Yes, sir.
I think I know why your team let you go.
You do?
Really?
Yes.
Last chance.
You sure you want to do this?
I like traveling.
Good.
Uh, who are those guys?
My old team.
What the hell are you doing here?
You were stupid enough to
get yourself into this mess.
We're the only ones crazy
enough to get you out of it.
Come on.
We're late for a war.
Galgo you might want to get out
of that seat, Christmas is coming.
But it's June.
Galgo, get the hell out.
Yes, sir.
My hat.
I'm curious.
What?
Since when did suicide become your hobby?
I got a will.
You know I'm probably the
only friend you've got.
I got lots of friends.
You walk into a room,
people jump on the tables.
I missed you, Christmas.
I miss you too, you demented bastard.
You could've left it demented.
It's a kind of a solid structure
that is taking us from one place to another
through unbelievable speeds.
Think about it.
If God... if God... if he
would've liked us you know flying.
He would've given us feathers.
Do you have feathers?
- I don't have feathers.
- It's gonna be a long ass flight fellas.
It's going to be.
It's going to be a long flight but don't worry...
I'm here, because I can't sleep on planes...
Yeah.
Thought you should know Barney,
you're walking into a shitstorm.
NSA ran a signals and frequencies
check on your team's phones.
This bastard's not even trying to hide them.
Where has he taken them?
They're in Azmanastan.
Another honeymoon hotspot.
Who is that?
Lee Christmas.
Not far off, Christmas.
Stonebanks's compound is where he trains his goons.
It's very heavily fortified.
What's up with the local army?
I don't understand a word this guy is saying.
Local army status.
Small, corrupt.
Stonebanks got all the brass in his pocket.
Been running his operations through
this shithole of a country for years.
Want some advice?
- What's the advice?
- What goddamn language is that?
They don't teach you
that on the stage either.
Look who's talking.
What's the advice Drummer?
Forget about what you're thinking.
Remember our deal.
We need him alive.
So he can sit in a courtroom
and beat this on a technicality?
Those are orders, Barney.
- You broke the phone.
- I got another one.
Think we'll make it back from this one?
You didn't have to come along, Christmas.
Sure I did.
Morons need friends.
Gentlemen.
Change of plans.
This is it?
This is your evac team?
Short notice.
Yeah.
Very short.
Where is your team?
Major Drummer?
No team, this one's off the books.
I'm not even here.
Nobody's here.
I thought Church was asshole.
Yeah, hysterical is strength. Weird.
Yes, a weird concept.
I mean, if you're hysterically strong...
you don't even have to go to the gym.
You are just strong. You just got it.
You just got it.
Hysterical was a concept that
actually was applied to women...
in the 19th century.
It's a 'dosimonenic' concept.
You know what I mean.
Well, this is an interesting place...
He gave me a migraine.
I hear that.
Don't you think?
Look on the bright side.
You run out of bullets,
you can talk him to death.
Roger that.
Tall one doesn't like me.
He doesn't like anybody.
- What you say?
- He likes you.
What the hell is that?
What?
That computer strapped to your wrist.
Nothing.
The same thing you were
busting that kid's balls about.
Nah, I had it for a while now.
Why'd your team let you go?
Why is it matter now?
I want to know who I'm working with.
They are not around anymore.
So...
This um,
So why'd they let you go?
They didn't.
Benghazi.
I was not in the army anymore. We were...
retrieving a hostage something like uh...
like what we are doing here.
It was a beautiful day.
No problems.
And then it all went bad.
We got hit, cut off...
Waited for support, no one came.
Everybody died.
Except me.
Galgo...
Torres and Tiger were right.
You were listening.
Yeah, I was listening.
Thank you.
So what do you think?
I think we should get this over with.
Four signals.
Eight stories up.
This is way too wrong.
Sally don't like it.
You know he's got eyes on us now.
- May I suggest something?
- No. No, later.
That's what I thought.
That's fine.
Go.
Break it.
What the hell!
Hello, Barney.
I knew you couldn't stay away.
But I'm relieved that someone
could pick up the kids.
You got them in there,
now try getting them out.
But unfortunately for you...
The entire complex has been wired with C-4.
It'd take a regular Joe about 90 seconds to
get out of there. You got, how about 45?
He's turned this whole place into a bomb.
Maybe not.
Hey!
9% battery power? You didn't charge it?
Excuse me but what are you doing?
Try to run some code, should be able to jam the signal.
Why didn't you think of that?
Well I use it to check the weather.
Will you just shut up and let him do his thing?
You sure you're gonna do this Thorn?
I can do it, I can do it.
Come on, man.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Thorn.
Come on.
You're good, come on Thorn.
Focus, focus.
Got it.
Good job, my boy.
We lost override. The signal is jammed.
Send them in.
Barney the battery's at 8%.
When this thing dies, we lose override.
That gives us about 25 minutes tops.
Don't pop the bottles yet, we still got trouble.
- What?
- Big trouble.
Lucky again bro.
Try to enjoy the view because shortly the
building that you're currently standing in
will be surrounded by the Azmanastan army.
- How did you shitheads manage to get captured anyway?
- Shut the fuck up!
Step back.
This is not an accident.
And we're trapped in here.
This is exactly what he knew would happen.
Us, tearing at each other.
This stops now.
We can do this.
But only if we do this together.
If we work as a team.
We just may get out of this alive.
Now do you, want to make it work.
That simple.
You got any weapons?
Here's the plan. We're gonna
break up into small groups.
And go out through the ground floor.
Get ready.
Come on.
- Thorn, you stay with me.
- You take Galgo.
Yeah I don't want to.
What, what? Shhh...
Don't stop!
One there, one there.
There's too many!
They're on our flank. Bring it to 'em.
That's enough, light them up.
Incoming.
Up the shaft Thorn.
You gotta protect that signal jammer.
I thought you could fight.
Jesus God, you're OK?
Do not worry. I love this.
Good keep moving.
Relax.
I told you you'd give yourself a stroke.
You got a tank problem pal.
Do something about it.
I'm on it.
Trench, on your right.
That's gotta hurt.
Drummer's in the house.
Let's go.
Time to pick up the tempo boys.
Look out for the chopper.
Not good.
Hold on.
This is not happening.
You want to do something?
Put me down! Put me down!
Oh shit!
Hi there.
Closer.
Yang, hit something.
Next.
Your name is Luna right?
Luna means moon.
Hypnotic, mysterious, magical, like yourself.
Would you like to hold my gun?
Goodbye, sweet.
There he is!
Come on, drive this thing.
This one's for Caesar, assholes.
Yeah!
Damn that's cool.
It was all under control.
That's what it looked like.
Come on!
This the happiest moment of my life.
Jingling jingling.
You finished here?
Men!
- You're not gonna believe this.
- Oh, god.
I've been thinking of you the whole time.
- During the whole fight!
- Can we just go?
Come on.
Hold up.
Where did you learn how to fly?
In Tehran.
Warning, we got reinforcements.
Shit.
Drummer, there's another wave coming.
The only way out is up.
On my way.
Evac in 5.
Got it.
Everybody get to the roof now.
Trench, Yang, come on, clear the roof.
Let's go.
Damn.
- Always this easy?
- Pretty much.
How hard can it be to kill 10 men?
You think you could even just wound a couple?
Watch closely.
And again.
Anybody else?
Useless bunch...
You want something done right...
You got valet parking here?
Yeah, there's some right here.
Go go go.
Don't stop.
Come on guys, move it.
Drummer, we're pinned down.
Stop mumbling.
Good morning.
Let's get to the chopper.
Let's go.
Go go go go move go.
Go gotta go.
- Yang?
- You're welcome.
You're working for Trench?
Yeah, he pay me more money.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm the guy that just saved your ass.
(Spanish profanity...)
Batteries at 2%.
Hey Barney, leaving so soon?
Come on, let's finish this.
How you feeling?
Come on, stand up, you'll feel better.
Barney where are you?
Lose the armor, I want you to feel this.
Barney we gotta go.
And don't even think about going
for that piece of garbage in the bag.
Come on.
That's it.
We don't need these, do we?
Come on.
Barney we gotta go.
Batteries at 1%.
Come on Barney.
What about The Hague huh?
I am The Hague.
Batteries gone.
Gotta go, gotta go.
No don't, wait, wait.
I can't wait.
Go!
Come on, Barney! Go!
What the hell!
You owe me Barney.
Barney!
Pull me up.
You're gonna fire us again, Barney?
Come on!
Can't hear you, pal!
I'm gonna kill you!
Alright, I'm sorry!
- Pull me up you idiots.
- Don't pull him up.
To Caeser.
Caeser.
Yo Barney.
Yeah.
I don't think I'll be needing this anymore.
You want your luck back?
I hope I didn't stretch it.
I think you did stretch it.
- Good to have you back man.
- Good to be back.
Don't scare us like that anymore, OK.
Hail Caeser.
You never got him to The Hague.
You know Drummer...
Working with you ain't been so bad.
I haven't had so much fun in years.
Fun's important.
These guys are nuts.
Our power's combined...
Yes, you are.
Come on, there must be a plan.
- Woah, Major Old-School.
- Major Badass
I'll drink to that.
I am sure I have done enough.
That I am worth my weight, in gold you know...
Am I close? And since I am as crazy as you...
I am sure I feel game...
- Galgo?
- Yes sir?
Welcome aboard.
Thank God!
Because I already spent a fortune on this.
You know what I mean.
I am so happy.
Barney, thank you.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
- No hugging.
Ooh...
Best two out of three.
- Hey!
- Just wanted to say thanks.
For what?
- For caring.
- Oh, come on.
- You know, if you were 30 years younger..
- I'd be afraid of you.
Cheers.
Hey Yang, looks like you had a growth spurt.
Tall people don't live long.
So you're working for Trench now.
And you, I thought you retired.
I lied.
Good.
You guys want to get a room?
So jealous.
We came in this thing together,
we gonna leave here together.
Absolutely.
Cheers.
You know for a guy that
doesn't take orders very well.
You did pretty good.
Yeah?
So when do I take over?
Keep drinking.
Hey Smilee!
Get over here.
You did good kid.
You look like a proud, demented father.
You could've skipped the demented part.
It was a compliment.
Subtitles corrected by coolsuren & Tronar