The oldest stories ever told,
are written in the stars.
Stories of time before men and gods,
when Titans ruled the Earth.
The Titans were powerful, but their
reign was ended by their own sons,
Zeus, Poseidon and Hades.
Zeus convinced his brother
Hades to create a beast so strong
that could defeat their parents.
And from his own flesh,
Hades gave birth to an unspeakable horror.
The Kraken.
Zeus became King of the heavens.
Poseidon King of the seas.
And Hades, tricked by Zeus,
was left to rule the underworld
in darkness and in misery.
It was Zeus who created man,
and man's prayers fed the Gods' immortality.
But in time, mankind grew restless.
They begun to question the Gods
and finally rise up against them.
Into this world, a child was born.
A boy who would change everything.
Perseus.
What is it son?
I will have a brother or a sister soon.
You think we're gonna love this child
differently to the way we love you...
But we won't.
This child will be yours.
Me...I'm no one's son.
I'm your father Perseus,
Marmara is your mother,
and you'll always be our son.
The bond between us,
is much more than flesh and bone.
But the love we have for you,
it's that love that Gods and kings are fight over.
I never understood the Gods,
but even I don't question that
you're saved for a reason.
And someday, that reason,
is gonna take you far away from here.
But not tonight.
TWELVE YEARS LATER
Perseus!
You get frail old man.
Marmara!
Another day...Nothing!
Cause of grief!
To whom do we direct
our gratitude for this glorious bounty?
- Spare us, please.
- Poseidon? Zeus?
- Who do I thank Manara?
-Thank the men who provoked them.
They crushed my island,
they put a plague on yours.
They take from us what they want.
We are their slaves.
The Gods gave us life.
For that, we should be thankful.
I'm tired of being thankful for scraps.
I am a fisherman, Perseus is a fisherman,
and they've even taken that away from us.
What we are.
And still they want us to love them anyway.
One day, somebody's gonna have to make a stand.
One day somebody's gonna have to say enough.
Just like the day you came to me.
The storm brought me right to you.
I know you have questions, son.
I wish I had the answers.
I have everything I need.
Right here.
Good night, son.
Hold it steady!
Tekla, take the wreath.
Fetch the wreath.
The Statue of Zeus! Magnificent!
Something isn't right.
The soldiers, what are they doing?
Hang on!
- Who are they?
- Soldiers from Argos.
- What have they done?
- They declared war.
The war against the Gods.
- Let's turn the boat around.
- No! Do nothing.
Where is the boy?!
Zeus, you must bring an end to this!
They attacked our temples!
Now they dared to disgrace Zeus's image.
- We could reach out to them.
- An accommodation could be made, a truce!
No!
I created them, and they reward my love with...
Defiance?!!
There will be no truce!
Finally, some rage from you.
How long has it been?
How long brother?
Since you've seen my face?
Hades.
Endless years, I've watched from the Underworld.
I saw your wrath tempered with love.
You created them for one reason,
so their prayers would fuel our immortality.
But you love them too well.
They grow strong, and now, I am forced to rise
because we are all threatened.
- What do you want brother?
- Let me loose upon them.
They will pray again, and you will
bathed in their awe and fear.
And we will grow strong again.
He belongs in the Underworld, not here.
You do not tell me where I belong.
You said it's love that feeds us,
but you depend on their love.
I've only learned to live on their fear...
- Their pain.
- Zeus, our brother speaks the truth.
Hear him.
Go, do what you will.
- Father, we need the mortals.
- No, Apollo.
Hades is right.
Their insolence has a price.
Like children, they need to be reminded
of the order of things.
Set an example brother.
Turn them on each other.
And back into our arms.
ARGOS
- We are the last boat to come in?
- No captain, you are the only one.
- Is he one of ours?
- No, we found him on the packs amongst our dead.
- He was the only survivor.
- Let the palace figure out what to do with him.
Go on.
They gave us the corn in the fields,
and the sun and the sky. These are all the gifts given to us.
The gifts, they can't be taken away. This will
be taken away, if we do not pay love to our gods.
If you do not wish to stay in our filth
and misery which we are brought upon ourselves.
- Argos, as for we bid for the whip...
- Out of the way!
The beauty and clarity of servitude.
Man cannot rule man, you fight the Gods
and you will be punished.
- Is this all there is?
- We lost many men, Your Majesty.
But we have victory.
To King Kepheus, to Queen Cassiopeia!
No ...
To you.
Our mighty legion, our heroes,
who'd dared to strike a blow
at the heart of Zeus!
The temples are burning,
the statues have fallen.
We have starved them
of our prayers.
Tonight, after a generation of struggle,
the sun does not set
over the ocean.
It sets on Olympus itself!
A new era has begun.
The era of Man!
That frown doesn't suit you Andromeda.
Have something to drink, you'll feel more lively.
Andromeda ...
- What is your name?
- Perseus.
Take this. Please, drink.
- Hands off!
- Enough!
Our daughter, the missionary.
Have you seen
what's happening out there?
Have you even
bothered to look?
We serve as an inspiration.
Hundreds of our men
have lost their lives.
Yet we celebrate.
You are provoking the Gods, and you act
like there won't be no consequence.
And what do you want?
Should we be afraid?
Should we be trembling and
soiling ourselves in fear?
The Gods need us.
They need our worship.
What do we need from them?
- Look at my daughter.
- Don't.
What could be more
divine than her face?
More beautiful than all the women of Greece,
more beautiful than Aphrodite herself.
The Olympians should envy her.
We are the Gods now!
My queen ...
Interesting.
You are specks of dust
underneath our fingernails.
Your very breath is a gift from Olympus.
You have insulted powers
beyond your comprehension.
Who are you?
I am Hades.
Kneel.
Not now Perseus,
you will have your chance.
What do you know of beauty?
What is more beautiful than death?
Gaze upon me mortal queen.
- Mother!
- Sit!
In ten days, when the sun is eclipsed.
I will unleash the Kraken.
Argos will be swept from
the earth, and all of you with it.
Unless, you sacrifice the princess,
you so foolishly compared to the Gods.
Only her blood will sate the Kraken
and Zeus, who you have so offended.
Choose your penance Argos,
destruction or sacrifice.
This is the will of Zeus,
the will of your father.
There's a demigod in Argos.
That's impossible.
He's Yours.
His name is Perseus.
We could offer him sanctuary.
Have I heard his prayers?
The son knows no love for me.
He is no different from any of the others
who have turned their backs on us.
One of us, our demigod.
Speak!
- I am not a demigod.
- Who are you? why were you sent?
I don't know.
My advice against it Sira,
he's not to be trusted.
What did you have me do?!
Draco!
Leave him.
Is it possible?
If it's true, you are the son of Zeus.
You can save us.
- You must save us.
- I can't save you, I'm just a man.
My Lord, as terrible as it is to out of the words
a sacrifice is the only way.
- Don't even say a word!
- He's right.
No one should have
to die for me.
Let Perseus go.
Sira, we need to get
the princess out of the city now.
- We'll find a place to hide her.
- You can't hide her from Hades.
So says the bastard son of a God.
My father...was killed by a God.
My mother, sister ...
Everyone I loved was killed by God.
I mend nets, not whirled the sword.
Demigod, you have a visitor.
She says, she knows you.
My name is Io, Perseus.
How do you know me?
I watched you all your life.
I guided you to your family.
- You are God?
- There are Gods and there are men.
And there are those of us,
who are in between.
Many years ago,
I refused a God's advance.
I was cursed with agelessness.
So much of a curse.
I've lived for years
watching my loved ones die.
I imagine you're sympathetic to that plaint.
Is it true?
Am I the son of Zeus?
Yes.
The story of your birth, begun
with the rebellion of King Acrisius.
Mankind had grown tired of the Gods
mistreatment and cruelty.
Acrisius led the siege on Olympus.
It is said that the other Gods wanted
to simply lay waste to Acrisius and his army.
But Zeus loved man too much.
Instead, he chose
to make an example of Acrisius.
He disguised himself as the king,
and visited the chamber, where
the king's wife was sleeping.
My king.
Zeus?
Acrisius grew mad with rage.
He ordered the execution of his wife
and Zeus's newborn son.
I curse you Zeus!
I deny you the body you soiled
and the bastard child with it!
The queen and her child were cast into the sea.
Your mother was killed, but you,
half man, part God, you lived.
I've watched over you ever since,
awaiting for the day when you'll help
bringing an end to the tyranny of the Gods.
You are born to kill the Kraken.
I don't know why I was born.
Or what I am.
But I know it's not the Kraken I wanna kill.
How do I get to Hades?
If the Kraken falls, Hades will be weak enough
for you to strike a deathly blow.
Only then, you will have the revenge you seek.
Then they better release me.
If the Kraken can be killed,
the Stygian witches would know how.
The witches are further away than
any legion has ever been.
- No man can go there.
- No man.
Keep your distance Io.
Zeus, forgive us for these
affronts and protect us.
And you still believe
they are going to help?
This is suicide.
Here's who you're throwing into this
Perseus, an honor guard.
Young men who look good
on a reviewing stand.
And old soldiers,
heading to retirement.
Do you know what the Kraken is?
The Kraken is the end of us.
A colossal elemental beast.
It doesn't think, it doesn't feel.
Even the Gods fear it,
and you, you're going to kill it?
Don't come.
- I do not need your help.
- Of course not.
You are the son of Zeus.
But we have orders.
Gentlemen, may our journey be long,
filled with agony and torment.
And maybe all complain about
as bitterly as old man.
- So, what should we bring?
- Bring everything.
What makes you think
the witches will tell us anything?
Well, they tell us,
or I'll kill them too.
- What is this?
- Just leave it.
Do not leave us to the mercy
of the Gods, please!
Do not go, please stay!
Stay here, please!
Please! Help us!
Just sacrifice the princess!
Watch your mouth!
Stay back! Stay back!
You think they might be thankful.
Maybe they are tired of being thankful.
Good news! My brother and I have decided
to accompany you on your journey.
- We have enough strangers here.
- We can be of great help to you. Trust me.
- You'll need us.
- I need soldiers, not hunters.
Which one of your soldier knows how to cut
the impenetrable skin of the Nemean lion?
Which one of them knows the soft
point on a central's armor?
Which one of them knows which juggler
to slice on a five-headed Hydra?
- The middle one.
- The middle one. Good guess.
My brother and I, we know how to kill.
- We enjoy it.
- If you can keep up,
you don't mind dying. Come along.
It's death who should be afraid of us.
- King Acrisius.
- There's no Acrisius.
Just Calibos.
We have an enemy in common.
Zeus.
My brother.
What do you want from me?
Zeus's seed in your
wife, survived.
The child of your shame.
- Perseus.
- He lives?
You murdered your wife for nothing.
Now, Perseus vows himself
from Argos to destroy me.
He must die.
- What would you have me do?
- Zeus must think I serve him,
but, I am growing stronger.
Until I possess my full power,
you will be my weapon.
Come.
Use this.
Kill Perseus for me.
- And I'll destroy Zeus for you.
- I serve you, the boy will die.
- How far is it?
- 4 days to the witches.
4 days?
I'm tired already.
Here, use this.
Would you like us to wait?
- You really are a fisherman.
- You should have seen my father.
You, bring your weapon.
- Have you handled a sword before?
- it's been no need.
I see.
Left foot forward.
Your motions, should be fluid.
The weapon is a part of you.
Let the sting on a wasp.
Stay focused.
Know what surrounds you.
Keep your balance of all times.
If you fall ...
You die.
Get up.
Don't ...
There is a God in you.
Be sure to bring it.
End of lesson.
Perseus ...
A gift from the Gods.
- Forged on limbus.
- Why?
Just accept it.
I can do this as a man.
The sword is yours.
Gentlemen, retrieve our Savior.
The Pegasus.
No man has ever ridden them.
It's the message,
they're watching us.
- Perseus!
Perseus!
- ... why we just always have to...
- Listen!
Help me!
You reek of your father!
- Who's that?
- I do not know.
Let's ask him.
Let it go.
No, we split up.
Just follow the blood.
Come on!
Look, his blood!
Are you happy now?
Attack!
Wait, wait!
What is that?
Ixas, lance!
Draco!
Jump!
Run!
Everyone, face to face!
Stand the ground.
- 3 More!
- In the name of the Gods, they're bigger!
What are they?
Djinn.
I fought them,
in the legion.
This is their desert.
- Enemies?
- I thought so.
They aren't humans, not anymore.
- Desert conjurers, cut-throats.
- Somebody should thank them.
What?
- What is it?
- Venom, from Hades.
- Pray, pray to Zeus for strength.
- No!
Pray to your dumb father.
No!
Take the bread.
We must turn our hearts to Hades,
This is the only way!
Brothers and sisters, come to me!
Come!
I have the way out of our misery!
Hades has asked for the princess!
Sacrifice one, for the life of the city!
Why do they remain silent,
while we suffer?
Why do they guard a woman whose
death will save us?
Is she better than anyone of you?
We've long worshiped Zeus on Argos,
but it is Hades
who now offers a salvation!
We must pray to the one,
who showed us our sins!
And who offers us redemption,
through blood!
A bribe for the ferryman.
When they get injured in a battle, they replace
their limbs with charm within black magic.
They feel no pain,
live hundreds of years.
So, how old is that one?
I do not care.
I don't trust them.
You're burnin'.
Drink this.
I'll get more water.
What's he sayin'?
The Djinns have waited many years
for the one who'd free them from the Gods.
- He says, he is no a friend of the humans.
- You don't say it.
But the only way
we can help Perseus, is together.
Draco, look.
Together.
- He's not ready to travel yet.
- Time's slipping away Io.
- He's maybe a demigod, but he's still mortal.
- Feeling better?
- A little bit.
- Good.
Your pride is killing my men!
You were given gifts, use them.
- These gifts are a trap!
- I do not care what they are, use them!
No! I do not wanna use that sword
or anything that they give me!
So, we'll just continue to die.
I can't become like them.
If I'd do this,
I'd do it as a man.
But you're not just a man.
I choose to be.
- A man cannot do this, Perseus.
- According to whom, the Gods?
If I had your gifts ...
When you need your sword,
it's in my bag.
They're ridin' it.
They just tried to kill us,
I am not getting on it.
Magnificent.
What are you waiting for?
Well, we need to make up
the lost time.
- We're making a good time.
- Not good enough.
The eclipse is drawing near.
How close are we to
the Northern mountains?
It will be two days
before we reach the witches.
This thing is making me
feel sick
Trust me, it is better
on the one than in one.
- Why don't you have a smile?
- When I spit in the eyes of the Gods.
Then I smile.
- What is this place?
- The Garden of Stygia.
This is where the Kraken
defeated the Titans.
It would Argos look like
when we fail.
Every step we take,
is an insult to the Gods.
Good.
Perseus, only ask what
you need to know, nothing more.
Of course.
- Visitors!
- Who is it?
Who is it?
- Perseus, no.
- We did not come here to fight.
-  A little one question.
- Perseus, the son of Zeus.
The flesh of a God.
Witch!
Easy.
Stay on me, ladies.
So, which one
is gonna answer my question?
You want to know about the Kraken.
How to kill it.
- That's right.
- A wasted journey.
The Kraken fears no weapons.
It must have a weakness.
Maybe, but the knowledge demands payment!
Sacrifice! Sacrifice!
The eye!
- Let him go!
- No!
- Do it!
- You wouldn't dare!
- We cannot see the answer without the eye.
- Let him go!
Now answer the question!
How do we kill the Kraken?
There is a solution,
but it is an impossible one.
The Gorgon Medusa.
Anything of flesh is killed by her gaze.
Her prison lies across the river Styx
at the edge of the Underworld.
- A Titan against the Titan.
- She's no use against the Kraken.
We can't control her.
- Then we'll take her head.
- Clever boy.
And the eye, give us the eye.
Wait, there's more.
Don't you want to know more?
Perseus, no.
- Tell him. Tell him!
- What?
Your journey does not end well.
Fate has spoken.
You will die, son of Zeus.
- It's a lie...Come.
- what's written is history.
Perseus, you will die.
- Why are the Djinns leaving us?
- They believe we will all die.
It's the prophecy.
Who are you?
Well, you can call me...father.
- If you wish.
- My father is dead.
He's killed by a God.
An unfortunate casualty
on the war men brought on themselves.
Men didn't murder my family,
your brother did.
You heard the witches' prophecy,
you won't defeat the Kraken, ...much less Hades.
If you continue this journey you will die
and Argos will still fall.
- If you're so sure, why are you here?
- To offer you a sanctuary.
Your blood is mine Perseus,
and that makes you a God.
It's time to came to Olympus
and start to living like one.
I'd rather die in the mud with those men,
than live forever as a God.
You foolish boy, men's entire existence
is the gift of my grace.
For someone who created men,
you don't know much about us.
We live, we fight and we die for each other.
Not for you.
Tell Hades I'll see him soon.
- I will not make this offer again.
- Good.
- 'Cause I hate to refuse you twice.
- Perseus ...
Wait.
It's the expensive way you are going.
Kucuk fashioned this shield from the scorpion.
Stronger and lighter than any metal.
Very rare and high quality item.
We can fight anywhere...
But not in the Underworld.
Good luck, fisherman.
You've heard what the witches said.
But we can prove them wrong.
I need your help.
It wasn't the Gods who saved me up there.
If you believe that we have a chance.
I never liked Argos much anyway.
I know the way.
Then we go to the Underworld...
We kill Medusa.
- Now what?
- We wait for Charon.
- Charon only ferries the dead.
- Any volunteers?
Let's we swim.
A bribe for the ferryman.
- So, what happens when we get there?
- Just another beast to kill.
A Beast?
Medusa was beautiful once.
So beautiful, that has tempted Poseidon.
When he came for her,
she ran to Athena's temple,
thinking that the Goddess will protect her.
She didn't.
Poseidon took her on the cold floor.
She prayed to Athena for comfort,
but the Goddess felt nothing but disgust.
She made sure no one
would ever want Medusa again.
One look at the creature she has become
would turn any living thing to stone.
I cannot assist you there,
my curse prevents me.
It was Athena's one bit of solace to Medusa,
so the Medusa would never harm a woman.
Only men are allowed in the temple.
But no man has ever made it out.
Medusa got a tail and she'll use it.
Listen.
Hear her muscles call you.
Smell her skin.
Feel her hunger in your gut.
Medusa has killed you twice now.
Do you think she'll hand you her head?
She won't be gracious about it.
One look in her eyes and
you'll turn to stone.
Good.
- I'm trying not to enjoy this so much...
- I'm trying to help you live.
Don't look at me!
Ease your storm.
We are near Medusa's lair.
I've never thought that
I could reach this place.
Who's you lose?
My daughter.
Taken away on her sixteenth birthday.
Dragged her down here.
I have a feeling I'll see her soon.
You brought us this far,
let's go to the rest of the way.
- How many coins did you get from Zeus?
- Just one.
I knew one great man in my life.
My father.
Now I know four more.
And the woman.
And whatever the hell you are.
I know we are all afraid.
But my father told me, someday
someone's gonna have to make a stand.
Someday,
someone's gonna have to say "Enough"!
This could be that day.
Trust your senses
and don't look this bitch in the eye!
- Doesn't really inspire confidence.
- Quiet.
Listen...Eusebios, keep your eyes down.
Here we go!
Keep going!
Try, go.
- Draco...
- Go!
Eusebios, follow me!
Hang on!
Eusebios...
Remember what Perseus said.
Eyes down!
Ixas, no.
Eyes down.
Where are you?
Eusebios...
Go!
Wait here.
I'll whirl her out.
Get ready!
Now!
Now we must die together!
Let them know, men did this.
Just you and me, son of Zeus.
Perseus ...
Don't become one of them.
Io, I'm here.
There is no time.
The eclipse...
Perseus, you must go before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere.
My fate is certain, but the fate
of Argos is still in your hands.
All my life, you've been there.
You've never left me.
I can't leave you.
This part of the journey you must do alone.
Perseus, you are not just part man, part God....
You're the best of both.
Everything will be all right.
Brother...
It is time for the mortals to pay!
My child waits to do your will.
Leave us.
Release the Kraken!
The Kraken comes now!
Our suffering ends,
when the beast is sated.
Will it take us?
Or will it take Andromeda?!
It's my name they are calling.
This cannot continue.
That's the Kraken!
Andromeda!
Hades, we sacrifice our
princess in your name.
It comes, brothers and sisters!
Argos is fallen.
Do you feel stronger, brother?
You thought the Kraken will
bring you their prayers.
But the Kraken is my child.
- It feeds only me.
- I command Olympus.
- Remember who you serve!
- I serve myself.
I have, since you cheated me.
You sent me to the Underworld to be hated
while you bath in their love.
- We need the love of humans.
- No, you need it.
I survived on their fear.
Your reign is over, brother Zeus.
You watch while my blessed avenger
devours their hopes,
and then, finally...you will know my pain.
There is still a demigod in Argos, brother.
Perseus ...
The bag!
Come on!
No!
I am a God.
I will live forever.
But not here.
The boats are coming for us.
For you, not for me.
You won't stay, will you?
Perseus, Argos needs a ruler.
I cannot be a king.
I serve you better as a man.
I might have fine queen for them.
Olympus owes you attitude of gratitude.
- As do I.
- Hades lives.
He's again back in the Underworld.
Buying his time, no doubt.
Waiting for men to go weakened,
and in their weakness he grows stronger.
It's mankind who holds the key
to Hades' rise, it always was.
So, we'll see him again?
Yes, but now the world knows
a man who can stop him.
Of course, you had some help.
A sword, the Pegasus.
I wanted men to worship us again,
but I didn't want it to cost me a son.
That's almost human of you.
I don't suppose you reconsider my offer,
to take your place as one of us?
I have everything I need right here.
You may not want to be a God, Perseus.
But after feats like yours,
men will worship you.
Be good to them.
Be better than we were.
And if you insist on continuing
this mundane human existence,
I won't have you do it alone.
You're the son of Zeus, after all!
Transcript by: Don4EveR & radojka
www.subscene.com