None of us really know each other.
We're all screw-ups.
But somehow ...
We were all in the same place at the same time
when Billy found those coins.
Guys, check out how we glow.
I'm blue!
I'm black!
-What?
-I am!
No, you're not!
You felt weird?
We're strong.
Insanely strong.
The answer to what is happening to you
is here.
You five ...
Are the Power Rangers.
Did I just hear say we're Power Rangers?
Is this some kinda joke?
We're talking to a wall.
I was kind of expecting a little more.
So where were you last night?
Me and 4 kids found a
spaceship buried underground.
I'm pretty sure I'm a superhero.
Cool!
Pee in that cup!
Power Rangers were a legion of Warriors.
You must become those warriors.
It's just a hologram like a video-game.
That's a strong-ass hologram.
Not a video-game.
You were born for this.
I will destroy everything.
She is pure evil.
How d'you expect us to stop her?
It's morphin' time.
That's a lotta gold.
This is your destiny.
Let's go!
Go!
This is your time.
Made by MovieTrailerSubs.