John Wick.
Excommunicado.
In effect 6:00 p.m.
Eastern Standard Time.
I do hope that Mr. Wick
finds his way to safety.
He knew the rules,
he broke them.
He killed a man on company
grounds, Charon.
Do you expect him
to make it out?
14 million dollar
bounty on his head
and every interested party in
the city wants a piece of it,
I'd say the odds are about even.
They'll kill you just as soon
as they'll make you better.
But I know better, man.
I know better.
I know it, I'm...
Tick tock, Mr. Wick.
Tick tock.
Tick tock... tick tock...
Tick...
No time to dilly-dally,
Mr. Wick!
New York Public Library.
You got it.
Change of plan.
The Continental.
Can you see that he's
received by the concierge?
Yes, sir, Mr. Wick.
Good dog.
John Wick, excommunicado.
In effect, 20 minutes.
Can I help you?
Russian folktale.
Alexander Afanasyev.
Narodnye russkie skazki,
- Level 2.
- Thank you.
"Consider your origins:
"you were not made
to live as brutes,
"but to follow virtue
and knowledge".
Dante.
Looking a little
run down there, John.
Ernest.
- I still have time.
- It's almost up.
Who's gonna know the difference?
You sure this is what
you wanna do?
14 million, it's a lot of money.
Not if you can't spend it.
Shhh.
John Wick, excommunicado.
In effect, 10 minutes.
Let it be known the Bowery
will honor the excommunicado.
No help.
No services of any kind.
Doc!
Doc, it's Wick!
Mr. Wick?
No, no, no,
you shouldn't be here.
Hour's almost up.
Come on, Doc, please.
There's still time.
No, I can't.
I still have five minutes.
Please.
Come on, come on.
All right, sit there.
Let me see, let me see.
Good.
Ah, puncture wound.
Went deep.
Nicked the artery.
All right.
John Wick, excommunicado.
In effect, one minute.
Doc...
Doc.
Yeah, halfway there.
Five seconds.
John Wick, excommunicado.
In effect in five,
four...
Three,
two...
One.
Sorry, Mr. Wick.
There are rules.
John Wick, $14 million.
Open contract is now in effect.
All services are suspended.
And away we go.
Top shelf, on the right.
Yeah.
Take four.
It'll give you energy,
help with the pain.
Mr. Wick.
They'll never believe
I stopped on the hour.
But you did.
They'll know.
Know what?
I told you where
the medicine was.
- Where?
- Right here.
Just below my floating rib.
It should not hit my...
Oh, wait!
One might not be enough.
Be sure not to graze my co...
Good luck, Mr. Wick.
Thanks, Doc.
John Wick, open contract.
Increase, $15 million.
Where are you going, Jonathan?
We are closed.
Jardani.
Why have you come home?
You present this to me
like an answer.
I still have my ticket.
After all the chaos you've
caused for the last few weeks,
you think your ticket is valid?
You forget that the Ruska Roma
is bound by the High Table?
And the High Table
stands above all.
They could kill me
just for talking to you.
You honor me
by bringing death
to my front door?
Oh, Jardani.
What has become of you?
My name is
Jardani Jovonovich.
I was born in Belarus.
You are bound.
And I am owed.
Runi, enough!
You are "owed."
You are owed nothing, Jardani.
You know, when my pupils
first come here,
they wish for one thing.
A life free of suffering.
I try to dissuade them
from these childish notions,
but as you know,
art is pain.
Life is suffering.
Somehow you managed
to get out.
But here you are,
back where you began.
All of this for what?
It wasn't just a puppy.
Sit.
Even if I wanted to...
I can't help you, Jardani.
The High Table wants your life.
How can you fight the wind?
How can you
smash the mountains?
How can you bury the ocean?
How can you
escape from the light?
Of course,
you can go to the dark.
But they're in the dark, too.
So tell me, Jardani,
what do you really want?
Passage.
Where did you want to go?
Casablanca.
The path to paradise
begins in hell.
So be it.
You hand me your ticket,
I will tear it...
if that's what you really desire.
With this, Jardani,
your ticket is torn.
You can never come home again.
Take him to the lifeboat.
Do svidaniya
Welcome to The Continental.
How may I help you?
Sir,
there is an adjudicator
here to see you.
Very well, sir.
The manager is in the lounge.
I presume you're here
to discuss John Wick.
If that's so,
we can make this short.
I told him to walk away,
he declined to do so.
And that's the all of it.
Mr. Wick broke the rules.
Oh, yes.
And I haven't got
the slightest idea...
You're mistaken.
I'm not here for Mr. Wick.
I'm here because Mr. Wick
broke the rules in this hotel.
The blood was spilt on the
grounds of The Continental,
was it not?
Oh, yes.
As a matter of fact,
the body gets colder
within these very walls.
I'd like to see it.
Santino D'Antonio.
A newly instated member
of the High Table
slain by Mr. Wick
while seeking sanctuary
in The Continental.
With a .45 ACP, it appears.
I have no control over
Mr. Wick's actions.
And yet he lives because
you deemed it so, yes?
Yes.
You've known Mr. Wick
for a great many years.
It might even be fair
to call you friends, yes?
Instead of stopping him,
instead of killing him,
you stood by
and let him walk away
after he shot Santino D'Antonio
in front on you.
I made him excommunicado.
But not before you gave him
an hour to escape.
He broke the rules in my hotel.
This is exactly the problem.
Your hotel.
Where is your fealty?
I've been in service
for over 40 years.
Under the Table.
Serving the Table.
Everything is under the Table.
I understand that
you have your loyalties,
but this cannot be overlooked.
Let me be clear:
I am here to adjudge you.
You have one week
to get your affairs in order.
Excuse me?
At such time, your
successor will be named.
There are rules.
They are the only things
that separate us...
From the animals.
Yes.
You have seven days.
In the meantime,
if you need any assistance
with your transition,
you may look for me
in room 217.
Enjoy your stay
at The Continental.
There's an adjudicator
here to see you.
Welcome!
My mission control.
Brainstem of my operation.
The information super fly-way
from whence I control
the word on the street.
The way of the world.
With pigeons?
Yes, you see rats with wings,
but I see the internet.
No IP addresses.
No digital footprint.
Can't track it, can't hack it,
can't trace it.
Can you get disease from it?
Well, I wouldn't recommend
that you eat one.
What the hell do you want?
I wanted to see where
it didn't happen.
Where what didn't happen?
Where you didn't kill John Wick.
Always been under the
impression that contracts
and executing them
were optional.
I have no problem
with John Wick.
And yet you gave John a
seven round Kimber 1911
knowing that he
intended to use it
to stand against the Table, yes?
This Kimber 1911, to be exact.
You gave John Wick
seven bullets,
the High Table is
giving you seven days.
Seven days for what, exactly?
To settle your affairs,
and find a new home
for your birds.
In seven days,
you abdicate your throne.
Oh, my dear.
Tell me, do you know what
the Bowery is, adjudicator?
Do you know what happens
when I wave my hand?
No, there will be no replacement
for me on the throne.
Because I am the throne, baby.
I am the Bowery!
I am all that you
dare not to look at
when you walk down
the street at night.
The Bowery is mine.
Mine alone.
Do not make a
mistake of thinking
you exist outside the rules.
No men do.
You have seven days.
Enough!
I'm afraid our friend
here is off limits.
But he is excommunicado.
It seems the manager
has granted him amnesty.
Mr. Jonathan,
would you be so kind
as to come with me?
Welcome to Casablanca,
Mr. Wick.
Thanks.
Mr. Jonathan,
it has been a long time
since our fine city has been
graced with your presence.
I need to talk to...
Yes, Miss Al-Ashwal,
she's expecting you.
My, my.
Welcome to the
Moroccan Continental.
I hope you find it
to your taste.
Right this way.
Miss Al-Ashwal,
she waits for no man.
Best of luck, Mr. Jonathan.
Best of luck.
You a dog person, John?
Sofia.
Sofia!
You can't kill the
bearer of your marker.
I didn't kill you.
I just shot you.
Nice suit.
Good to see you, too.
I should shoot you
in the head right now.
I know.
Don't you do it.
You're excommunicado, John.
And that marker...
doesn't mean shit.
This is your blood.
Your bond.
When you needed help,
I was there.
Sit.
I was talkin' to you, John.
You do realize that I'm
management now, right?
I'm not service anymore, John,
so I don't go around
shooting people in the head.
I'm not asking you
to kill anyone.
I just need you
to get me to him.
To who?
Your old boss.
You wanna kill Berrada?
I'm not gonna kill him.
I just need to talk.
What could he
possibly give to you?
Guidance.
Oh, come on.
I made a deal when I
agreed to run this hotel.
And that deal said that I had to
follow the rules of the Table.
If you're not gonna kill him,
he is gonna kill you.
And then probably me, too
for walking you up in there.
If I make one mistake,
one enemy,
maybe somebody goes
looking for my daughter.
And I know what you did,
John, to get her out.
But that's not a chance
I can take.
Sorry.
Do you want to know
where she is?
No.
I don't ever want to know.
Because I don't trust
that I won't go find her.
A part of me longs for her.
And I have to kill that
part of myself every day
just to keep her safe.
Because sometimes,
you have to kill
what you love.
That's why I gave you that
marker in the first place.
And that's why I'm
sitting here right now.
And that's why I'm fucked!
- Consequences.
- Yeah.
Consequences.
I'm just asking you to try.
Either way, you and me,
we'll be even.
No.
After this,
we are less than even.
We leave in 10 minutes.
Irasshaimase!
How can I help you?
I wasn't expecting the
High Table so soon.
There is a task.
It involves someone
who broke the rules
and stood against the Table.
John Wick, you mean?
My students have not been idle.
John Wick and
all who helped him.
You've heard the stories
about him, of course.
Killed scores of men this
past week alone because of...
A dog.
A car.
I'm familiar.
And I'm interested.
Very.
Blowfish.
Very fatal.
I have served.
I will be of service.
Stop!
Out!
The High Table and the Ruska
Roma have an understanding.
Yes, and you helped John Wick.
He had a ticket.
But a ticket does not
stand above the Table.
Your penance will
be paid in blood.
Now...
hold out your helping hands
and pledge your fealty.
I have served.
I will be of service.
We're not going in
like the old days.
It's just a conversation.
Nothing's ever just a
conversation with you, John.
Let's go.
Sofia!
Always so nice to see you.
And the dogs, of course,
how marvelous.
May I pet one?
Certainly.
Dazir, Havan.
Fantastic.
Jonathan Wick.
I had heard you had made
your way to our shores.
Come along now.
I'm certain we have
much to discuss.
I must admit, I am curious.
What brings you to my domain?
Tell me,
you come here to kill me?
No.
Mr. Wick,
do you know where the word
"assassin" comes from?
People argue.
"Assassin."
Hashashin.
Followers of Hassan-i.
Eaters of hashish.
No, thank you.
But others contend that
it comes from "Asasiyun",
meaning men who have faith
and who abide by their beliefs.
You see that coin?
The first coin ever
minted in this facility.
Next to it,
the first mark.
Not easy to track down,
believe me.
Now this coin, of course,
it does not represent
monetary value.
It represents the commerce
of relationships.
A social contract in which
you agree to partake.
Order and rules.
You have broken the rules.
The High Table has
marked you for death.
Why would I allow you
to leave here alive
when your life has been,
by your own actions, forfeit?
I seek to make amends.
To pay for what I've done.
I seek a meeting with the
One who sits above the Table.
This dog...
I do so love it.
Tell me,
does it shed a great deal?
Occasionally.
When I leave, you can tell
the Elder I'm coming.
And if he wants me dead...
Then he will see to it that your
bounds bleach under the sun.
I see.
And I would have provided
him with a choice.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wick.
I cannot tell you where
to find the Elder.
You fail to understand.
The Elder is not a man you find.
He can only choose
to find you.
You wish to speak with him?
Go to the edge of the desert,
look up.
Canis Minor.
The dog the followed the
lion through the sky.
You follow the brightest star.
Walk until you are almost dead.
Then, keep walking.
When you are
on your last breath,
he will find you.
Or he will not.
I am grateful.
Thank you, sir.
Perhaps you were not
listening before.
The social contract.
The commerce of relationships.
You have received a great gift.
I have hosted your friend.
What do you offer in return?
So soft, and yet so fierce.
I love it, this dog.
I will keep it.
Excuse me?
This will be my gift.
This will be how you
show me your fealty.
No.
Surely, it's the least you can do.
No. You cannot keep my dog.
Very well.
Then I will kill it.
I'm sorry, Sofia.
This was for you to learn.
Don't.
Sofia, don't.
He shot my dog.
I get it.
We gotta go. Now.
Up!
Here you go.
You're gonna die, John.
Whether out here
on this desert.
Or somewhere else
down the road.
But you are gonna die.
Consequences.
Better get going.
Sofia.
Okay.
You've made your point.
You have earned my fealty.
Matter of fact,
I'm gonna shove so much
fealty up your ass,
it's gonna come spitting
our of your mouth.
You had your chance.
Well, since you see it that way,
I guess it's time I told you
to climb down off
of your High Table
and go fuck yourself!
Duly noted.
You gave John Wick
seven bullets.
Your penance will be paid with
seven cuts.
Well, sometimes you gotta
cut a motherfucker.
Avert your eyes, my sweet.
The king...
is dead.
Long live the king.
Drink.
Don't worry,
your weapon is still there.
Please drink.
My son,
how have you come to be so lost?
I'm not lost.
Looking for you.
You think I speak
of your location?
Never seen a man fight so hard
to end up back where he started.
So tell me, Jonathan.
Why do you wish to live?
My wife.
Helen.
To remember her.
To remember us.
So you seek to live
for the memory of love?
At least a chance to earn it.
I can give you one last
chance to earn a life.
However, it might not be
the life that you wish.
Complete a task for us,
and your excommunicado
will be reversed.
The open contract closed.
You will be permitted
to continue to live.
Not freed under the Table,
but bound to it
doing what you do best
for the rest of your days.
The choice is yours.
Die here and now,
or continue to live and
remember through death.
What must be done?
The cost of your life will
be the death of others.
The first of which will be
the man they call Winston.
What?
He has forgotten his fealty.
Neither the open contract
nor the excommunicado
will be lifted
until you complete your task.
So, if you wish to live,
and if you wish to remember,
this is the choice you must make.
I will serve.
I will be of service.
Very well, my son.
Cast aside your weakness
and reaffirm your
fealty to the Table.
Mr. John Wick.
Thank you.
I accept this offering
and your fealty.
I wish you good luck
on your path.
Zair will help you prepare
for your departure.
And Mr. Wick...
Welcome back.
Stick together, kids!
Make sure you're
holding hands...
You see?
That's why you're special,
John Wick.
I wouldn't have stopped.
It's good they have your back.
How was your trip?
Going to The Continental?
He with you?
He was.
Nice trick.
Sir!
Put your weapon down.
He's excommunicado.
Unless you wish to
become the same,
I suggest you lower your gun.
I'd like to see the manager.
Of course.
If you would be so kind
as to follow me.
Please take a seat.
I will let him know
you have arrived.
I gotta tell you.
I've been looking forward to
meeting you for a long time.
I'm a huge fan.
John Wick!
And so far, you haven't disappointed.
Is that the dog?
He likes you.
Oh, but me...
I'm more of a cat
person, myself.
Hey, dog.
We're the same, you know.
Both given the same gift.
We're not the same.
Yes, we are.
No, we're not.
The manager is ready for you now
in the administrative
lounge, sir.
Mr. Wick.
Sit.
Stay.
Good dog.
Tread carefully, Jonathan.
We only use this room on
special occasions.
When you simply
have to see what your
opponent is holding
under the table.
How was your journey here,
eventful?
Yeah.
Of course.
They sent men to kill you,
and now you to kill me.
Isn't that why you're here?
I have served.
I will be of service.
But you're having doubts.
Just don't make the mistake of
pretending this is personal.
If you feel you must,
put a bullet through my heart.
The High Table has
asked me to step down.
The hour?
The hour.
You should've killed me
in The Continental.
Maybe I should have.
Rules and consequences.
Mmm.
Seems like everyone is suffering
from the consequences
of their actions.
And you're not stepping down.
No.
I don't think I am.
So it's war?
You're going to war
with the High Table.
Skirmish.
Unless you decide to shoot me,
but then, I'd rather die
at the hand of a friend
than that of an enemy.
Oh, I've made my choice.
It's up to you to make yours.
What choice?
You shoot me,
you sell your soul.
But I'll be alive.
And I can remember her.
Until you die as a servant
of the High Table.
Now, you did the impossible.
You stopped, you got out.
You only came back because
Helen was taken away from you.
The real question is,
who do you wish to die as?
The Baba Yaga?
The last thing
many men ever see.
Or as a man,
who loved and was loved
by his wife.
Who do you wish
to die as, Jonathan?
Mr. Wick.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am an adjudicator.
Have you decided to step down?
I think not.
And you,
will you be putting
a bullet in his head?
No.
I don't think I will.
Very well.
Administration.
I'd like to change a designation.
Verification?
Adjudication 1011979.
The Continental Hotel, New York.
New designation?
Deconsecrated.
Processing.
Administrator.
File:
The New York Continental Hotel.
New York Continental Hotel
has been deconsecrated.
Goodbye.
Gentlemen, this institution
is now deconsecrated.
Business may now be conducted
on Continental grounds.
Since you are
refusing to step down,
and you are refusing
a direct order,
your lives are now forfeit.
High Table emissaries will
be joining you presently
to see the removal of your
souls from the property.
Good evening, gentlemen.
This haven is safe no more.
Are services still
off limits to me?
Under the circumstances,
your privileges are
reinstated immediately.
What do you need?
Guns.
Lots of guns.
Let's make a withdrawal.
Remember, sir.
These will be High Table forces.
We may have to consider
our choices carefully.
Why?
Much has changed
during your time away.
Like what?
Well, let us say they have made
armor improvements.
May I suggest
the 2011 Combat Master
in combination with
the 9 mm NATO?
Attention all guests.
The Continental lost power and
has frozen all communications.
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
It seems circumstances
have changed in your favor.
Your transaction may now be
conducted on Continental grounds.
We'll be sending some of our
finest for additional support.
Cool.
Very cool.
125 grain,
1425 feet per second.
Serious business.
Thank you.
Let us begin.
Charon, will you help set
the mood for our new guests?
Of course, sir.
I know you'll do
The Continental proud.
I'll see you soon, sir.
And you, Jonathan,
do what you do best.
What's that?
Hunt.
If you want peace,
prepare for war.
Winston!
I need more firepower.
Armor improvements.
12 gauge steel slugs.
Armor piercing.
Only by my sword, John.
I know you believe
you can keep this up
but I assure you...
Nice to meet you, Mr. Wick.
It's an honor to fight with you,
Mr. Wick.
He's getting slow.
He's been retired for five years.
But he is still... John Wick.
We will see.
See you later.
John.
You're incredible.
Exhausted.
Outnumbered.
Obviously in pain.
You still beat all of my students.
If I didn't have to kill you,
we'd be... pals.
Let's do this.
See?
We're the same.
I would like to suggest a parley.
A parley would be good.
Very well.
Are we in play, sir?
Oh, very much so.
Hey, John.
That was a pretty good fight, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah...
Don't worry about...
me, John...
Just gotta catch my breath.
I'll catch up to you, John.
No, you won't.
You gentlemen, of course,
realize that was the first wave.
Merely an amuse-bouche.
We can keep this up
as long as you'd like,
but it only ends one way.
Are you sure a protracted
war is the best way forward?
There won't be anything
protracted about it.
Oh, you can take The Continental,
I have no doubt about that,
but keeping it,
that's a different matter entirely.
My allegiances run way
beyond this building.
We are High Table.
And we...
are New York City.
Are we negotiating?
I believe we are.
Parley?
Parley.
What do you propose we do?
Let me keep my power.
Under the Table?
I have served
and been a beacon of order
and stability to our industry
for over 40 years.
Now, I humbly acknowledge
I overstepped.
And repledge my fealty
to the High Table.
Winston.
You were merely showing strength
so we would let you
keep The Continental.
The High Table
accepts your fealty.
But what about him?
What are we going to do
about John Wick?
Oh, he has to die.
Sorry, Jonathan.
- Winston!
- Don't see any other way.
Very well, gentlemen.
The Continental will now
be reconsecrated.
Good day to you both.
Well played, sir.
How long do you estimate
a trim rebuilding?
Oh, it should be no time at all.
Mr. Wick is gone.
A true tragedy.
You misunderstand.
I mean that he is
no longer on the street.
Seems improbable.
And yet true.
I trust you understand the
repercussions if he survives
both from above and below.
The last thing
either one of us needs
is Mr. Wick paying us
a visit in the night.
For both our sakes,
I hope you see to it that this
situation is taken care of, yes?
Absolutely.
How far can he get?
Baba Yaga.
How you doin', John?
Well, you look as bad as I feel.
Johnny, Johnny, Johnny.
Raise a hand
if you can hear me, John.
Oh, shit. They took a finger.
Ain't that a bitch.
Oh, John fuckin' Wick.
So, the old boy keeps his
hotel and you take the fall.
Can't say I blame him.
I would've done the same thing
if I was in his shoes.
But this High Table shit...
Seven cuts.
Under the Table is
where shit gets done.
And they about to find out
if you cut a king,
you better cut him
to the quick.
So...
Lemme ask you, John.
How do you feel?
'Cause I am really
pissed off.
You pissed, John?
Hmm?
Are you?
Yeah.
subs by enwansix