[bagpipes playing]
[electricity crackles]
[music playing]
[horse grunts]
[Lord Boresh] Violence...
tyranny...
intrigues...
power...
After the death of Bohemian king
and holy
Roman Emperor Charles IV,
everything has changed
for the worse.
The darkness started to spread
with much of Europe
sank into chaos.
[crowd clamoring]
[groans]
[eagle screeches]
[Lord Boresh] The continent
was engulfed in war,
plague, and famine.
The Catholic Church
also fell into such disarray
that two Popes were elected.
One in Rome, and another one
under the protection
of the King of France
in Avignon.
Only the coronation
of a new emperor
can restore the rule of law.
But the Charles IV's
firstborn son,
Bohemian King Wenceslas,
who was chosen for that
is drowning in debt.
He can only be crowned in Rome
by the Pope.
And all those who supported
the second Pope in France
are now trying to stop
his coronation at all costs.
[intense music playing]
[exhales]
Forgive us...
for what we are about to do.
[rattles]
[indistinct chatter]
[horses neighing]
Eight.
Seven.
[exhales]
Six left.
And against 2,000 or more now.
[swords clashing]
We won't hold up
much longer, Jan.
[soldiers clamoring]
Five, now.
[intense music playing]
[knights clamoring]
[knights screaming]
[horses neighing]
[grunts]
[men grunting]
[wagon rattling]
[knights groan]
[screams]
[horses neighing]
[yells]
[assassins clamoring]
[grunts]
[groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
[yells]
[grunts]
[assassin groans]
[yells]
[grunts, screams]
[grunts]
[pants]
[screams]
[grunts]
[yells]
[screams]
[chuckles, grunts]
[music playing]
[pants]
[Lord Boresh] You wait till
you see my last knight dead,
and then you show up?
You're alive.
Are you insane?
[horse grunts]
Maybe next time you pay on time.
And we want groschen.
Not Florence.
When have you not
been paid by me?
been protected by us?
Jan.
Prague is ten days away.
You know the importance
of what I'm doing.
If I don't get there on time,
everything is gonna get worse.
[grunts]
I need to know
who sent the assassins for me.
[Jan] Who sent you?
Just kill me.
Or...
you can join us.
[breathes heavily]
Why?
[Cyril] You are the last
like most of us,
and the luckiest.
[breathes heavily]
The lord that hired us
wore a checked coat of arms.
It was Henry of Rosenberg.
[groans]
I'm supposed to trust a man
who has just tried to kill me?
Yes.
[soldiers laugh]
[music playing]
[emotional music playing]
[Jan] Death brings life.
[eagle screeching]
[King Sigismund] Lord Rosenberg.
If you do not loan those funds
to my brother to go to Rome,
you may find men waiting
on the doorstep of your castle.
[Rosenberg] King Sigismund.
Just because your half-brother
here gave you a bit of power,
we will not allow you to behave
like you do in your own kingdom.
This is not Hungary.
You allow me nothing!
I am here solely to help
my brother get to Rome,
to be crowned
by the only true Pope.
Winter is coming.
In a matter of weeks,
his journey will be impossible.
There must be a way
to address your concerns.
I only have one concern.
If you were killed
on this journey,
we will not only lose the money
you ask now,
but also the substantial sums
you already owe.
This will not happen.
God brought our father through
Italy safely for the same crown.
And God brought
your great-grandfather
back from Italy
as a box of bones.
[door slams] Great-grandfather
did not have this.
I hold safe passage
for our king to his coronation
as emperor in Rome.
This will address your concerns,
Rosenberg.
You look as though
you've seen a ghost.
[indistinct chatter]
Girl.
Could we trouble you
for something to drink?
Water?
Or would a fierce warrior
such as yourselves prefer
something more robust?
Ah.
Do your worst, girl.
She can smell a real man.
Hmm.
I can smell one, too.
Back up.
Thank you.
[men shouting in distance]
[Giovanni] Sounds like
somebody's not too happy
about sending the king to Rome.
The lord here has to pay for it.
[both chuckles]
You must be very rich.
I can't spend it all.
Perhaps you'd like to help.
Maybe she loaned some
to the king.
Yes.
Well, no matter what the king
manages to get,
nobody poor or even outside
that room will benefit.
[gate opens]
[Lord Boresh] Rosenberg, wait!
You cannot just leave.
You promised your support
if I brought the safe passage.
[gate closes]
I promised that
before Sigismund arrived.
Before he started to plunder
and brought our kingdom
close to a civil war.
Forget about my money.
Thank you.
[Lord Boresh] Lady Katherine.
Lord Boresh.
My father's missed you
since your last visit.
If things keep going
as they are...
I may come more often.
[indistinct chatter]
[swords rattling]
Zizka.
[Jan] Torak.
It surprises me to see you
back home.
Just passing through.
You're still working
for Sigismund?
We're recruiting.
[soldiers shouting]
To support
his brother's trip to Rome.
You're still as generous
with the pay?
Even more so, my friend. Never
been a better time for you to come back.
They're all very soft
and gentle.
They're almost volunteering.
We'll think about it.
[Torak]
Well, unless you work for me,
you think about it
in another kingdom.
Keep in mind,
we're doing God's work here.
God's work!
[music playing]
[man groans]
Stop that immediately!
Henry, do something!
Stop hurting him!
Anybody else who doesn't
wanna join your king's army?
Every citizen
has to be properly judged
according to the law decree
given by Emperor Charles IV.
He's dead.
Sigismund is new judge
and jury here.
Do something.
We can't let them do this.
[groans]
[Rosenberg] That's Sigismund's
soldiers' recruiter.
I'll deal with it.
But we might need the help
of your father.
Whatever it takes.
We have come to the conclusion
that kidnapping is the only way
to help Rosenberg keep his word.
Well, I'll give you a discount
for taking him.
Not him.
His fiancée. Katherine.
We... We don't kidnap women.
Good rule.
But this is the king.
And his rules.
It makes no difference.
If you still believe
that things could be changed
for the better...
I need your help.
There is something
you should know.
But keep it to yourself.
Her uncle is the king of France.
[music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[men laughing]
More wine for everybody!
[men cheer]
And a toast to Javier.
[Conrad] Gonna miss you,
brother.
He died a good death.
[thumps]
Unto God.
[men laugh]
[eagle screeches]
[whooping]
That's enough, son.
Just one more, okay?
Come on, Dad. I know.
Grab the bucket.
No!
There's someone up there.
A knight.
Well, ask if he can help
carry buckets.
I... I'm not lying.
He's coming down.
Stay back, Jan.
[emotional music playing]
Brother.
[chuckles]
[men laugh]
[Zizkov] So, is it true you killed
a boar with your bare hands?
[Jan] Don't believe everything
people say about me.
I had a knife.
And the boar was small.
So was I.
[chuckles]
There's not much game left.
But there is...
Are they still fighting
with your army in Italy?
How many men
have you killed there?
[door banging]
[Barbara] Hey.
Hello.
Hi.
[door closes]
[Jaroslav] Barbara, Matthew.
This is my brother, Jan.
It's a pleasure, sir.
Your father spoke
a great deal about you.
I'll come back later.
[Jaroslav] Goodnight.
[Matthew] Goodnight.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jaroslav.
Your wife?
Uh, no.
My mother died of the plague.
They're rebels.
Shush now, boy. Time for bed.
Grandfather didn't like anyone
to touch that.
I know.
[Jaroslav]
"This was given to me."
[both chuckles]
"By Emperor Charles IV's
Imperial Chamberlain."
"Imperial Chamberlain."
[Jaroslav chuckles]
[Jan] This boar tusk
will make you fast and strong.
[music playing]
So, are you here
to kill someone?
[Jaroslav] Bed now.
[music playing]
Are you?
Of course not.
[exhales]
No, come on.
You need a new roof
among other things.
I could repair all of Trocnov
with this.
Father was proud of you,
you know?
You should've been there.
You get 1,000 for each of us
who makes it through this.
3,000 total to be split.
Kidnapping a woman
may bring bad luck.
For 1,000 groschen,
I'll gladly give up, my friend.
[men laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
Will you join me at the service?
And have people think
I'm a supporter of Jan Hus?
[chuckles]
If you came to the service,
you'd would realize
that it's not just
what Jan Hus preaches.
Those people hate Sigismund
just as much as you do.
You do realize that many of them
also hate me.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
But to support Hus,
who speaks out
against the very doctrine
of the Catholic Church...
Jan Hus is about Jesus' doctrine
over that of the Pope.
It might be what the church
needs to come together.
And Hus may be right.
Until I know
with absolute certainty,
I will be outside.
[horse neighing]
Bless you, bless you, bless you.
Bless you, my lady.
I'll pray for you.
Not out loud, please.
While you're in there,
pray to God for forgiveness
for failing to kill Boresh.
[Hus] These kings and the lords
fight each other for power...
Welcome, Lady Katherine.
[Hus] ...Instead of not going
to war to survive.
Look around.
King Sigismund is recruiting
our innocent brothers
to build an army
for Wenceslas's coronation
in Rome.
But at the same time,
he's plundering our kingdom
in the name of God.
Is this how he imagines the path
to unifying the holy church,
which two Popes have now
brought to the edge of ruin?
It was the ambitions
of those power-hungry rulers
that tore it asunder.
They only have room
for themselves in their hearts.
These kings and lords
behave like they're...
[man] My lady, if you please.
The brothers would like a word
about your generous donation.
[Hus]
Everybody is equal in His eyes.
Be strong.
And spread the word
to your neighbors.
Let us sing.
♪ Ye who are God's warriors ♪
♪ And of his law ♪
♪ Pray to God for help ♪
♪ And have faith in Him ♪
[gate closes]
[Jan] Lord, forgive us
for what we're about to do.
[Katherine muffled screams]
Shh!
[grunts]
Lady Katherine?
[Hus speaking indistinctly
in distance]
Lady Katherine!
[Katherine screams]
Lady Katherine. Is everything
all right in there?
My lady?
[banging on gate]
[screams]
Open that.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Stop it. Stop it.
What are you doing?
You have the key.
Well, go and get it.
You go with him.
Yes, sir.
Get inside.
Go.
[gate unlocks]
Silently.
Move it!
Get the door!
Dammit!
Go! Go!
Search those houses! Go!
[raven cawing]
[Katherine grunts]
[Lars chuckles]
Did you enjoy the ride?
[Katherine shrieks]
Not really horrible.
Smelled almost like your feet.
[Lars] My feet?
[men chuckle]
[Katherine] Do you have any idea
what you have done?
[pants] And in a church.
Don't you understand
that is the house of God?
If it means anything,
I refused to go inside it.
Take the groschen, don't ya?
[men laugh]
[Katherine grunts]
[music playing]
[man] Admiring
your fiancé's handiwork.
He wouldn't do this.
[woman] I'm gonna miss this
once you're married.
Oh, no, you won't.
'Cause the things you do for me,
my little princess
wouldn't even dream of.
[Captain Martin] Rosenberg!
Open the gates!
[gate opens]
Oh, my God.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman shrieks]
[guard 1] Nothing here!
[hounds barking]
Lord Boresh.
He'll take her
to your hunting castle
in the next few days.
[King Wenceslas] Good.
So, we don't have to worry
about the money anymore.
Perhaps we should use
more of her political value.
[Cyril singing in French]
[gasps softly]
[Jan] I don't want anyone
to recognize who you are.
My fiancé will take it off
your corpse.
[Cyril continues singing]
I need you alive.
Well, I'm not cold.
Hmm.
I wouldn't be surprised...
[intense music playing]
[King Sigismund humming]
[Rosenberg] I assumed
your brother was behind this.
But your involvement
makes much more sense.
I'd watch your tongue
if I were you.
I'm here to help.
To help me?
So, you're saying
it was your brother?
[chuckles]
Once I return
your lovely fiancée...
I want the full support
of your noble union
of any and all activities here.
You'd go so far
as to take the Bohemian crown
off your brother's head?
Half-brother.
And don't look so shocked.
You and your noble union
already made plans to take it.
That's why you tried
to kill Boresh.
But what about the business
I'd lose with her father
for making
an arrangement with you?
You know how much he hates you.
If I was king here, I would
let you take so much more.
And as you know,
her family hates most to see
my brother as an emperor.
On top of everything,
if you haven't found her by now,
you won't.
What makes you so confident
that you can?
I don't need to find her.
God will deliver her to me.
Hmm.
So far. [chuckles]
You're stronger than I am.
[chuckles]
[pants]
Where is Jan?
In the house maybe?
[whooping]
You see your target?
Mm-hmm.
[Torak] Yeah.
You got it?
Uh-huh.
Just like you're letting go
of your arm.
Yes. Uh-huh.
[Torak] Stand steady.
You got it?
Uh-huh.
Faster.
Do it fast.
Put your arms out in the middle.
You see your target?
Yes.
[thumps]
[thuds]
[grunts, groans]
You see?
[breathing heavily]
Father!
Run! Go! Run!
I don't know if I would
let him play with this.
You see how dangerous it is?
[whimpers, sobs]
[Zizkov] Leave him!
Leave him be!
Run!
Leave him!
He's a real Zizka, huh?
[sword slashes]
[Ulrich] Jan? Come over here.
Look, it's Trocnov.
We're moving!
[bell tolling]
Search the houses!
[pants]
[Zizkov whimpers, sniffles]
I know.
You fought bravely.
[Zizkov groans]
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
[Barbara sobs]
Rosenberg?
No. Sigismund's man.
Torak.
He left me alive
to give you a message.
"Your brother will hang
if she's not returned to him."
[sobs]
[music playing]
[Jan] Death brings life.
It doesn't make sense.
Why would Sigismund
want to steal her from our king?
[Conrad] Maybe he wants
the ransom only for himself.
We can't trade her.
Of course, not.
We're not doing this.
No girl, no money.
We don't leave our men behind.
He wasn't one of us.
He did help with the caves.
Torak warned us not to work
in this area.
So, even if we trade,
you know he'll never let us go.
And your brother will die
anyway, but right along with us.
Mm-mm!
[grunts]
We need your help.
Speak with the rebels.
[indistinct chatter]
You'll be paid well.
You don't have to pay us.
Jaroslav is a good man.
One of us.
This is business.
Not a rebellion.
Not for us.
We're here to fight for justice.
To keep her fiancé
from taking our land.
If we die without a son,
Rosenberg's law
deeds our property to him.
I'm here for my daughter.
I'm just here to kill
every Rosenberg soldier
in South Bohemia.
And then him.
I need your help
sending a message.
Where are your weapons?
Here.
We just killed
two of Rosenberg's men.
[chuckles]
You're welcome here.
[indistinct chatter]
[villager spits]
I can trust you to protect her.
[indistinct chatter]
[King Sigismund] My Lord.
You know my brother is too weak
to unite the holy church
under Rome.
This task is mine.
With your blessing,
I will use Katherine
to keep the French king
from getting in my way,
so we can achieve our goal.
[gate opens]
[Torak] King Sigismund.
[gate closes]
God has answered your prayers
once again.
Has he?
Tomorrow, she will be yours.
What about Zizka?
We will be prepared.
'Cause I trained him.
But I'm better.
[indistinct chatter]
[men screaming]
[men grunting]
Whip back.
Yeah.
Again. And one!
[men grunting]
Hands drawn.
Like this.
[grunts]
I need a blacksmith
and big nails.
He first saw you
in the church of Jan Hus.
What would you be doing there?
He's the only one
who's not afraid of the church.
And how it twists
what's really in the Bible.
Maybe there is a thing or two
we can agree on.
[blows]
One of your fiancé's men
didn't like my cooking.
Something more
must have happened.
[baby wailing in distance]
A lot more.
It is nothing compared
to what some have suffered.
Nobody wants to be here.
But we can only take so much.
Jan!
[Katherine pants]
[men shouting]
[Katherine shrieks, grunts]
Why are you running?
I cannot betrothed to Sigismund.
You don't know who he is.
He's good enough
for your fiancé.
Sigismund does this on his own.
By rescuing me,
he'll force my fiancé
to do his bidding for him.
I can't live with that!
God's will.
All because you believe
that kings were placed
on the throne by God.
Please tell me
more about God's will.
Tie her up.
Your nephew was murdered
because of you.
Is that God's will?
[breathes heavily]
If you had not done this,
he would still be alive!
[grunts]
[music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Take that off.
[rebel 1] Let's move.
[grunts]
[rebel 2] Come on.
[Rebel 3 whistling]
[Rebel 3] Let's go. Hurry up.
I went too far...
bringing up your nephew.
We're here.
You built yourself a real army,
huh?
I'm proud of you.
I'd prefer it
if it was just the two of us.
I warned you, didn't I?
Little shit was a thief anyway.
Or did you give it to him
as a token of your affection?
[scoffs]
Bring out
my old friend's brother.
[grunts]
I'll never go with your king.
You prefer to stay
with your kidnappers?
Captain Martin.
Did Rosenberg
give you permission
to impale children?
Lady Katherine...
I'm in charge here.
This is all in the name
of the church.
And saving you, my lady.
Well, I'm in charge now.
And if this animal
comes near me,
you will lead your men
against him.
Lady Katherine,
can you give us...
You're not in your kingdom
with your sisters anymore.
Building your uncle's
grand alliance
with your legs spread, my lady.
[grunts]
[slashes]
[screams]
What have you done?
You killed him!
If Father was alive, he'd be
ashamed you were his son.
[grunts]
Shh! Come here.
[wagon rattling]
[horn blowing]
Turn around. We're here.
[Lars grunts]
Door.
[indistinct chatter]
[horses neighing]
Could I have a little?
[grunts]
No.
Now!
[grunts]
Archers!
Aim!
Now!
Shield!
[men grunting]
[Jan] Up!
[men grunting, panting]
Horsemen!
Attack!
[soldier groaning]
[guard 2] Release!
[men grunting]
Hold!
[soldiers screaming]
[Jan] And strike!
[soldiers groaning]
[grunts]
[horseman groans]
[whooping]
[horsemen groan]
I need more
of Rosenberg's soldiers.
Now!
[horn blows]
Go! Run!
You watch her.
[screams]
[rebels screaming, grunting]
[soldiers groaning]
[horsemen groans]
[soldier 1] Fall back!
[screams]
[horseman 2 groans]
What are you doing?
You cowards! Go back!
[rebels cheering]
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groans]
[Katherine shrieks]
[grunts]
[groans]
[Katherine muffled screams]
Rosenberg's foot soldiers.
Attack!
[loud thumping]
♪ Ye who are God's warriors ♪
♪ And of his law ♪
♪ Pray to God for help ♪
♪ And have faith in Him ♪
♪ That always with Him
You will be victorious ♪
[foot soldiers groaning]
[rebels cheering]
[foot soldiers
continue groaning]
[coughing, screaming]
Too much?
[all] No, sir!
[speaks foreign language]
[soldiers cheer]
The groschen are back
in our pocket.
Go!
[soldiers groaning]
This way. Come on. Come on.
[explosion]
[soldiers groaning]
[Captain Martin] It was a trap!
What?
They have her back!
I know where they are.
[pants, groans]
[chuckles]
This is not a good way to go.
It's been an honor
fighting alongside you.
I hope she's worth it.
[chuckling]
Her uncle is the king of France.
[Giovanni chuckling]
[emotional music playing]
[man] Zizka, what's the plan?
[groans]
[men screaming]
[grunts]
[groans]
[soldiers screaming]
[grunts]
[screams]
[soldier groans]
[grunts]
[breathes shakily]
[Torak grunts]
[screams]
Come on.
This way.
[men grunting]
[Torak grunts]
Zizka!
There!
Come on, let's go.
[grunts]
Jan!
Hey! Up... Up here!
[grunts]
Jan!
[coughs]
We have to go back.
We can't.
[Torak] Zizka!
[men coughing]
It's a dead-end.
[inhales sharply, coughs]
[thunder rumbling]
[coughs]
[pants]
[Katherine grunts]
[coughs]
[pants]
[thunder rumbling]
[soldiers coughing]
Follow the smoke
to all the exits.
You got it?
Give my dogs the trigger.
[grunts]
[Conrad]
Torak opened Jan's head.
We have to get back in there
and help him.
[Ulrich] No!
We follow his plan, and
regroup at the meeting point
near the hunting castle.
All of this
because of his brother.
All of this because of you!
They have our tracks.
We can lead them away from Jan.
But we have to go now.
[blows horn]
[hounds barking]
[grunts]
[emotional music playing]
[whimpers, breathes shakily]
[music continues]
[Anna] Jan!
Help me!
[young Jan] No!
Anna!
Death brings life.
[Jan] Death brings life.
[Katherine] There must
be a reason for all of this.
[groans]
[young Jan] Anna!
Anna!
Anna.
[hounds barking]
Keep moving.
[Zizka breathes heavily]
My mother gave me this ring.
Before I lost her.
Who's Anna?
You mentioned her in your sleep.
Don't disturb that.
[Jan groans softly]
How long do you think it will be
until the water is low enough?
I have to go home soon
and sort this all out.
We'll have to wait a bit longer.
You're not letting me go?
I saved your life.
[intense music playing]
Ask God where we hide
from her father
if they've killed her.
Because of this
incapable animal,
I'll do this differently.
I'll just give your brother
what he wants.
Why would you break
our agreement?
Less chance of her dying
and me along with her.
Not necessarily.
Out of my way, you animal!
[grunts, chokes]
[grunts]
[King Sigismund]
If you change our agreement,
I will do whatever it takes
to kill her.
I will burn every tree.
I will burn
every man in the forest.
And I will put an end to her.
And even the king of France
will go after you.
Hmm.
Forever.
[Torak] So...
if you're not with me,
you're against God.
Did I not mention that earlier?
[sobs]
[women whimpering]
Where's Zizka?
Maybe we should let
the dogs play.
No. [whimpers]
Huh?
[whimpers]
[groans softly]
[music playing]
[muffled screams]
[groans]
[swords rattling]
[Jan] Did you see the woman?
Come on, faster.
Look, down there.
Thanks for the armor.
[grunts]
[intense music playing]
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groans]
[pants]
[hounds barking]
I'm gonna need more stakes.
[pants]
Conrad is gone.
Son of a bitch.
[crowd clamoring]
[screams]
[grunts]
[wailing]
[Conrad]
That smell brings back memories.
Conrad.
So, to what do we owe the honor?
They will deliver her
to the king's hunting castle.
But... I can take you
to where they regroup
before that.
Ten thousand groschen.
[caws]
[whimpers]
Have you seen this all
so many times,
you no longer feel anything?
Jan Hus teaches us...
I've heard him preach.
[slurps]
But he's never been to war.
[squeaks]
[door closes]
[caws]
What happened to Anna?
She's gone.
I can see that you cared
for her.
Those feelings may be the only
thing you ever know that's true.
If there's one thing
that was given to us by God,
maybe that's all we're given.
Did you love her?
[music playing]
I ask as much for myself.
I'm not certain I can feel this.
My father gave me the freedom
to follow my heart.
Just as he needs his people.
But my mother she felt that...
women like me
shouldn't be married for love.
And if the marriages of my
sisters and I were arranged, well.
It could serve the greater good.
[indistinct chatter]
Because of you
Zizka will be close
to deliver her
to King Wenceslas.
[grunts]
Get the horses ready!
[Captain Martin] Move!
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[Jan] Let her go!
[bell tolling]
[Jan's father] Help!
You must kill him,
Father. [sobs]
[Jan's father]
They enforce the laws, Jan.
God would not allow this.
God's blessings
are not in what he gives.
They're what he takes.
Go get help!
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[music playing]
Let's go!
God's will.
I'll give you time
to get some distance.
[Jan] The one who paid to murder
Lord Boresh was your Rosenberg.
There's much to him
that you don't know.
[Captain Martin]
All right! We keep moving.
[guard 3] Yes, sir!
[Captain Martin]
Let the horses go.
[horse neighs]
[Captain Martin] Let's go!
[Katherine]
I won't let them use me anymore.
My will.
[music playing]
She's here?
Or Rosenberg with our money?
No.
Your brother...
now helps Rosenberg
try to rescue her.
Then my brother doesn't know
we are behind it.
You'll get word to him.
He knows.
Well...
we can always go to Rome
next spring.
[Lord Boresh]
You must unite the church.
And you must unite Europe.
Now.
Tell me,
did you want to be emperor?
What can we do to make sure
that Katherine escapes my brother?
Pray for them.
And for me.
[sighs]
[music playing]
[Captain Martin] This must
be punished without mercy,
according to laws passed down by
Emperor Charles IV, extended hand of God.
By order of Lord Rosenberg,
I sentence you
to hang for treason.
No.
Let him go. He's done nothing.
[grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
[Katherine]
We have to do something.
Too many.
Please, sir.
Just tell us what he's done.
We will punish him.
This bastard helped Zizka!
How can you live with this?
Hang him!
[groans, chokes]
[music playing]
[grunts]
[chokes]
No! Stop!
No, David!
No!
[pants]
Stop!
Stop it!
Lady Katherine?
Get him down now!
Take him down now!
[grunts]
Stop it!
Get him down!
Take your hands off her,
you fool!
Take him down!
Get him down, you fool!
No! Stop!
Take him down!
Now!
[Jan grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
[sobs]
[woman] David.
[ Grunts]
[grunts]
[guard groans]
David!
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
[whimpers, groans]
[sobs]
[David breathes heavily]
[horn blowing]
They have her.
[blows horn]
[villager] You can take her.
But let Zizka go.
Yes.
[Captain Martin]
You better back off!
Or every one of you
is gonna die here.
Let him go.
Yeah.
Let him go!
[groans]
[villagers gasp]
Stand back!
[groans]
[villagers scream]
[guards groan]
[groans]
[grunts]
[screams]
[groans]
[groans, screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
[whimpers]
[breathes shakily]
[pants]
We can still get them.
It's not far... [groans]
[thuds]
[pants]
[emotional music playing]
[sobs softly]
[sobs]
Are you all right?
I don't know.
Maybe the first thing I've ever
done that actually changed me.
[sobs]
[pants]
He killed ten men to save me.
And she?
She killed the captain herself.
Zizka.
There are so many joining us.
We no longer need to run.
We'll help you take Katherine
to the king.
I'm taking Katherine
to her father.
Her father?
She's the only chance
we have against Rosenberg here.
When he hears what's happened,
he'll do more damage to
Rosenberg than you ever could.
Let's go.
We have to take her
to the castle.
[Mick] Her father is in France.
We can get paid here tomorrow.
Her father will pay.
You can have my share.
[Ulrich] It's a waste of it.
Torak has ten more days
to find us...
It's an order!
Come on.
You'd really go
against your own king?
You remember
what we were taught?
Father was wrong.
[door opens]
You look as though you think
you might be staying.
[scoffs] Well, your hospitality
has me thinking about it.
But please,
no more as necessary.
How could you help Rosenberg
against us?
Against you?
I thought helping him
might put us in his good graces
for that money you need.
And I could never imagine that
you would be part of such a thing.
I assume that as you now know,
you will seize.
[growls]
[gate opens, closes]
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
to see you.
I need any soldier you can spare to
help your mercenaries bring her in.
And if you do that,
I'll support your trip to Rome.
For all this additional trouble,
we also need you
to lower the taxes
for the people in your region.
How many times
has my good brother told me
that God will always find a way
for us.
[meat cleaver thuds]
[roars]
[gasps]
Why are you doing this?
When I was a boy, all I
wanted to be was a king's knight.
I trained in the woods.
I trained...
hard.
Then one day,
the king's knights hanged Anna
for killing a hawk.
I tried to stop them, but...
my father made me understand
that what had happened
was right,
because the king's law
is God's law.
The kings may be chosen by God,
but they still make the mistakes
of men.
[groans]
Stop! No!
[Jan grunts]
Stop!
[grunts]
[Katherine grunts]
No!
[grunts]
Jan!
[Lars] France is too far.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
[singer vocalizing]
[music playing]
[eagle screeches]
[King Sigismund] I will carry
on faithfully, embracing duties
which you entrusted me at birth,
I will work tirelessly against
all those who work against us.
And until our work here is done,
the world may be mine,
but the power and glory
belong to you forever and ever.
Thank you, Lord,
for helping me to get there.
[music playing]
[whimpers]
You will never get away
with this.
Rosenberg and I
already have a deal.
[King Sigismund chuckles]
That was just to convince you
to empty your castle of men,
so that I could come along,
and...
take it. [chuckles]
And in return for my help,
the support
of Lord Henry Rosenberg
will give me
not only your crown, but...
[exhales] ...maybe even
the crown of emperor, too.
Uh, I don't remember
anything about that.
Oh. Did I forget
to mention that?
How absentminded of me.
[chuckles]
[gate opens]
[gate closes]
[David] Zizka!
Zizka!
I'm here!
[pants]
Lord Boresh is looking for you.
He was attacked
at the hunting castle.
But his captain got him out.
[grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
Zizka.
Where's Katherine?
She's headed to the castle
with my men.
Sigismund has taken it.
The castle.
He cannot be allowed
to get Katherine.
[grunts, groans]
He cannot be allowed to get her.
That'll be the end
of the kingdom.
When even those who rule...
can sink this low,
it is not possible
to change anything.
And to think,
I overlooked these people.
There's a way...
for you...
for all of you.
[music playing]
If you choose to fight,
you may die.
But for your cause!
And that is a good death.
I have already lost too much.
Please.
Stay here.
[smooches]
David.
Bring more help
from other villages.
[intense music playing]
[gate rattles, closes]
Your compensation.
Katherine.
Where's Lord Boresh?
Hunting with the king.
Katherine.
Why so anxious?
[groans]
[men groaning]
[whimpers]
Do it again!
Hold your arrows.
Show us another way out.
This way.
[whimpers]
Go, get her!
Go get her, you morons!
[groans]
[Mick grunts]
Protect this door.
[guards clamoring]
[both groans]
[men clamoring]
[grunts]
[groans]
[shrieks]
Stay back!
Once we're out with the money,
she's yours.
[grunts]
[Jan] Freddy.
Cover us.
Hmm.
[groans, pants]
[lion roars]
[screams]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[men clamoring]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
Don't move.
[growls]
[roars]
[whimpers]
[men clamoring]
[screams, groans]
Take me out!
No, no!
[all pants]
[men clamoring]
[grunts]
[Torak] Zizka!
He's mine!
[Zizka grunts]
[grunts]
Zizka!
[groans]
[grunts]
[screams, groans]
[screams]
[gasps]
No!
Zizka!
[grunts]
[screams]
[whimpers, chokes]
[groans]
[grunts]
[screams]
[emotional music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[screams]
[grunts, screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
[breathes shakily]
Come on.
[grunt]
[groans]
[grunts]
[screams, groans]
[groans]
[grunts]
[breathes shakily]
[groans]
[grunts]
No!
[snarls, spits]
[grunts]
[groans]
Look at me! Look at me!
[spits]
No rules.
You're the last.
Come and work for me.
[music playing]
As you wish.
[Katherine]
You'll kill him for no reason.
Death brings life.
No.
No!
[grunts]
[music playing]
[Torak grunts]
[groans]
Do you understand
what you've done to me?
[music playing]
[pants]
[retches, coughs]
I have you.
You're gonna be all right.
[smooches]
Better than ever.
Because now I know how it feels.
[music playing]
[breathes shakily]
♪ Ye who are God's warriors ♪
♪ And of his law ♪
♪ Pray to God for help ♪
♪ And have faith in Him ♪
♪ Ye who are God's warriors ♪
♪ And of his law ♪
♪ Pray to God for help ♪
♪ And have faith in Him ♪
[instrumental music playing]
[horse snorts]
[Jan] Honor...
justice...
freedom...
faith...
[heroic music playing]
...hope.
[loud rumbling]
Lord, forgive us
for what we're about to do.
[men clamoring]
[music playing]
♪ Find me ♪
♪ In the quiet ♪
♪ In the fields ♪
♪ In the water ♪
♪ In weed ♪
♪ From death comes life ♪
♪ If you listen for me
I'll be there with you ♪
♪ If you catch me ♪
♪ Whisper your life ♪
♪ If you catch me
Whisper your name ♪
[singer vocalizing]
♪ I'll sing for you ♪
[music playing]
♪ If you listen for me
I'll be there with you ♪
♪ If you catch me
Whisper your name ♪
♪ I'll sing for you ♪
♪ If you catch me
Whisper your name ♪
♪ I'll sing for you ♪
[vocalizing]