Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Did you do all that?
Beretta 93.
Usually dependable.
Should be good to go now.
What the fuck are you doing? Relaxing?
Where is Anton?
His phone is off.
Vali!
Your father's looking for you, let's go.
Wake up!
Hey girls, come on.
Go home.
Anton?
Where the fuck is Vali?
You were supposed to take care of him!
Hello. Yes?
Who is this?
It's me, Vali.
Vali? Vali?
Where the hell are you?
Why didn't you...
These bastards kidnapped me outside the hotel
and put me in a van.
What?
Who?
Who kidnapped you?
How the fuck should I know who kidnapped me?
They want three million Euro, right now.
Tell me what they look like.
Why the fuck does it matter what they look like?
They want three million Euro
in two hours
or I'll be cut up like a pig!
How dare you take my boy?
There it is.
You wanna count it?
Do you know who I am?
Don Preda...
Butcher of Bucharest,
Killer of Men.
Tell your boss it's done.
Exactly, who are you people?
We just...
We just find people
who can't be found.
The money...
You're gonna have it maybe for an hour.
Then we come take it back,
cut you both into pieces
and feed you to my pigs.
That doesn't worry you?
No.
Why?
I didn't come here for money.
I came here for you.
Why are you fighting
so hard, huh?
You're going home,
motherfucker. Fuck off.
I'm good.
- Didn't take any, huh?
- Take what?
Money.
It was all there, right?
We were paid to eliminate
a target. We did that.
Well, you know, three mil in dirty
money and nobody's looking for 'em...
Just saying.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you were hurting.
Please.
This is R&D Plumbing.
Your leak has been fixed.
Please remit the balance
of your payment for the...
Done.
You need to see a doctor
about that cough.
Traditional or a witch?
You? Definitely a witch.
Ah. I know
just the voodoo queen to call.
Chelmsford
was a bloody war zone.
Every train was 30 minutes
late and jam-packed as always.
Welcome back.
Thank you
for taking care of her.
You know you're the only one
she'll tolerate, right?
She gets really mean
when you're away.
Spent most of her time hanging
out with Proust.
- Is that true?
- Three weeks,
and this is all
you come back with?
You know sellers.
They know you've come all that
way, and they play hard to get.
Don't you want to just
kill people like that?
What are you doing, huh?
So the other day, he says to
me, "70 is the new 30."
Well, that's just something
old guys say.
How's he doing
with his protocol?
Is he following
the doctor's orders?
More like following
his own orders.
Happy birthday!
No more fucking birthdays!
Take birthdays
and shove them up your ass!
Bastard.
What a wonderful toy!
You skimped
on the candles I see.
Seventy would have been
a fire hazard.
- Could you make us some tea, please?
- Sure.
All right. Make your wish.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
A thank-you.
A 1958 Gibson Flying V. Mmm.
This was in production
just two years.
There's only 90
in the whole world.
I know.
That sound...
...it's the wood.
African limba.
Nothing else sounds like it.
I'd just about given up hope
of finding one.
- How in the world did you?
- You.
You taught me how to find things
that didn't wanna be found.
Albert King played one.
Albert King played that one.
No.
You're gonna cry now,
aren't you?
Oh, only because I can't play it
the way it needs to be played.
Thank you.
You know, one of the twins called me
last night to say she was pregnant.
Daisy in Dover?
Nah, Daisy in Manchester.
Daisy in Dover's a dyke.
Oh.
It is a rare gift to have
a friend who trusts you enough
not to try
and help until you ask.
Mmm.
If you fell in a pond
with those, you'd drown.
Well, if I fell in the pond without
'em, I'd probably float away.
- Hi, honey.
- Ah, ah, ah! Mind your fingers.
That heifer bites.
She's a baby
and doesn't know any better.
There.
You have
your own secret hideout.
Why am I not surprised?
I bought the building.
- What?
- The book store.
It's yours, free and clear.
You didn't have to do that.
I know, but it's your passion.
And makes me feel good to know
you'll have something
worthwhile when I'm gone.
What is that?
Those are the souls waiting
for me on the other side.
I'm sure they have
a reception planned.
Ah, I sent away so many
prematurely.
Either by my hand
or through you.
We never sent anyone away
who didn't have it coming.
Maybe.
But I'm sure there are
quite a few spirits up there,
waiting for me
with a bone to pick.
Aw.
You really believe
you're going up?
Don't you?
Lucas Hayes. I need our friend
to find him for me.
I have him up to 1998, Paris.
- After that, nothing.
- Just find?
Just find. Discreetly
and with a quickness.
Okay.
I may have to
go back to Vietnam.
Be nice if you went with me.
I'm never going back there.
Our past is never where
we left it, little chameleon.
We all have scars.
You stare at them long enough,
you remember how you got them.
- Hi.
- Morning.
The blue dress
has a small tear in it.
I was hoping
to talk to Benny about it?
What do you think?
- Of what?
- My, um... My mustache.
Oh, you know,
I don't have my contacts in.
- Mmm.
- Sorry.
Funny.
You wait till this grows in.
Women like you
are gonna be so...
- No, no, you're not, are you?
- No.
Need you to find this guy.
What, no satellite shots of a
mafia compound outside Bucharest?
No. But that was
some of your better work.
Moody wants this guy,
Lucas Hayes.
Last seen in Paris in '98,
and then nothing.
Mmm. Ah.
- I'll be with you in a second.
- Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for a book.
An old book.
Like, rare.
- Like, rare?
- Yeah.
Either they are
or they aren't.
Books aren't like a steak.
You can't get them, like, medium-rare.
That's funny.
- Sarcastic.
- Yeah, but funny.
Listen, my boss's wife
is having a party
and she collects books.
First editions.
- Any particular subject?
- Birds.
It's Audubon's, um...
- Birds of America?
- Yeah, that's it.
He said
she's looking for a copy.
- A first edition?
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- You don't have it?
No one does.
Only one first edition exists.
It was sold to a private buyer
in 1991 for $9.6 million.
Wow. Okay. Well,
looks like I'm outta luck.
All right. What do you think?
Maybe poetry?
Hang on.
You'd be the hit of the party.
I don't, uh...
I don't know this one.
It's Edgar Allen Poe,
actually.
His first collection of poems,
published anonymously.
You think she might have it?
Doubtful.
Only 50 copies were printed,
only 12 are known to exist.
Hmm. How much?
I can give it to you
for 265,000.
Perhaps a bracelet instead.
She does have
exquisite wrists. Good idea.
Is there something else?
I find you interesting.
- You mean...
- You're interesting.
And beautiful, sure.
Not in
that ornamental kind of way.
It's the interesting part
that's got me wondering.
Wondering what?
How long after I give you my
number will it take you to decide
that I'm just as interesting
and give me a call?
- Twenty-seven minutes.
- That long?
First, I have to pretend
to cancel my date
and then
I have to feed my cat.
That's six.
The rest
is me playing hard to get.
Cute. How many of these
are you carrying around, Mr...
Rembrandt. Michael Rembrandt.
Actually, I haven't had an
occasion to use one until just now.
So...
Interesting.
"There rose
a fountain once, and there
Full many a fair flow'r
rais'd its head:"
That was from the book,
wasn't it?
"But she who rear'd them
was long dead,
And in such follies
had no part..."
You almost got me on this one.
You didn't say I'd be tracking
an eight-year-old.
Lucas Hayes did arrive
in Paris in '98.
But returned to Da Nang,
March '99.
Everything else I have
is on there.
Benny, you'll stay open
until I get there, 45 minutes.
Moody.
Fuck, man!
Shit!
What the fuck was that?
Fuck.
Never thought
I'd see you here again.
Well, maybe you're not
seeing me now.
Who's the bitch?
Billy Boy.
I know you run with all kinds,
but now you're running
with stupid?
- Fuck you!
- Hey.
Go get a drink, sugar.
You give the adults some privacy, huh?
Beers!
Is that your ride outside?
Yours now.
It ain't my birthday.
Jossino Vohl.
How's Moody?
He's dead.
To Moody.
Vohl involved?
I don't know.
But he knows who is.
- He's gonna be hard to kill.
- I just wanna talk to him.
- Steverino!
- Yeah, boss?
You worked security
at the State Tower.
My friend here needs
a few minutes with Vohl.
Alone.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
Goes nowhere
without private security.
The guy's never alone.
This is how easy it is for me
to get to you, Mr. Vohl.
Do you understand?
You were friends and business
partners with Edward Hayes,
so you would know most about his
short, but interesting life?
Good, 'cause I have questions.
You give me answers.
If I'm satisfied,
you'll never see me again.
If I'm not, I'll be
the last thing you ever see.
I look forward
to hearing from you.
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
It's been a long time since
such a beautiful young woman
gave me her number.
You know who I am.
Jossino Vohl,
born in April 1945.
French national
residing full-time in Vietnam,
was in business with Edward
Hayes until his untimely death.
Now you're
a top political power broker
with some
interesting side hobbies.
I see you're familiar
with my résumé.
I am not interested in your
business activities, Mr. Vohl.
I want to talk about
your friend's son, Lucas.
My office. One hour.
Will you be alone?
My lawyer will be present.
That would be the man standing behind
you, pouring the scotch?
Enchantée, mademoiselle.
Exactly on time.
Please.
Monsieur Duquet,
my personal attorney.
- Would you like some champagne?
- Edward Arthur Hayes.
Mmm.
Eddie and I were involved in a
bauxite mining project together,
- until his accident.
- It wasn't an accident.
It was an assassination.
We were useful.
The country was malleable,
ripe for certain business practices.
Eddie was juggling
a lot of delicate plates.
What's your interest in a man
who's been dead almost 30 years?
I'm interested in his son.
Lucas Hayes.
I'm sorry?
Three people are dead because
they inquired about him.
He had them killed
and I'm going to find him.
Should I be talking to him?
I have no connection
with Lucas Hayes.
And what has any of this
got to do with me?
I was wondering
the same thing.
Mr. Vohl's past relationships
are no one's concern.
- And certainly none of yours.
- Well, I've made them my concern.
Too bad.
I need to know everything.
Who are you?
Who hired you?
Why the interest
in Lucas Hayes?
We can do this another way,
if you'd like.
Fucking let me go.
Get up there.
- Hand me a gun.
- Here.
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
Say it.
- Fuck you.
- Say it!
Let's start with your name.
Why was Moody looking
for Edward Hayes's son?
Who else out there
should we know about?
Fuck.
Anyone ever last this long?
It's out of our hands now
anyway.
Him?
That was a long 27 minutes.
I'm still waiting
for your call.
It's all right. I don't
take these things personally.
Bone broth.
Helps with inflammation
and bruising.
Here.
Careful, it's hot. Watch it.
There you go.
Made this myself.
Here you go. Small sips.
Good?
I'm not gonna lie to you.
There's not much chance
this ends well for you.
That guy out there, we work
for the same individual.
Boss has a problem, he calls
him, he takes care of it.
Little heavy-handed for my
taste, but that's not my call.
I'm sorry
about your friend, Moody.
I had no part of that.
Or the firefight
at the bookstore.
I'm an "after-the-facts" guy.
I come in and make sure
there's no loose ends.
I look for things that might
seem benign, but aren't.
Like a bookstore owned
by an assassin.
Boy, I never saw
that one coming.
I misread you completely.
I can help you outta here,
okay?
But you have to help me.
I'm your last line of defense.
End of the road.
No more lifelines.
You understand?
All right.
You forgot to blanch
the bones.
Your soup.
You have to blanch the bones
before you roast them.
It locks the minerals in.
It's better for healing.
- You get anything out of her?
- Yes and no.
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
It means I'll be back in the
morning to follow up with her.
I don't need you here,
Rembrandt.
Well, the man who signs
the checks felt differently.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- And why's that?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it's because you killed Vohl
without asking his permission.
Vohl knew everything.
He was a direct connection.
He would have folded
like a tent.
You guys kill me.
You're all the same.
Shoot first
and ask questions later.
And hold off on those enhanced
interrogation techniques.
I want her clearheaded
in the morning.
He'll break her tomorrow.
Maybe he broke her already.
The old man is desperate
to know what she knows.
Wonder how he'd feel
if his boy wonder
ends up killing her
before he finds out.
I'm guessing you look
for a new boy wonder?
Just when we were getting
to know each other.
I've got teams at every airport,
shipyard and train station.
She's not gonna run.
She's gonna lick her wounds,
then she's coming after you.
Good.
Really?
'Cause right now it's 4-0.
She's winning.
Where do you buy your suits?
'Cause I've got a cousin
who's big and tall,
and he has a hard time.
Nobody home.
Well,
we can get you to the border.
London may not be safe
for you right now.
This is Vietnam, Anna.
You know what it's like here.
You owe it to Moody
to stay alive.
I know what I owe him.
The fuck you think
I gave you the money for...
End of the line, kid.
Moody was beautiful.
In his way.
He was kind.
And not through effort.
It was just a part of who he was.
He didn't save my life,
he gave me a life.
He knew who I was
and what I'd... become.
And he protected me.
Hayes has been dead
for 30 years.
Vohl is no longer.
And you got some very bad
people looking for you.
Lucas Hayes killed Moody.
He knows I'm looking for him.
His last known location is
Saint Quiteria Hospital.
Nobody is as deaf as those
who don't wanna listen.
I must say, Ms. Nguyen,
it's been some time
since we've had
a visit
from the Ministry of Health.
And to request records
from that far back...
Yes, I know. Well,
we're hoping to find something in there
that will help us rule out
environmental factors,
as we are in the midst
of a study. Thank you.
Lucas Hayes...
Well before my time here.
2585024586.
Copy. I'll get Doc on it.
Okay.
Doc came through.
Pulled his records.
- And?
- You sitting down?
Lucas Hayes was admitted to Saint
Quiteria on the 2nd of June, 1999.
And according to his records,
never left.
I apologize. Seems the boy was
readmitted under the name "Christian".
Christian, right,
his mother's maiden name.
He was already here
when I arrived.
He's been a patient
for more than 20 years.
He doesn't like to be touched.
He can't speak.
Also, deaf and blind.
And how long
has he been like this?
He was diagnosed
when he was six, I believe.
It progressed rapidly.
It's a miracle
he's lived this long.
And who pays for his care?
We have a generous endowment.
Everyone here
is treated for free.
Wow. Four men dead
and nothing on camera.
Place looked like an abattoir.
- Was it the food?
- You know, it was bad manners.
Yeah, well,
that's no way to treat a lady.
Oh, I'm no lady.
Well, I'm not always
a gentleman myself.
I wouldn't
sell yourself short.
Mmm. Well, coming from you,
that's a compliment.
Listen, I'm in the middle of
something, if you don't mind...
Hey, how were the good Sisters
of Saint Quiteria?
Good enough to let me know I've
been looking for the wrong person.
They're good gals up there.
- Saint Quiteria, you know who she was?
- Mm-mmm.
Fifteen years old, she led a guerrilla
war against the Roman legions.
- Badass.
- Yeah. They chopped off her head
and fed the rest to the dogs.
Again, bad manners.
Hey, you up for dinner?
I can answer some questions and,
you know, save you some time.
What do you say, we say to La Cinq?
Tomorrow night. Eight o'clock.
I mean you can say it,
but I won't be there.
I'll give you a time
and place.
You're intrigued by her.
Curious.
Need I worry?
The gala list, sir.
Our 200 guests, all vetted.
Huh. The joys of a room full
of the wealthy and the privileged
donating large sums
for a noble cause.
It never gets old.
Good.
Why do you do this?
It's what people in my position
are supposed to do, Michael.
- Give to the less fortunate.
- Ah.
I asked
if I should be worried.
About the woman.
Nope.
Not yet.
Please wrap up
this unpleasantness by Sunday.
I don't wanna be embarrassed
before the celebration.
Wow.
Thank you, Ben.
They know me here.
Cheers!
Someone killed
a friend of mine
because of a contract
he completed years ago.
And anyone I ask about it
ends up dead. Why is that?
Well, I don't know,
but some people might take that as a sign.
Why don't you just consider it
a mystery best left unsolved.
But I like mysteries.
When I started this,
I was curious.
And then I went from curious
to concerned.
- And now?
- I'm testy.
And trust me, you don't
wanna know me when I'm testy.
HK 9-millimeter.
Very good.
Not where I'm sitting.
Who's paying
for the orphan kid?
I'd like to talk
to whoever that is.
That would be unwise.
Unwise is killing a man
who was a second father to me.
We are way past unwise.
This is a really bad place
for a hit.
High-end restaurant
with security at every exit,
not to mention the cameras.
You know what,
you already knew that.
Oh, I'm not here to kill you...
yet.
Just get answers.
You always ask like this?
Yeah, I like to have people's
attention when I talk, you know?
Well,
you certainly have the attention
of the boys down there.
Look, you're going
to have to put
at least three in me
to be sure.
- Four.
- Fine. That leaves you five.
- In case there's trouble.
- Uh-huh.
You think that's enough
to get you out of here?
Four quick shots
and then a slow walk
to the exit amongst the chaos.
Yeah.
Something unexpected
could happen.
You know, usually does.
SIG 226.
- Mmm, it's got that great kick.
- Kick.
Yeah.
How about that?
Our first awkward silence.
You know what?
I didn't get your name.
Anna.
- Pleasure.
- We'll see.
What do you say
we forget these drinks?
Let's just go find
a nice hotel.
You point a gun at my pussy
and then you ask me to bed?
I like your style.
Said the woman with hollow
points pointed at my balls.
Well, let's hope this doesn't get messy.
These are my favorite shoes.
Manolo's,
classic four-inch pumps.
A man who knows Poe
and footwear.
Let me put this to you
delicately.
You keep this up,
you're gonna die.
Vietnam has always been
a place of death.
Only the lucky ones make it out alive.
I was lucky once.
You don't get lucky twice.
I'm going to find out
who killed my friend.
And when you do?
I'm going to end their life
and anyone standing in my way.
Thank you
for a lovely evening.
Hey, I know
this sounds crazy, but...
I'd really like
to see you again.
Under, you know,
different circumstances.
This was personal time.
So these are the best circumstances
you'll ever see me in.
Speak.
Call me when it's done.
Thought you were off
chasing corrupt accountants?
Found her hotel room, all of her
shit, including her passport.
Name's Nadia Zhukova.
An Asian Russian...
Boy.
You don't really see that.
Ever.
Good work.
You must be exhausted, huh?
Looks like I'm a day late.
And a dollar short.
Didn't take much I'm afraid.
Sang like a bird, did he?
Oh, the things I know now.
I know who your boss is.
The man who sanctioned Moody's killing.
Huh.
- He's a big fish.
- More fun when you hook 'em.
Well, then I guess...
I guess we'll be seeing
each other real soon then.
Sooner than you'd think.
Hey, what happened
to your hand?
Make up your mind.
Kill me...
or fuck me.
Is it weird that we're
in this guy's bed while he's...
up there?
You know, hanging?
No.
- Be a waste of a nice bed.
- Okay.
How long you been doing this?
Not, you know, this, but...
Long enough not to miss.
You got lucky.
Nah. You don't
want me dead...
yet.
Why haven't you killed me?
Could you?
I could put two in the back of
your head and go make a sandwich.
Well...
you always said
this wasn't gonna work out.
Well, it's been my experience,
it never does.
At least not
for the other guy.
- There a way around that?
- You're holding all the cards.
I'm watching a woman walk
over a shark tank,
on a tight rope,
in high winds.
You're not gonna make it,
Anna.
He's a bad man
who's done very bad things.
So, you just gonna lay there?
Good to see you, kid.
Get in. Get out.
You know you only get lucky once.
- Yeah, someone else just told me that.
- Okay.
- Oh, God! Good God!
- Ah, ah, ah. Just a little glue.
- Just a little glue. It's okay.
- Wrong with you?
Grit your teeth.
Oh, God.
You know, I still feel
really bad about Claudia.
I mean, she couldn't cook
worth a shit,
but she didn't deserve
to die like that.
- There we go.
- Okay.
Okay, okay, we're done.
We're done here.
Did you really think they
could kill me that easily?
Before I blew
the rest of it off,
he didn't have much of a face
to begin with.
And I left just enough of me for
the authorities to think it was me.
Sorry you had to be
the one who found him.
But you could always
think on your feet anyway.
Not so much tonight.
That's what friends are for,
right?
Oh, good.
We're friends again.
Ooh, you got laid,
didn't you?
Depending more and more on
this shit to take the edge off.
So, what's the plan?
Four hundred acres.
To get there,
you'd have to hike
through 12 miles
of rat-infested jungle.
That leaves a river, cameras,
sonar, patrol boats.
Still a pessimistic
little shit, aren't you?
And you're still
a cockroach you can't kill.
I mean that in a good way.
They know you're coming.
What is this?
It's a panic room.
In this case, it's a panic bunker.
If he gets in there,
you're done.
All the guests arrive
by boat.
They'll be screened
the moment they disembark.
Perimeter locked down
and site secured.
And I've added
an additional team
of 16 out of Israel
just for the night.
Seems like you got
everything covered.
Michael.
Thoughts?
Venice.
It's really nice
this time of year.
You should go. Now.
These guys have no idea
who they're dealing with.
You look a little tense.
I've protected everyone from
crown princes to cartel kingpins.
Nothing's gonna happen
tonight,
especially when we know
what she looks like.
Boy, I really hope
you got paid up front.
Sir?
- Anything?
- Nothing so far.
Sectors 1, 2 and 3 are clear.
I'm waiting on the reports from sector 4.
Mmm.
Thank you. It is with great
pleasure that I welcome you all here
on this
very expensive evening.
It warms my crusty heart
to look across
the room and see
so many familiar faces,
dear friends
and close business associates,
as well as
quite a few unfamiliar faces
that, with luck,
will not remain so for long.
Perhaps I may even have spotted
a few former foes of mine.
I want especially to thank you
for coming
and for seeing the error
of your ways.
Over these considerable years,
I've learned to my great satisfaction
there is no better way to
cleanse the soul than to do good,
to perform selfless deeds
and acts of kindness,
to sacrifice for others,
and most importantly, to give generously.
It is due to your generous
spirit that we have been able
to enrich and enhance
the lives of so many infants,
children, young men and women
in desperate need of care
to a degree that would have
been impossible to achieve
without every one of you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for the privilege
of being your host tonight.
And for allowing me to slide my
hands into your pockets and purses.
But for a worthy cause.
The Sisters of Saint Quiteria
do outstanding work,
so give with your hearts.
Get to the door now!
You look really good for a man
who's been dead 30 years, Mr. Hayes.
How'd you get in here?
Technology. Shit's
gonna fuck us all one day.
Who are you?
I'm the big bad wolf
that comes to get you
when someone on this earth
decides your time is up.
Moody.
Resurrection's a bitch,
ain't it?
Come to finish the job,
have you?
Well, you did hire me all those
years ago to kill you, right?
Who was really in that car?
Does it matter? Disposable asset.
No one of consequence.
See, that's the kind of shit I
expect someone like you to say.
"No one of any consequence."
Someone like me?
I mean, I can't be all morally righteous.
I kill people for a living.
Bad people, mind you.
But still, I never pretend
to be anything else.
You, you're front and center of a
dozen high-profile charitable causes.
The world sees you as clean
as first fucking snow.
But your hands are covered
in shit and blood,
and everything from sarin gas
to human trafficking.
So you know why
I had to arrange my demise.
I had a son.
Unexpected in many ways.
But what I couldn't fathom was the
depth of love I had for this child,
this imperfect,
wonderful, vulnerable boy.
If I were dead, Lucas would be
free from any threats or harm.
Bullshit.
You may love your son,
Mr. Hayes,
but this was your chance
to disappear.
You're very astute.
No one looks for a dead man.
I was able to continue
behind a shroud
of respectability
that allowed me to...
To become a bigger monster.
The irony of all this,
Mr. Hayes,
is that I was just trying
to make amends
to your son for taking
his father away from him.
You brought all this
upon yourself.
Anna.
You don't look so good.
Oh, I don't know.
Nothing an apple martini and a
liter of AB-positive won't fix, huh?
Hey, what do you think the
chances are of me getting either?
Faint.
Something funny?
I find it amusing you think
you're better than me.
Not better.
Different.
See, most people are good,
Mr. Hayes.
And occasionally, they do
something they know is bad.
Some people are bad,
and they struggle every day
to keep it under control.
Others are corrupt to the core
and just don't give a damn.
That would be me.
But evil?
Evil is a completely
different creature, Mr. Hayes.
Evil believes bad is okay,
its actions justified.
Violence divorced
from conscience.
No matter what toll it takes,
or who it takes it upon.
And there, my friend,
is where we part ways.
I'm just a bad man who's
looking to pay for his sins.
I see.
So you're here to clear
your conscience first?
You'll never get out
of here alive.
I never intended to.
One more thing.
You could have killed
the old man.
Why didn't you?
That wasn't the plan.
Stop! Stop!
- No!
- Mama!
No!
What took you?
Stopped for a bite.
You just gonna stand there?
For now.
Doesn't have to
be this way, Anna.
Not anymore.
We all have to pay
for our sins eventually.
Doesn't have to be today.
I'm tired.
I want peace.
And I can't have it
knowing you're out there.
What if I told you, you could?
Yeah.
Two in the back of the head,
then go have a sandwich.
You can't buy back your past,
Anna.
You can't change
where you came from.
But you can change
where you're going.
Where would that be?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull