Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
What the hell is that?
What's going on?
Port side engine's on fire.
Go back to your seat.
Controls aren't responding.
Brace for impact!
At 0130, a C-47,
alongside its 10-man crew,
disappeared 80 miles
south of Stuttgart.
So...
We've been tasked
with checking it out.
- Hey, get the gear.
- Move out.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Korsky, Hoyte,
Gardner, Castle, move.
Get to work.
Simms, rear!
Hey, we found
some clips of Swedish...
Everyone else,
keep your goddamn ears open.
Vehicle, six o'clock!
Easy, Sergeant.
Fuck.
Son of a fucking...
Major Johnson.
What a surprise.
I was told you were
running operations
from a chateau
outside of Reims, sir.
Yeah, well, I guess
I got a little tired
of eating frog legs
and foie gras.
Well, I just hope you didn't
make the drive in vain, sir.
Hey, come on.
You know, Sergeant,
a conductor needs to just
come to the orchestra pit
for some time.
You know, from time
to time, brother.
Mm.
Yeah, but this ain't no opera,
and these ain't no violins.
They just happen to make
sweet music of their own.
Come on, you think you
could pick it up a little?
Well, I think it's time I
introduce you to someone.
Walsh is an old pupil of
mine from back in Texas.
He's also quite literally
the only man for the job.
I got 12 men already,
and you know 13
ain't a lucky number.
You know that plane went
down behind enemy lines,
and it was carrying
sensitive material.
And Walsh is going to be
riding with you to retrieve it.
My team doesn't need outside
help recovering cargo, sir.
Disobeying orders.
That's a court martial offense.
Yeah, but if I'm in jail,
who's gonna do your
dirty work, huh?
It's nice to see
you haven't changed.
It's great catching up,
Sergeant.
It's always such a
pleasure to see you.
Well, but as you know,
time is of the essence.
Watch your step.
Come here.
Don't just stand
around, we got work, man.
You ever whacked any Jerries?
Depends on your definition
of whacked, sir.
Christ, just keeps
getting better and better.
All right, listen up, boys.
We're gonna find that wreckage
and we're gonna
patch up who we can,
and we're gonna let this
guy sift through the rest.
Let's move out!
Keep moving,
come on, hey.
You know, when we
were at Marseilles,
I pulled Brewer
from a burning APC.
Two of his men were
still trapped inside.
Bastards, they were screaming,
and before I could get to them,
a Stuka swooped
down out of nowhere,
and well, what can I say,
there was nothing left but
a crater where they'd been.
Brewer still despises me
for it.
He'd rather die a
thousand deaths himself
than lose a single damn soldier.
That's the kind of man he is.
And I'll tell you what, I sure
wish we had more like him.
All right, all right,
waterproof your gear,
we're taking the scenic route.
Yes, Sarge.
All right, wait,
fuck, just wait.
Come on, get those
tubs and a whetstone.
Walsh, tell me.
What makes this sensitive
material so special they need a,
an entire squad dedicated to it?
I don't ask about what
they send me to retrieve.
- And why is that?
- Keep moving, come on.
Well, if I'm captured, that
way it's impossible for them
to get anything out of me,
no matter how much
they torture me.
Come on, hurry up.
This just arrived
from command, sir.
Let's have some
coffee first, huh?
Sir, yes sir.
- Quit moving around!
- Flatten it out!
We'll search this quad first.
Make our way to high ground.
All right.
Then scan from there.
I wanna find this
crash site before nightfall.
Come on, let's move out.
Oh, shit.
Well, you certainly know you're
back in the thick of things
when the lukewarm dirt
passes for coffee.
Listen, this operation's
been designated top secret.
Anything you hear or see
from this point forward
is not to leave this tent.
You get my drift?
Yes, sir.
Understood, sir.
I'm curious, though.
You have some of the best
surveyors in the world
at your disposal.
Why bring me in?
Well, I hear your
German is impeccable.
My PhD thesis was
on dialect diversity
of ancient Germanic tribes.
Well then, let's put it
to the test, shall we?
I want you to listen up.
Our codebreaker's been
analyzing a transmission
recorded by OSS.
Okay.
Right here,
what are they saying?
Just a bunch of
random numbers, sir.
No, no, no, no.
The voice in the
background, the woman.
I will play it at a half speed.
Sounds like...
Sounds like Baum des Lebens.
Baum des Lebens,
what does that mean?
Tree of life.
Sarge.
Sarge, can I wipe
my ass with this
when we run out of toilet paper?
Did our guys do it?
No way.
SAS, maybe.
The Brits wouldn't do
this, or the French,
and the Russians
ain't this far west.
Luger, nine millimeter.
Krauts did this to their own?
I bet these men were deserters.
You know what I say?
The Krauts start killing Krauts,
sit back and enjoy
the fireworks.
Taft.
Let the Jerry rot in peace.
Take cover!
Don't worry, it's okay to
piss yourself the first time!
Korsky!
Go.
Thoretti!
Cover fire!
- Go, get in there.
- Go!
Clear!
Gardner.
Ask him how many
are still out there.
Hey, easy, man, easy.
Can I look?
Come on, boy,
speak English.
Shell shock due
to severe trauma.
I've seen this before.
Beat him all you want,
he ain't saying a word.
Yeah, he shoots well
for severe trauma.
Get him up, he's coming with us.
Sergeant?
What's the problem, Walsh?
Forget to get shot?
I hope you get over
your trauma soon,
you limey son of a bitch.
Sure it's wise to
take him with us?
I'll find a use for him.
He'll give away our position
first chance he gets.
You just worry about that
plane we need to find, huh?
You and Rucker check it out.
Right there.
Yeah, check it out.
It's nothing, let's go.
Let's go.
Holy fucking fruit.
Let's go!
Okay, yeah.
Oh shit!
Who... who the hell
are those women?
They're civilians,
they hide up here from us.
Their husbands are off
fighting the war somewhere.
I never seen
civilians like that before.
Not even in France.
Oh, you haven't been
laid in a long time, Ruck.
Maybe you never have.
You kidding me?
I used to get it all the
time back home in Sweden.
Yeah, right.
- Women?
- Absolute knockouts.
The redhead, man.
She got this gorgeous body
with two perfectly round...
At ease, Rucker.
But sorry, Chief,
them girls might know
where the plane went down.
Yeah, he's right, Sarge.
Me and Simms here, we can
use our interrogation skills
from Paris, you know?
My zook's loaded and
ready to fire, man.
We got a man down.
We're not gonna
risk our position
to mess with civvies, got it?
- Got it.
- Yeah.
You got a problem, Walsh?
No, sir.
Let's move.
So I'm thinking about asking
Sarge for a one night pass.
Dream on, Ruck.
Are you telling me you
wouldn't wanna ride
one of them moaning girls?
We got married two
days before I shipped.
Look at this.
She's two already,
and I never held her once.
I ain't betraying my
family for some Nazi whore.
Ooh, Nazi whore.
I like the sound of that.
What the hell?
This don't make a
shit worth of sense.
We've been following
that contour for an hour.
Now we're in the same spot?
There's no way the sun is north.
We must be in the middle of
some, some kind of magnetic ore.
It could be what
took down the plane.
What?
It could be what
took down the plane.
When Odysseus entered
the land of the dead,
the demons,
they changed the stars
so he would lose direction.
What kind of fufu
gibberish is that, Walsh?
It's Greek mythology.
Okay, do me a favor.
You keep your goddamn poetry
to yourself, all right?
Somebody's been here
after we left.
Well, it takes wolves
a couple hours
to sniff out the grave and
start digging up the body.
Olin, fire up the radio.
We'll use it as a
signal to navigate.
I need two volunteers
to guard the perimeter.
Everyone else, 10-minute rest.
I'll take the
southeast quadrant.
Will you now?
All right, whatever, Walsh.
Carbony, your rifle.
Walsh, don't make me regret it.
Gotta drop a bomb.
Keep right where I can see you.
I'd rather get shot than have
you watch me taking a shit.
Sierra Echo,
this is Falcon Seven.
- Do you copy, over.
- Sarge.
Sierra Echo,
Major Johnson
needs to speak with you, over.
Copy, Falcon Seven.
It's dead, sir.
♪ Go on, brave Spartan ♪
♪ You are most welcome ♪
♪ To stay here for food ♪
♪ So tired from trouble ♪
♪ So weary of war ♪
♪ Give into rest, soldier ♪
♪ Fight no more ♪
I have no idea
what you're saying.
Hey, you stay right
where you are.
Friend?
That's our bird.
Damn.
Now would you
believe if I told you
I've never done this before?
This is Captain Rice.
Everyone else is dead.
Captain Rice?
Captain, can you hear me?
Do you copy me?
Captain Rice?
Captain, can you hear me?
Oh no, dear god.
First section, let's move!
Please help me!
Help me.
Don't kill me.
- Walsh.
- Yeah, at ease, G.I.
What the hell are you doing?
I heard a shot.
Why'd you discharge your weapon?
I ain't telling you shit.
You ain't the sarge.
But I am.
Walsh put a knife
to my throat, sir.
Almost killed me.
Walsh?
Your man, he fired his weapon,
he charged the squad.
I'm not taking any chances.
What were you
firing at, Private?
I was charged by a wild pig.
What were you doing
out there anyway?
I...
I found the plane, sir.
Good job, Private.
Let's move!
I thought you said you didn't
have any combat experience.
Well, I never said that.
I guess maybe you
just assumed it?
Then how'd you learn to
take down a man like that?
Burma.
Hey, Walsh.
I really don't
care how many Japs
you bushwhacked in the jungle.
You do that to one
of my men again,
you're gonna answer to me.
It's just wild boars.
Sounded like one of
Rucker's potato farts.
Remember D-Day, Bo?
Yeah, I thought
we were gonna die
before we hit the beach.
Let's move.
Friar, north perimeter.
Rucker south, rest of
you sweep for survivors.
Walsh, do what
you came here for.
Sergeant.
There were 11 flyboys on
this bird when it crashed.
There should be bodies,
or parts of them anyway.
Krauts must have got
in here before we did,
took all the bodies away.
No, it wasn't the Germans,
that's for sure.
Oh, I almost forgot.
We got an expert in our midst.
If the Nazis had been here, sir,
they wouldn't have left this.
Okay, we found the plane,
we found the secret stuff.
Can we go home now?
We're not going anywhere.
If there's a, even
the slightest chance
that one of these
flyboys is still alive,
I'm not leaving them behind.
Sarge.
This way.
Ah, Jesus.
You okay, man?
Yeah, okay.
Sarge.
Simms!
Captain Rice.
USAF.
Morgan.
Check him out.
He's dead, sir.
I said check him out.
The Japs got to him.
That ain't
Japanese, you idiot.
Then what is it?
Bird, tree, death.
Ancient magical symbols.
Cut him open.
- I'll do it.
- Do it.
I heard stories
about Nazi doctors
doing this kind of thing.
You know, medical experiments,
mutilations, drugs.
Had enough of this bullshit.
This man, he has
no internal organs.
In Haiti they use feathers
to bring back the dead and shit.
It's called hoodoo or something.
Stop that crap right now.
All right.
You fellas wanna
know what's going on?
We got all the
answers right here.
Right here.
You start talking
or you start eating.
Hexen.
- Hexen.
- What does hexen mean?
Witches, sir.
You fellas are right.
Should have shot him
right on the spot.
I'll do
him right now, Sarge,
- just say the word.
- No, no, it's too late.
Too late.
Crew's dead.
And I ain't going
back empty-handed.
Put the dead in the ground.
We're going home.
What do you know?
You know, in 1840,
Hans Garmin, the German
national wanted in connection
to dozens of missing
children in Leipzig.
He was arrested trying
to enter the US,
and this manuscript was found
sewn into the lining
of his luggage.
It's the first of
a two-volume set.
You have the
second part as well, sir?
Well, certainly not
for lack of trying.
I've led teams across three
continents in search of it.
Come here, tell me what
you make out of it.
Right here.
Hm.
Old High German, definitely.
Well, I mean, I could
have told you that.
But sir, this is the oldest
form of the Germanic language,
hasn't been spoken this
way in 1,000 years.
Okay.
Defeating time, does that
make any sense to you, sir?
Well, yeah, more than
you could imagine.
No wonder that fucking
Fuhrer's agents
have been scouring the area.
I just hope we find
it before they do.
This ain't playtime, Walsh.
You gonna tell me that
after everything we've seen,
nothing seems strange
to you in the slightest?
Two years ago, I was in Italy.
And we'd been spilling
our brains out
fighting the Germans
right and left.
But then, on Christmas Eve,
everything got quiet.
The Jerries started
playing Christmas carols
on their loudspeakers.
And their boys and our boys
joined together.
Two days later,
we started blowing each
other's brains out,
just like before.
So, no.
Nothing seems strange
to me anymore.
Help dig.
Rucker.
Rucker, tell me what you saw
back there, at the windmill.
Come on, man, I know
you saw something.
Tell me what you saw.
Tell me about the women.
Oh, Jesus, I think
I'm gonna be sick.
Easy there, easy, easy.
Let me help you.
Don't touch me!
Rucker?
Morgan, help him out.
Stay back.
Whoa, whoa.
Stay back, or I'll shoot myself.
What the hell you doing, Ruck?
I'm so sorry.
Come on.
Stay down, stay down.
Give him a shot!
Stick him!
Jesus Christ.
I told him to stay away
from those French tarts.
He didn't go with no
French tarts, Gardy.
Ruck's never even
had a girlfriend.
Look like it's eating his flesh.
If he can't walk,
put him on a stretcher.
We gotta hit that river
by nightfall.
Let's finish up this
business, all right?
Where is he?
- Get that goddamn Jerry!
- Shit!
You got one chance
to quit squirming.
Oh God.
Who did this?
He says they
exsanguinated him,
like they did to his men.
Sergeant, nobody can
bleed out a man that fast.
Witches can.
I want a better explanation.
Brewer!
I really think you
should talk to Rucker.
You got something you
wanna tell me, Private?
More, ow, morphine.
It hurts really bad.
No.
Not till you tell us
what you know.
I shot one.
What the hell you talking about?
I fucked one,
and then I shot her.
You shot a civilian?
I, she was, she,
she wasn't a civilian.
She was a witch, Sarge.
The hell did you do to me?
Get back.
As my chosen one,
you will never die.
Get the hell away from me.
We're never getting out
of this forest.
They won't let us.
All right, all right, all right.
Give this fucker his morphine.
Make it a triple shot,
will you, huh?
Bury Friar with the others.
I want a defensive
position along that ridge,
mined with everything
we got, okay?
In five minutes,
I want you to switch over
to this frequency.
0321.
Copy, over.
Walsh, it's
Johnson, go ahead, over.
I found the film, sir.
We were informed that
another SS search party
is currently in route.
But Brewer, his squad is
really losing it, sir.
This place, it...
It plays tricks on the mind.
Goddamn lazy surprise
sons of bitches.
Fuck!
I can't take it anymore,
I swear to god,
I can't take another
fucking minute.
Rucker's cursed us.
Okay, Sarge?
No, he's not okay,
none of us is okay.
Shut your fucking mouth
or I will shut it for you.
Sarge...
Speak to me.
Sierra Echo,
reading you loud
and clear, over.
Four KIA, one severely infirmed.
Requesting updated extraction
point due to casualties, over.
Son of a bitch.
Poison gas.
And Major Johnson's
outdone himself this time.
Treating us, acting like
fucking guinea pigs.
Sir, all I heard was static.
- Huh?
- I didn't hear anything either.
What about you, Korsky?
Sir, I heard exactly
what you heard.
Bullshit!
This is Sierra Echo,
do you copy me, over.
The hell you think you're doing?
Proving to you that
there is no one there.
Base come in,
this is Sierra Echo,
- do you copy me, over.
- Put the handset down.
See, nothing.
Hello, base command,
anyone, please,
my CO has lost his fucking mind.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
- whoa whoa!
- Oh Jesus.
- You shot me.
- Just a graze.
Next one won't be.
Now sit the fuck down.
Private Taft, you do
not have permission
to leave this space!
Anyone else wanna
question my authority?
Huh?
Anyone?
What about you, Walsh?
You hear the voice
on that radio?
Oh god, please don't
kill me, please.
Please.
Hey.
Your watch.
There was only static
on that radio, Korsky,
and you know it.
Sarge got us through
four years of this crap
without getting us shot.
If he wants to hear
voices on the radio,
then I'll hear them too.
Come on!
Is that a pig?
I got one!
What happened?
Sarge here, he just got
us our first decent meal.
Right, Sarge?
Sure hope Taft's all right.
Ah, he'll be fine.
Had a similar incident
in Marseilles.
He'll be back soon
as he gets a whiff
of this good old barbecue.
Mm, num num.
Want me to feed the Kraut too?
We all know you got a
soft spot for Krauts,
ever since your mama fucked one.
Don't make me kick your
ass, you son of a bitch.
I'll feed the goddamn Jerry.
All right.
Let it be known how Americans
treat their prisoners.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
You knew.
10 yards!
One o'clock, in the trees!
Sarge!
Sarge?
No one
respects your authority.
Everyone's against you.
Walsh is a spy.
They joined the enemy.
These things, they use
strike and retreat tactics.
They slink off into the forest
the first sign of gunfire,
only to come back for the
bodies once the coast is clear.
They're scavengers.
So bullets can hurt them then.
Rucker said he shot one of them.
Wake his ass up, we need
to know everything he does.
Rucker, wake up.
Rucker.
Where is he?
They're picking us off
one by one.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
Nah, we stay together,
all right?
We take the fight to them.
No more being hunted,
it's time we start hunting.
No.
Sergeant Brewer gave us
specific orders.
Sergeant Brewer's
lost his goddamn mind.
When do we start?
Right now.
Who's with me?
Fine.
Yeah.
Suit up.
A solar compass
consists of three arcs,
latitude, declination of sun
and time of day
to conduct accurate
land surveys,
providing one has the
current coordinates.
So, numbers on that recording,
what if they're not
so random after all?
I've been watching you guys.
Wanted to see if you
were really gonna leave.
Welcome to join us.
So you're in charge now, huh?
These men,
they're your men, Brewer.
They care about you.
Hey, Sarge.
We looked for you.
Then we waited.
Thought maybe the gas got you.
You're a terrible liar, Morgan.
That was our medic!
Wasn't there from the start.
An outsider.
He was a good man!
He was a traitor!
So are you, so are all of you!
Sarge, I'm sorry!
Hey asshole!
Olin!
Get back here!
Olin?
Olin!
Come back, Olin!
Where are you?
Olin, come here!
Olin!
Please, God.
I just wanna see her again.
Betty?
God listens.
It's impossible.
Do you remember our wedding day?
It was the best day of my life.
Do you take this woman
as your beloved wife
for the rest of
your natural life?
I do.
Can't fight this off,
go, go, go, go, go!
Shit ain't right, man.
♪ Hitler,
he's only got one ball ♪
♪ Goering's got two
but very small ♪
♪ Adolf ♪
Damn.
♪ God bless America ♪
♪ Land that I love ♪
♪ Stand beside ♪
♪ And guide ♪
♪ Through the night ♪
♪ From the mountains ♪
♪ Through the prairies ♪
Gone!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
It's Major Johnson,
do you copy?
This is Walsh, sir, over.
All right, Walsh,
use a solar compass.
I'll have the
coordinates for you.
Where are you going, sir?
I'm going to get my
boots a little dirty.
Wait a minute.
The windmill.
It was right here, we saw it.
We saw what they wanted
us to see, Freeman.
Just a illusion.
A projection of the real place.
Which is hidden under
a concealment spell.
Impossible to find unless
you have the right angle.
The right time.
And then...
It's gotta be right there.
There.
Walsh.
Walsh!
There.
There it is.
Come on.
Freeman, check upstairs.
The complete witch's archive.
The major was only ever able
to get his hands on volume one.
The Nazis got part two.
Last week one of our
operatives in Berlin
was able to smuggle out a
photographic copy of this.
So that's what was on the plane.
Uh-huh.
Come take a look at this.
It's Latin for warrior's blood.
Right here it says, "Oh tree
of life, quench thy thirst,
"'til flowers burst."
The witches, they were
killing the soldiers
to live forever.
Immortality.
It's real, Freeman.
If Hitler gets his
hands on this...
How do you fight an army
you can't even kill?
Three days ago, OSS
intercepted a transmission
sent by those Germans
we found in the woods,
announcing that they had
found the tree for the Fuhrer.
That was the real
mission, Freeman.
You knew what we
were up against,
and you didn't say a thing?
I couldn't jeopardize
- the mission.
- Most of the squad
is dead now because of you.
Hey, you need to calm down...
Hey, calm down.
Freeman, stop.
Easy, huh?
We good?
What the hell is that?
Wait.
They've been harvesting
warriors for centuries.
Tree of life.
Warrior's blood.
This is it, Freeman.
The tree of life the Fuhrer's
fantasized about for years.
Don't touch her.
Hey, Rucker, you put down
that gun there, buddy,
and I promise I'll get
us all out of here.
Jesus.
Only one problem
with that, Walsh.
I like it here.
She'll be back for me soon.
Look what she did to you.
The tree.
It's gonna heal me.
They promised me that.
No.
Rucker, they're lying to you.
They're just gonna feed you to
the tree like all the others.
Walsh, get up.
Walsh, tags, look.
- Walsh.
- Yeah.
Prepare the others.
You're up first, Freeman.
You knew we were
never going home.
God.
Let's do this.
Get up, son.
I was supposed to meet you
at the extraction point.
Where are the others?
They're all dead.
Collect the flowers,
let's get out of here.
Huh, mustard gas.
Killed 120,000 people
in World War One,
before it was banned.
Think it'll still work?
Well, I imagine we're
gonna find out soon.
Major, I'm gonna
get you out of here.
Torch the bitch, torch it.
Just torch it.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull