Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'm telling you, Addie,
if we build these factories
in San Miguel,
the business is going
through the roof.
I'd rather have you
than the money.
You're away too much, Slade,
and I...
You okay?
When you're home,
when we're all together,
I never even think about it.
But as soon as you're away, I...
For God's sake, Addie,
Cambodia was years ago.
Before we were even married.
We were in love.
We were engaged.
And we've both
seen enough combat
to know that however much
wounds may heal...
How could you do this to me?
I trusted you.
...the scars never go away.
Can I talk to him?
I know. I know.
And I swear to you, Addie,
I haven't lied to you since.
And I will never
lie to you again.
You believe me, don't you?
Of course I do.
- It's just...
- Can I talk?
Somebody wants you.
- I wonder who.
- Hi, Papa.
Hey, buddy. Teeth all brushed?
Yeah.
Read to me.
I would, Joe,
but I'm late for
a dinner meeting and...
Just a little.
A little little.
Hmm?
"The land
was filled with dragons"
and the people were afraid.
But the Shining Knight
came riding forth
to protect both man and maid.
He faced the fiercest creatures
that the world had ever known.
And he did it without any help.
He did it all alone.
And when his work was done,
the dragons were no more.
And so the Knight rode on,
"into legend, into lore."
And that's it for tonight, kid.
More. Please?
I've gotta go, buddy,
and you've gotta get to sleep.
Okay.
He misses you.
We miss you.
I'll be on the last plane
out tonight.
I love you, Adeline Wilson.
And I adore you, Slade Wilson.
Under the covers,
little soldier.
Aye-aye, Captain.
Read to me, Mama.
- But Papa already read you...
- Please?
Don't give me that wide-eyed
innocent routine, mister.
Please, Mama?
Not that one.
That's just for Papa.
You are clearly the commanding
officer in this family.
'Night, little soldier.
Good night, Mama.
No need to panic.
You'd be dead already
if I wanted it.
What do you want?
Your son.
If you were looking
for a helpless victim,
you came to the wrong house.
You're out of practice Adeline.
From what I've heard,
you were something to behold,
before marriage and motherhood
made you soft.
Leader of an elite squad within
the Green Berets called Team Seven.
You trained Slade Wilson.
Helped make him the killing
machine that he is today.
"Killing machine"?
He's a businessman.
Oh, Adeline,
there's so much you don't know.
Who the hell are you?
The Jackal.
Molina sent you.
El Presidente doesn't
like his generals plotting against him.
He finds revolution distasteful.
Then go ahead.
Cut my throat.
You'll never
get out of here alive.
Of course I will.
What is this?
The head of President Molina.
Note the look of surprise
on his face.
Very similar to
how you look right now.
I don't understand.
If Molina hired you
to assassinate me, then...
I'm a mercenary,
not an idiot.
Your president
was an oppressive fascist
who ground his people
into the dirt.
Under his rule,
San Miguel became a cesspool
of poverty, hunger and disease,
while he just grew richer
and fatter.
Do better, General Suarez.
Or this will be you.
And, oh, yes,
there is the little matter
of my fee.
Which I am delighted to pay.
Took a few hits, I see.
It's nothing.
Do you ever consider what would
happen to Adeline and Joseph
if you died on
one of these little jaunts?
You've been doing this for
what, eight years now? Nine?
Maybe it's time to stop being
a mercenary and start being...
I'll need transport
ASAP, Wintergreen.
And you will have it,
old friend.
The older I get,
the more I envy your ability to heal.
The Army certainly got
what they paid for.
And more.
It's not working, dammit!
- Will he live?
- Doesn't matter.
We've failed again.
They said...
They said it was a miracle
I'm still alive.
I told you not to volunteer
for that damn drug trial.
When they wouldn't even tell you
what it was for, I knew that...
It was my choice.
I could have said no.
Then why didn't you?
Because they needed me.
There were only a handful of
men that fit the profile...
And you've always been
a good soldier.
Maybe too good.
They'll be sending me home
in a few days.
And I'm going with you.
But your duties...
I've served my country.
And done a damn good job of it.
- But you need me now...
- No.
You've got another 14 months.
You do what you signed on to do.
Let me try to build
a life for myself, for us.
Then...
Then, if you still want me...
Why wouldn't I want you?
I love you, Slade.
We've got plans.
A whole life ahead of us.
The Army's the only life
I've ever known, Addie.
Being that good soldier.
Following orders.
Killing the enemy.
There's more to you than that.
I hope so.
Addie?
Dear God, what happened?
Where's Joseph?
He said if I called the police,
he'd kill him.
Who? Who did this?
Said it's you he wants.
Who did this?
The Jackal.
Who the hell is the Jackal?
You know who he is!
"I haven't lied to you since,"
you said,
"and I will never
lie to you again."
But it's all been
nothing but lies, hasn't it?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Stop!
The Jackal told me everything.
The Army thought
the experiment was a failure,
that their drug didn't work.
That's why they discharged you.
But it just took a little time
to turn you into...
What did he call you?
Deathstroke.
I'm a businessman.
That's what I always believed.
Slade Wilson, a good
and decent man,
who loved his wife and son,
who'd do anything
for his family.
But you're a goddamn mercenary.
Selling death
to the highest bidder,
and you hid it from me.
All these years.
Why?
I'll bring Joseph back.
And I'll bring the Jackal's
carcass back with me.
I don't need you.
We don't need you.
I can do this without you.
Broken, damn it.
In several places,
from the look of it.
Go.
When this is over, Addie,
we'll talk.
Don't even try
to lie to me again,
you manipulative son of a bitch.
Just bring Joseph home.
And God help you if you fail.
I never fail.
How's the wife,
Wilson?
Show yourself.
I'm right here.
My son...
Is fine.
Just a bargaining chip.
Accept the bargain
and he doesn't get hurt.
I won't work with H.I.V.E.
So you said
the last time I asked.
And I respect that.
Unfortunately,
my superiors don't.
They think your skills
would be of great value to us.
You're terrorists.
Equal opportunity murderers.
Selling our services
to the highest bidder,
just like you.
Only difference is
you're small-time.
H.I.V.E. thinks globally.
How many innocent people,
women and children
have died at your hands?
Honestly,
I've lost count.
But we're all murderers
under the skin, Wilson.
It's just a matter of scale.
Morality is delusion that fools
wear like a comforting cloak.
But you're no fool.
Are you?
A monster perhaps,
but not a fool.
Monster?
Yes, I kill for a living.
But only if the cause is right.
There are lines I won't cross.
I don't know
if the widows and children
of those soldiers you murdered
in San Miguel would agree.
We're the same.
Can't you see that?
Men like us pretend
to have hearts and souls.
But underneath that,
only darkness.
I...
The answer is no.
Reconsider.
Enough!
Enough.
You do realize
that you've proven my point.
She was
an extraordinary operative.
But clearly
not extraordinary enough.
Bronze Tiger's skills are legendary.
And look at him.
Give me my boy.
Give me your answer.
Will you join H.I.V.E.?
Or will my man slit little
Joseph's throat here and now?
Joseph, don't be afraid.
Joe.
Joseph!
You're not gonna die.
I swear to God
you're not gonna die.
Dear Joseph,
your mother thinks it's best
that I stay away for a while.
And I agree.
You see, I have a secret,
one I've never shared
with you before.
I'm a knight, like the ones
in our favorite book,
roaming a dangerous world.
Righting wrongs,
slaying dragons.
And I don't want those dragons
to hurt you, or your mom...
ever again.
That was a mistake.
Who sent you?
Does it matter?
I was paid a small fortune
to liberate what's
hidden away downstairs.
But frankly, Bora...
...I would have done this one
for free.
It's all right.
No one's gonna hurt you
ever again.
Hello, Wilson.
Or do you prefer "Deathstroke"?
Who the hell...
You can call me
the H.I.V.E. Queen.
H.I.V.E. is gone.
I spent years
making sure of that.
No, not gone, underground.
Regrouping.
Dozens of independent cells
scattered across the world.
And my little cell is very
interested in the Wilson family.
I turned H.I.V.E. down
ten years ago.
- And if you think...
- Don't flatter yourself.
You made it clear then
that you were a bad fit.
And really, why bother
with the father
when I have the son?
What?
Joseph?
You're a handgun, Slade.
Your boy, he's a nuclear bomb.
A bomb that belongs to me now.
What have you done to him?
Me? Don't you know?
You did this.
You didn't know.
More's the pity.
I chose that school in
Switzerland for the security.
You chose poorly.
Did you know?
That whatever the Army did to
alter your biology, your genetics,
was passed on to Joseph?
Of course not.
From what
that H.I.V.E. Queen said,
his abilities are
very different than mine.
Not physical in nature,
psychic.
What?
There were times when I'd...
feel him.
As if he was
in the room with me.
But I thought
I was just imagining it.
He should have been with you.
How could you just
send him away like that?
I did it to keep him safe.
I could have kept him safe.
The way you did last time?
When that animal cut his
throat and left him mute?
You punished me enough
for it, didn't you?
Locked me out of his life.
And you never
once questioned it.
Never once tried to see him.
Another man would have
fought me tooth and nail,
would have begged
to see his son.
But you? One pathetic letter,
and then you were gone forever.
Why?
I always seem to be
asking you that. Why?
The past is dead, Addie,
and nothing we do,
nothing we say, can change it.
But the past isn't dead, Slade.
It's happening all over again.
So what are we
going to do about it?
"We"?
You're not going after him
alone this time.
I'm going with you.
Do you remember
what the Jackal did to you?
Oh, I remember.
He broke me.
Humiliated me.
And it was my own fault.
I put so much energy
into being a mother,
being your wife,
that I lost my center.
Well, I've found it again.
You haven't been
on a combat mission in years.
Guess I'm just too rusty, huh?
Stay out of it, Adeline.
Slade. Slade.
Good luck.
It's a beautiful home,
Colonel Kapoor,
Built with H.I.V.E. money,
as I recall.
I stopped working for them years
ago, as you no doubt also recall.
You had no choice.
I destroyed them.
Or so I thought.
They're back?
And I want information
about one cell in particular,
led by a woman who calls
herself the H.I.V.E. Queen.
I closed the door
on that chapter of my life.
I've spoken to
close to a dozen former operatives
who all claim the same thing.
And?
Telling the truth,
as far as I know.
And?
Don't worry, Colonel,
I left them all intact.
Aside from Myshkin.
He was so afraid to even talk about
H.I.V.E. that he killed himself.
I was never in very deep,
Deathstroke, you know that.
As a colonel I could
provide a favor here and there.
For which you were
richly rewarded.
And the truth is,
I was relieved when you took them down.
I have a wife now. A family.
A little graft is one thing, but
getting involved with H.I.V.E. again...
No.
If you hear anything,
you contact me immediately.
I will.
This better be good, Kapoor.
Impressive.
This is a surprise.
Look at you.
Hero of the Kaznian revolution.
You know how it goes.
Southern Kaznians
take the capital.
A few years go by,
and then the north takes it.
Been going on for years.
I've worked for both sides.
They're very generous.
And children starve.
Innocents die.
Still singing the same song,
huh, Wilson?
The mercenary with a conscience.
The rest of us...
we're beneath you!
I didn't come here
to debate, Tiger.
Or to fight.
I came here for information.
If it's dope on H.I.V.E.
you want...
You have nothing
to do with them.
Didn't even know
they still existed.
Oh, I knew.
Once the Jackal took over.
Jackal? He's alive?
You should've made sure
he was dead.
That man has
a serious hate on for you.
After that mess with your kid,
Jackal decided that H.I.V.E.
needed reorganization.
New leadership.
So he stepped back.
And let
me wipe out his competition.
And then, very quietly,
put the pieces back together.
But I was tired
of taking orders.
Decided to freelance.
Worked out pretty well.
Again?
Son of a bitch.
You did it again.
Where can I find
the H.I.V.E Queen?
Fine.
The Kerguelen Islands.
Thank you.
That's my ride.
Don't bother.
Where he's headed,
there's no coming back.
Oh, shit.
So, how the hell did you get your
hands on an aircraft like this?
Somebody owed me a favor.
A very big one, apparently.
There's every chance
they know you're coming.
I'm counting on it.
You'll never change.
Having second thoughts,
Wintergreen?
On the contrary.
Since MI6 retired me,
the only fun I ever have is when you
invite me along on these little jaunts.
I'll be too old for this
soon enough.
Well, I'm probably
too old for it now,
but I'm not ready
for the nursing home just yet.
This one's no jaunt.
Joseph's life is at stake.
And what kind of
godfather would I be
if I wasn't helping you
bring him home?
In fact, I...
There they are.
The Kerguelens. Also known as
the Desolation Islands.
Aptly named, I think.
Best of luck, Slade.
I don't believe in luck.
But in this case, I'll take it.
I was expecting an army.
They don't need an army.
They've got me.
Sandra Wu San.
Also known as Lady Shiva.
There are people
who consider you
the deadliest hand-to-hand
combatant in the world.
And they would be right.
What are you doing?
Surrendering.
I do not accept your surrender.
Not tonight, Shiva.
I want him alive.
Bring him to me.
Yes, my Queen.
Up.
Surrender is a clever strategy.
Easier than fighting
your way into the fortress.
But it won't be
quite as easy getting out.
What?
You're just a child.
And you're a dinosaur
whose time has passed.
Let's cut the bullshit,
shall we?
Where's my boy? Where's Joseph.
Yes. Let's cut the bullshit.
Where is he?
Such concern.
And yet, you abandoned Joseph
without a second thought
just as his mother did.
Left him trapped, isolated,
friendless in that school.
His mind, his very soul,
on fire.
I didn't know.
Could it be...
you didn't want to?
So, he's what,
your little lab rat?
We're going to train him.
Help him master his powers.
You've got him
locked in a damn cage.
For his own protection.
His psychic energies
are still wildly unstable.
But his potential,
limitless.
- As a weapon.
- Yes.
Think of it.
Manipulation on a global scale
through the power of the mind.
Domination of the planet
with no bullets.
No bombs.
What country on Earth
could resist us?
Joseph? Joseph!
Joseph!
Don't be afraid.
Joe...
"Joseph" was the name
you gave him.
But I've given him a new name.
A better name.
Jericho.
Because, with my help,
he's going to bring the walls
of the old order tumbling down.
Be honest, Wilson.
You don't really care about him.
You never did.
This is just another
adventure to you.
Another chance to prove
your questionable manhood.
But here,
he'll find a home, a family.
Help me, Papa.
Get me out of here!
Please!
Get back, buddy.
No!
I can help.
Put me down.
- You're weak.
- I'm all right.
Joe.
I know a way out.
This will get us to the surface.
But I don't know what to do
once we're up there.
I've got that covered.
Wintergreen, it's time.
On my way, Slade.
That's all...
That's all I can...
Wintergreen.
Wintergreen?
Uncle William's not coming.
What?
I blocked the signal.
But I heard him.
You heard
what I wanted you to hear.
Joseph, why?
Did you really think
I would betray my own sister?
Sister?
The H.I.V.E. Queen, she's...
Your daughter.
You really didn't know?
Joseph, listen to me.
I came here...
Ride to the rescue
like a knight in shining armor?
Joseph. Joseph!
My name
is Jericho!
Joseph's gone.
Joseph!
Good-bye, Deathstroke.
Joseph.
Well done, boy. Well done.
Dark.
Stillness.
Peace.
Oblivion.
Is it such a terrible thing
to embrace the void,
surrender to the silence,
die?
But I can't die now.
One day, maybe soon.
But not yet.
Joseph needs me.
My son needs me.
And I...
have...
to live!
Easy. Easy.
How am I even alive?
You almost weren't.
If I hadn't
fished you out in time...
Addie?
You may have an incredible
ability to heal, Slade.
But you're not immortal.
And one of these days,
you won't be coming back.
Told you I wasn't gonna
let you do this alone.
Where are we?
On a boat.
Far enough away
from that damn island.
How did...
How did you find me?
I've been on you the whole time.
Used a nano-tracker that I
procured from an old friend.
Tiny GPS device that lodged
into your intestinal tract.
- But how did...
- Sealed with a kiss.
You implanted it
with your tongue?
And here I thought
I'd won your heart again.
It's got a limited shelf life.
Should dissolve
in another few days.
Drink this.
A mix of herbs that should help
speed up your natural healing.
Ugh.
Drink it, tough guy.
Ah...
Wait.
You said you got your tracker
from an old friend.
Wintergreen.
You two have been conspiring?
Not conspiring,
just sharing information
and resources.
When I see that old man...
If you're going to be angry
at someone, try yourself.
You've made some terrible
choices in your life, Slade.
And the people you love,
that you claim to love,
have paid a terrible price.
So he's dead?
The sharks have made
a meal of him by now.
You must feel a profound sense
of satisfaction, Rose.
I wish I did.
I've wanted this for so long,
but now that I have it...
Let it go, child.
You've done well.
Made me proud.
Now let's move on
with our plans.
We need more time.
Jericho is not ready.
You'll make sure he's ready,
won't you?
- But...
- Won't you?
Yes.
I have faith in you, Rose.
I've always had faith in you.
Since the day we met
and I rescued you
from a hellish existence.
It wasn't all hell.
My mother,
she loved me.
Yes, she did.
After Wilson abandoned her.
Left her pregnant and alone,
she sacrificed everything
to build a good life for you.
And perhaps,
it would have been good...
...had she lived.
And you were left alone.
And Wilson,
did he ever look back
and wonder?
If he'd bothered,
he might have discovered
that he had a daughter
living on the streets
of Phnom Penh.
But your father
did leave you one legacy.
He passed his altered genetics
on to you.
Speed,
stamina,
heightened strength...
What a gift.
It was a curse.
I suppose it was at first.
But then...
I found you.
Took you under my wing,
trained you,
became the father you never had.
Made you a queen.
And now, you'll make
your brother a king.
And together...
We'll rule the world?
No. We'll rule the rulers.
So much better that way.
Project Jericho launches
in ten days, Rose.
I have my final preparations
to see to and you have yours.
Be ready.
Will I see you then?
It's been more than a year.
You know I have to
remain in seclusion.
No one can know
where the H.I.V.E. Lord is.
Not even you.
But this, child,
I wouldn't miss for the world.
You okay?
I am now.
I didn't know
Lillian was pregnant.
She never told me.
- If I had known...
- You would've been the father to that girl
that you were to Joseph?
Years ago, when you told me
about Lillian,
you said she didn't mean
anything to you.
Was that true?
She didn't.
Not like you, Addie.
But?
After I realized
what had happened to me...
what the army
had turned me into, I felt...
lost.
Untethered.
I needed time
to sort through things.
So, I travelled. Looking for...
Something I couldn't give you?
I don't know.
Maybe it was easier
turning to a stranger.
Lillian was a good woman.
Sweet. Kind.
So you did care about her.
Yes. But not like...
And just left her,
pregnant and alone.
I didn't know about the child.
Would you rather I'd stayed
with her and not...
I'd rather
it had never happened.
It sounds funny, I know.
But my affair with Lillian,
it's what made me realize
that you were the only one.
That no other woman could...
I'm not laughing.
I didn't mean it like that.
What did you mean?
Addie, I...
Doesn't matter now, does it?
No.
Not when you
destroyed our family,
and another one
you didn't even know you had.
That's your forte, isn't it?
Destruction.
If you feel that way,
then why the hell are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping Joseph.
And once this is done,
so are we.
We did
the right thing, didn't we?
Yes.
Of course, we did.
He was a monster.
He had to die.
He was a knight once.
What?
Nothing.
I know a part of you
still loves them.
You can't help it.
But Slade Wilson
never gave a damn about you.
His entire life was a lie.
And your mother,
if she really loved you,
would she have locked
you away in that school,
left you there to rot?
Would she?
No.
We were both so alone, Jericho.
So alone.
But we found each other,
didn't we?
I guess we can thank
Deathstroke for that much.
Years before we ever met,
your mind reached out,
found me.
We knew each other,
shared each other's thoughts,
feelings, all our hopes,
all our sorrows.
When this...
this power inside me came alive,
I was so scared, Rose.
I thought it was
going to burn me up,
tear me apart.
But then, I felt something.
Like...
Like the echo of my own soul.
Me.
You.
I think I would have died
without you.
And I would have died
You see, Jericho,
you don't need
a mother or a father...
when you have me.
And what about the man
who calls himself your father?
What about the Jackal?
Wintergreen, you there?
Always.
Hey, what about the boat?
I stole it, anyway.
Bring them in.
Thank you, agents,
for volunteering.
But we didn't volun...
Agent Sanchez, step forward.
On your knees.
Now her.
Your weapon.
This is nothing
compared to what's coming.
And if you can't do this,
all our plans are for nothing.
All right.
Shoot him.
I can't.
Why'd you stop?
It worked, didn't it?
She would've killed him
on my command.
Why lose a perfectly good agent?
Fine.
Then let's have a show,
shall we?
That's enough, Jericho.
That's enough.
Jericho, stop!
Stop!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I'm sorry, Rose.
I don't know what happened!
I couldn't control it! I...
Shh! It's my fault.
I pushed you too far. Too fast.
We'll go
a little slower tonight.
Tonight? But, can't we...
Tomorrow, then.
And no more excuses.
How did you get this?
While you were blundering
into the H.I.V.E. Queen's trap,
I was hacking
into their servers.
Jericho.
That's what she called Joseph.
They're turning our son
into a weapon of war.
Remember what she said?
I'm a handgun, but Joseph's...
A nuclear bomb.
But not in the way you think.
Those exercises are to help him
master his abilities, focus them.
But the goal?
A revolution from within.
Imagine if you
controlled someone
who could control
the minds of others.
Presidents, prime ministers,
despots, kings.
Mind-theft on a global scale.
You could reshape the planet
without firing a single shot.
And we've got ten days to figure
out what their first move is.
And it's all because of her.
She used Joseph.
Manipulated him.
You can do this.
I know you're scared, Jericho,
but I believe in you.
As long as we have
each other, little brother,
there's nothing
we can't accomplish.
We're two parts of a whole.
I'll never leave you.
Never abandon you
the way they did.
We're family.
Is that manipulation or love?
Thanks, Addie.
I'll take it from here.
The hell you will!
You don't get to decide
what I do or don't do.
You've risked enough.
This is my job.
I lived with risk every
damn day we were married,
only, I never knew it,
did I, Deathstroke?
You never told me.
Please, can we stop
dredging up the past?
You know there's something else
you never told me.
Why?
Why did you choose
Deathstroke over us?
A life of deceit and risk,
instead of...
I didn't choose to be
one over the other, Addie.
And I didn't choose to be this.
There's always a choice.
Those bastards made me this way
with their damned experiment.
And I did the best
I could with it.
That was your best?
A mercenary? A murderer?
My father was a soldier.
His father was a soldier.
All I knew
was the military life.
So I took that training and...
Corrupted it. Spit on it.
This world is filled with evil.
On a scale you can't comprehend.
Oh, I have some idea.
Then you should understand that I just
did what we did when we served together.
Took down the bad guys.
Don't you dare compare the two.
I...
I tried to be the knight
Joseph believed I was.
A knight?
Is that what you think you are?
Oh, my God, Slade,
are you that delusional?
Joseph didn't need a knight.
He needed a father.
I needed a husband.
What's so wrong inside you that
you preferred Deathstroke to us?
My life as Deathstroke,
it was separate
from my life with you.
It had nothing to do with...
You really don't see it?
All these years
you've been compartmentalizing.
Filing pieces of yourself
away in little boxes.
Lying to yourself.
And to me.
Thank you.
For what?
For reminding me why I've chosen to
remain a bachelor all these years.
Now, are you two going to spend
the day at each other's throats,
or are we going to save Joseph,
and perhaps the world?
The nation
has been rocked this morning
by what appear to be a series of
coordinated terrorist attacks.
Moments after a hijacked
Patriot Airlines flight
was deliberately crashed
into the Golden Gate Bridge,
a dozen armed men launched a mass
attack in New York Times Square.
While in Washington,
at least one bomb,
possibly more,
tore through
the Capitol Building.
No estimates yet
on total casualties,
but it's clear that hundreds of
lives have been lost, perhaps more.
The president, just returning from
the World Economic Forum in Davos,
remains aboard Air Force One,
while all other flights across
the nation have been grounded.
God damn it!
I look like a weak fool,
circling around up here,
afraid to land.
It has nothing to
do with fear, sir.
It's for your safety.
Until we know the full
extent of the attacks...
The nation needs
to be reassured!
And the commander-in-chief
needs to be protected.
Eerie, isn't it?
We're the only plane in the sky.
At least, we're supposed to be.
Our attacks were
the perfect distraction.
The entire country is in chaos.
People are hiding away
in their little holes
like the frightened rabbits
they are.
And there he sits, all alone.
A fat, ripe fruit,
ready for the picking.
Without you, child,
none of this would be possible.
If I've pleased you, sir,
then...
You've more than pleased me.
You've given me the world.
Are you ready, son?
I... I think so.
You think?
I am, sir.
We'll swarm them.
Confuse and terrify them.
And when they're close enough,
you'll use
your astonishing gift.
And our little puppet
will return to Washington.
Declare martial law.
The most powerful nation on Earth
will be in H.I.V.E.'s control and...
And we
will be in control of H.I.V.E.
What?
Now, Jericho!
Rose?
I've waited a long time
for this.
You trained him well.
Better than I knew.
And all of this for what?
Vengeance?
A righteous killing?
You manipulated me from the first
moment you stepped into my life.
Did you think I didn't know
what you were even then?
I was a father to you.
I trained you.
Helped you master those powers.
A father?
You used a lonely,
grief-stricken girl.
But I wasn't as alone
as you believed.
I had my brother, in here.
Long before I ever
told you about him.
And I knew what you did to him.
I made you a queen.
And now that queen
is taking your throne.
H.I.V.E. won't use us again.
No one will ever use us,
hurt us, again.
We have the power.
And what will you do
with all that power, Rose?
I'll start by making you pay
for what you did.
But not with your life.
With your mind.
Take him! Become him!
Did you really think
I'd unleash a weapon like you
without providing
myself protection?
Took my best technicians eight months
to come up with psychic dampers
capable of absorbing
your psionic powers,
and hurling them back
in your astonished face.
You knew?
I suspected.
After all, a guttersnipe
like you can't be trusted.
Jericho.
Jericho?
You should know, Rose,
that family will always disappoint you.
Denied the president's mind,
we'll have to take his body.
I enjoy a good old-fashioned
kidnapping, don't you?
Initiate Plan Jericho Two.
On my...
Sir, another plane, heading our way.
Who the hell could it...
Deathstroke.
We warned them.
Why didn't they listen?
By the time our contacts got through to
the people who could make a difference,
it was just too late.
But we'll damn sure
make a difference here.
These energy readings
are extraordinary.
It's got to be Joseph.
He's in the lead plane.
You gonna be okay
all alone, Grandpa?
Oy, behave yourself.
Have you looked in the mirror
lately, you old bag of wind?
I've got this, Slade.
You always do.
You're not talking me
out of this.
I wouldn't dream of it.
You're the finest commanding
officer I've ever served under.
And you get extra points
since I've seen you naked.
Fuck you.
How did they know?
They're here now.
And maybe that's for the best.
Wilson's brats may have betrayed
me and ruined my careful planning.
But now their father
can have a front-row seat
when his children die.
What's happening?
Kill them.
Bravo, Rose.
Bravo.
Not bad for an old dog.
No! No, no, no!
Air Force
One, prepare to be boarded.
You just saved the President
of the United States.
Damn right I did.
It appears we were expected.
Joseph!
So, tell me, Wilson.
Which one do I murder first?
The girl whose mother
you used for your own pleasure
and then so casually threw away?
Or the boy
you so easily abandoned?
Spare me the litany
of my sins, Jackal.
I know them well enough.
Of course. You're not
the only sinner here.
Take our dear friend Rose,
for instance.
She's been manipulating
her brother for years.
Poisoning his mind
against you and Adeline.
Making sure
his only loyalty was to her.
I told him the truth.
I love Jericho.
And what's love but another
way to control people?
No.
What you did to him was no
different from what I did to you.
No.
God, no!
It's not the same, Rose.
You're not the same.
But I did use him. I...
I didn't mean to, but I did.
Just because love isn't perfect,
doesn't mean it isn't real.
You were there for him,
when I wasn't.
Not for him.
Not for you.
Hardly the time or
place for family therapy.
Let them go.
Say "please."
Please.
They've suffered enough.
Then I'll end their suffering.
You fucking monster.
I told you years ago, Wilson.
We're two of a kind.
Get the hell away from my kids!
I've performed several
major upgrades to this armor
since our last battle.
And, now,
I'm unstoppable!
Not bad.
Thank you.
We've got to help him.
Jericho.
Jericho. Joseph.
I'm so sorry.
- I never meant to-
- I know. I...
Mom?
Hey, little soldier.
All these years, Jackal...
Why? Why me?
Why my children?
Do you think you were the only
man to ever have a daughter?
She was your...
Yes, she was!
And now, I'll take from you
what you took from me.
No!
Slade!
You were right, Addie.
All these years I've been filing
pieces of myself away in little boxes.
Lying to myself.
And to you.
It was the only way
I knew how to survive.
I'm not a knight, my love.
I never was.
But maybe now I can be
the man you always needed.
- Can you?
- I can try.
How long can you keep it there?
As long as I have to.
I'm not losing you again.
I'll get us down fast.
Wintergreen,
can you see them?
No, I...
Wait! There!
You get to ground.
I'll try to reach Slade.
This has been fun, Wilson.
But it's time to
say our good-byes.
This isn't gonna
end well for you.
Not for you either, asshole.
What?
Joseph, I love you.
Slade!
Papa!
"The land was filled with
dragons and the people were afraid."
But the Shining Knight
came riding forth
to protect both man and maid.
He faced the fiercest creatures
that the world had ever known.
And he did it all to save us.
"For the knight was not alone."
Oh, how he loved reading
that book to you.
That...
That was a long time ago.
The past is dead.
He needs time.
We all need time.
Do you think he survived?
Not even he could
have survived that.
I'll be leaving tomorrow.
And going where?
You stay as long as you need to.
We're family now.
Dysfunctional as
hell, but we're family.
"The land was filled
with dragons,"
and the people were afraid.
But the Shining Knight
came riding forth
to protect both man and maid.
He faced the fiercest creatures
that the world had ever known.
And he did it all to save us.
For the Knight was not alone.
And when his work was done,
the dragons were no more.
And so the Knight rode on
into legend,
"into lore."
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org