Where's our money?
Where's our fucking coke?
Guys.
Where's our fucking money?
Let me see.
Your heart's racing.
Huh?
Mine is too.
See?
It's okay. Hm?
Where's Freddy?
Ten-fifty-seven,
shots fired. Shots fired.
Proceed with caution.
All available units,
car 31.
Ah, this is Unit 13,
please send location.
Sending location.
Suspect is a Caucasian male
on foot and possibly armed.
Proceed with caution.
Ten-four,
Caucasian male,
approximately 170 pounds.
Armed and very dangerous.
Shots fired.
Traveling on foot.
Five out.
Copy.
Come on.
Watch it, bro.
Yeah, you walk in here.
Whoa, whoa.
No. Got your ticket?
I'll just give you money.
No, you don't.
Get your ticket right there.
No, I...
I'm almost outta minutes.
Don't worry. It's fine.
I... I'm almost.
Five-oh-five to Cairo, Georgia.
First stop, Lake City, Florida,
then Valdosta.
Then on to Cairo
like the Cairo, Georgia.
Last stop, Cairo, Georgia.
Hey! Hey!
Answer it.
Hey. Ask him where he is.
That's it.
No, no, no. Fuck.
Okay! Okay!
Freddy?
Where the fuck are you?
I heard shots, man!
Are you bailing on us?
Man, they were shooting!
I had to fucking bounce, man!
Where's Mac?
What do you mean where's Mac?
Mac's with you, bro.
No, he is not with me.
Where is he?
Fuck, man.
Shit!
Turn around and go pick him up.
Fuck that, man. I'm not
going back. You fuckin' crazy?
- We have to find him.
- I can't go back, Freddy.
I'm not built like you, man.
I'm fucking scared, man.
You were parked
down the street, man.
If they didn't see you,
then they didn't see you.
You're paranoid. Turn around.
Fuck you, dude!
I fucking can't do it, man.
This is fucked, bro.
Hey.
I need to use your phone.
No.
I gotta make a quick phone call.
No!
I can't fucking do it, man.
I'm freaking the fuck out.
Listen to me.
Everything is fine.
Just go find Mac.
All right?
Fuck, Freddy.
Find him.
All right, I got you.
7675.
The NFL season begins tonight
with.
Oh, come on, J.J., pick up.
You got two phones.
Yeah. Now leave me
the fuck alone.
Hello?
Chrissy, it's me.
It's Freddy.
What do you want?
I need to see you tonight.
Leave me alone, Freddy.
I'm on the ward,
I got 30 patients on my ward.
I don't need this shit.
Please, I need to see you.
- It's important.
- What are you calling me on?
- It's a burner.
- You're calling me from a burner?
It's the only way
I knew you'd answer.
Go fuck yourself!
Ple...
Fuck.
- Yeah?
- I found Mac.
Okay, good.
Put him on the phone.
He's dead, man.
- They dumped him on the street.
- What?
They dumped him on the street,
bro.
They shot him in the head, man.
- He's dead!
- We got a white male...
You said this was gonna
turn out clean, man.
Fuck!
Um...
Ah, fuck.
We're fucked, dude.
Game's up, man.
I gotta think, man.
I gotta think.
Freddy, don't hang up!
Freddy, don't hang up...
I gotta think.
Fuck!
Yo, what you looking at, bro?
What the fuck
you looking at?
You and me, it's over.
You need to come back.
You made a big mistake.
Do not fuck with me.
Fuck you!
I'm doing this for Lily.
Pick up.
Please don't hang up.
I told you I'm working.
I got to give you something.
What you wanna give me
that you ain't
already taken, Freddy?
Look, I'm in trouble.
I fucked up.
I fucked up bad.
So what? I ain't your mama.
You want one?
Run home to Vic like you always
do cause I ain't interested.
Neither is Lily.
Don't you hang up on me
like that again, man.
All right. All right.
Freddy, what's the plan, man?
I don't know.
Lake City bus station.
You got to meet me
there right now.
I got to make more stuff.
Okay?
Fuck, man.
- Shit!
- What?
I think
somebody's following me, man.
- What?
- Yeah.
I got this fucking car
up my ass, man.
It's on me, man. I know it.
Is it the Puerto Ricans?
I think it's Vic's.
Bro, I know it, man.
They're on me.
No, no, man. No.
No one followed us, dude.
You're being paranoid.
Fuck, fuck. Listen to me, man.
I'm telling you. They're on me.
Take a couple rights.
See if they follow you
and call me back.
Got it.
Lily?
Yo, man.
Hey, what the fuck?
Who's Lily?
What?
You said Lily.
Stop playing with me, man.
But you a play ah though, right?
I mean, only playahs
got two phones.
How old are you?
Twenty-one.
Twenty-one, my ass.
They following you?
They turned off somewhere.
Oh, good.
Good.
Fuck,
Freddy, I can't do this shit.
Man, I can't pick you up, man.
- What?
- It's fucked, man.
It wasn't supposed to
go down this way, man.
J.J., shut the...
shut the fuck up.
Meet me at the Lake City
bus station, goddammit.
All right?
Freddy, goddammit.
What's the point without Mac?
Mac is fucking dead, man.
It's just me and you.
We good?
Yeah, good, man.
Don't answer the phone
from nobody.
Don't fuckin' stop.
Just get to the station,
all right?
All right, man. I'm chill.
I got you.
All right. Fuck.
Freddy?
No, J.J.
He's on the 95 downtown.
Get him and bring him here.
Okay.
You piss yourself or something?
I call my boo?
I'm not giving you
my fucking phone.
- Fuck!
- Hey! You mind?
I'm trying to get
some shut-eye here.
I'm sorry.
See, you're
pissing everybody off.
Stop asking me for my phone.
I'm not giving it to you.
It's an emergency.
Mm. You know what?
Make it quick.
Pick up. Pick up.
Pick up.
Hi, S... Smokie.
Yeah. Hi.
No, I just...
I had... had to borrow one.
No. I... I told... I told you
mine was... mine...
Mine was tapped out.
Just some guy.
No, no!
He's not my friend.
Just.
Just... just... just.
No.
Of course not.
I had to.
I'm coming.
I'm gonna be safe.
Mm-hm.
Okay. Yeah, I'm alone.
Yeah. I'm alone.
Mm-hm.
Yeah.
You are fucked up.
Mm-hm. No one.
No. It's me.
No one knows.
No one knows, okay?
Yeah.
Phone.
I gotta go. I gotta go.
Where you going?
What?
You said, "No one knows."
No one knows what?
Fuck you care?
You ever meet this guy before?
Why you in my business?
How old are you?
Really.
I'm 17.
Hm.
Fuck you, man.
Pick up. Pick up.
J.J.,
where the fuck are you, man?
I'm right behind you.
I don't see you.
Hurry the fuck up!
I said
I'll meet you at Lake City, man.
Get the fuck out the road.
I'm passing you now.
Get to move. Move!
Fuck, yeah.
Freddy,
I'm almost at Lake City, bro.
Hey, remember
that guy that patched up Reggie
after he got shot by the cop?
The vet?
- The what?
- The dog guy, man.
The veterinarian.
You know where he's at?
No. I'll have to call Reg.
Why?
You're gonna have to take me
to go see him
after you pick me up.
Yo, did you get shot?
It's just a scratch.
Then why you going to a vet?
If it was serious,
I'd go to the hospital.
Fuck you!
But then you'd go to jail!
Just find the
fucking number, J.J.
Fuck!
All right. All right.
All right.
I'll call Reggie now.
Fuck.
Lake City, Florida coming up.
Anybody for Lake City, Florida?
Yo.
What's his name?
The dude you're going to meet.
Smokie.
What's his real name?
You don't know his real name?
You know what he looks like?
Now answer this question
honestly.
How old are you?
Why do you keep asking me that?
Does he know how old you are?
Smokie?
What'd you tell him?
Twenty-one?
He knows how old I am.
Your parents know where you are?
Freddy? I'm here, man.
I got that vet's number.
What bus are you on?
I just pulled up. Hold tight.
All right.
Lake City, folks.
Anyone for Lake City?
Take care of yourself.
Like you give a shit.
Move, dumb-ass.
Dumbass.
Fuckers.
Fuck.
Son of a bitch.
On or off?
You sick or something?
Like you give a shit.
Next stop's gonna be Valdosta.
Where is he?
Where's Freddy, J.J.?
I haven't see him.
Lie! It's a lie.
Call Coco.
We got J.J.
Good. Hurry up then.
In Lake City.
Hm.
Next stop, Valdosta.
Valdosta.
Who is it?
It's Freddy.
You still in Valdosta?
Yeah.
So what?
I need some help.
I'm busy.
I just need
a ride somewhere, man.
Get a cab.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because I'm in trouble.
Please.
Please who?
What?
Just say it.
Fuck you, I...
Damn.
You are fucked up.
Fuck.
Stop. Fucking. Calling. Me.
Chrissy, I got money.
Jesus.
It's for Lily. Please.
Hah. You missed
13 years of payments,
you wanna be a daddy now?
I can pay it all back right now.
So now you wanna play grownups.
Where'd you get it?
That's not important.
You stole it.
Didn't you?
I'm shot. I've been shot.
There's a fucking bullet
in my stomach, Chrissy.
Please.
I'm fucking begging you, please.
Fuck, I'm scared, Christine.
What do you want me to do, huh?
Go ask Vic.
That whore.
Fuck.
It's a parole violation for me
to associate with known felons.
Look, I just need a ride
to the hospital.
I can't drive you.
I lost my license.
Even if I wanted
to help you I can't.
Anything else?
Don't hang up.
Then say it.
Dad.
Don't hang up, Dad.
Now, see?
That wasn't so hard now, was it?
So you're in trouble, huh?
I've been shot.
Hm.
You don't sound shot.
I got some money, too.
Hm. Is that why you're shot?
Yeah.
Who'd you knock off? Vic?
Oh, man.
You are once special kinda
fuck up, you know that?
So I guess I'm the only one
that can help you, am I right?
Are you still in Valdosta?
You already asked me that.
Well, are you?
Fuck. Pft.
So fucking.
Holy shit!
Chrissy.
When?
When were you shot?
About an hour ago.
Is there an exit wound?
I don't think so.
Jesus. How much blood
have you lost?
A lot.
What's a lot?
I don't know. A pint?
You need a hospital.
I can't.
I can't do that.
Where are you?
I'm on a bus to Cairo.
Look, my hospital's not far
from there.
- Can... can you get a cab?
- I need the chart.
I need you to get all the files.
Shit.
- How long do I got before I bleed out?
- I can't tell over the phone.
Morgan, I need that chart ASAP!
Yeah, coming, Doctor.
Freddy,
I can't make a diagnosis...
Pressure's dropping.
...but if you've
lost a pint of blood.
Nurse, get that chart!
Morgan! You dropped the ball.
Look, just get to the hospital.
I'll treat you in my car
in the parking lot,
that way we won't have to
register you.
But if you need surgery.
You know what? I don't.
Okay.
You need to stop the bleeding.
Direct pressure
is how you do that.
You need to get
a cloth or something absorbent.
I gotta go.
Just get to the hospital
and make sure
you don't pass out.
Hey.
Do you have a pad?
Like a... like a tampon?
What?
Please.
Oh, shit.
[Freddy Thank you.
You got sliced?
Shot.
You a gangster?
Yep.
Don't tell no one.
Well, if you a
gangster, why are you on a bus?
Wasn't my intention initially.
What'd you do?
I took something
that doesn't belong to me.
Can I use your phone then?
Why?
So you can call that guy?
Yeah. So what?
Fine.
Take it.
Don't pass out.
You pass out,
we ain't waking back up.
Hi.
What do you want, man?
Do you know that girl?
What?
She's just a kid, dude.
Whoa.
You got the wrong idea,
my friend.
I hope so.
Are you a cop?
That's a guilty thing to ask.
My name's Will.
I work in Social Services.
You don't look
like a social worker.
Well, we come
in all shapes and sizes.
Why the fuck
is a social worker taking a bus?
Is that a real question
you want an answer to?
Look, man,
she asked to borrow my phone.
I gave it to her.
I ain't bothering her.
Hm.
Are we gonna have a problem?
No. No problem.
I had to check.
I checked.
Hello?
She remind you of someone?
Yup.
There goes another little girl
your sorry ass let down.
You're making a habit of this.
Hey, pst, what's the plan?
The plan, the plan, the plan.
Come on, man.
Lily.
Bingo.
Get you patched up,
we'll stick to the plan.
It's just you and me now.
You and me.
Freddy?
Freddy, you there?
You won't believe what the fuck
happened to me, man.
So I got to Lake City,
these motherfuckers straight up
jumped my ass, bro.
Yeah? So what'd you do?
They had knuckles up, bro.
I got away.
Are you still on the bus, man,
or d... did you get off?
Talk to me, man.
Yeah, I'm still on the bus.
I'mma come get you.
When's your next stop?
Fifteen minutes.
Where you gonna be at?
Pine Park.
Pine Park. All right, cool.
Sit tight, man.
I'm gonna come get you.
Please.
I'm gonna be real gentle.
Chrissy, I'm seeing shit.
Visions. Fucked-up shit.
You're becoming catatonic,
probably going into shock.
You said I needed blood.
Like a transfusion?
Can you get it?
You're a rare blood type.
That's a long shot.
What are my chances?
I'd call your father.
I already did that.
If you weren't shot,
would you have called me?
I told you why I called you.
Why now?
Because I'm going away.
This is it.
You're always
running away, Freddy.
The fuck.
There he is.
I need a transfusion.
You want my blood?
I'll pay you for it.
I know you'll pay me.
It ain't that. I hate needles.
I'm fuckin' dying here, man!
Are you gonna help me or not?
Phone.
Phone!
I told you I'm not
doing nothing, man.
I know. I know.
Then what do you want?
Look, I can see
you're in some kind of trouble
Back the fuck off, man.
Hey, is she in trouble?
Is she running away? What?
You okay?
She's hooking up with some guy
she met online named Smokie.
That's all I know.
Smokie.
Guess his last name's
The Bear or Robinson.
I'm pretty sure
that's not his real name.
How the hell would I know that?
I can help her.
Then why are you talking to me?
Because I see she trusts you.
I'm a stranger to her.
Sometimes these kids,
they run the other way
once they find
you're social services.
But you could sway her.
You could get her to talk to me
so I could help her.
God, I don't have time for that.
You're on a bus.
What else you got to do?
- I gotta take this.
- Hey.
We gotta do somethin', man.
She's just a kid.
You do something.
I gotta take this.
Just talk to her.
I already have.
Then tell her
not to meet that guy.
Come on, man.
Okay, how about this?
Okay, I'll call my office.
I'll tell them to come pick us
up wherever she gets off.
Make sure she gets home safe...
All right. All right, man.
I'll talk to her.
Good.
J.J.
You're not going to Pines Park.
You stole from me. Freddy.
You put my whole crew
on the line.
Where's J.J.?
I'm gonna have
to prove to the Puerto Ricans
that I had no hand in this.
Let me talk to him.
I was warned not to trust you
with a shipment this size.
Put J.J. on the phone.
Okay.
Freddy, Freddy, man.
I... I didn't say anything, man.
J.J., everything's cool, man.
It's all good.
This is shit.
Okay.
We can make this right.
Do you have the coke?
Yeah.
And the money?
All of it?
All of it.
Okay, I'm gonna need to see you.
Where you headed?
I know you're hurting, okay?
I got a doctor lined up.
We'll get you fixed up.
Vic.
I know, baby,
but they want blood.
And they already got Mac.
Please. Oh, my god.
But Mac's not enough.
You're right.
Mac won't be enough.
Please!
- No.
- Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the
fruit of thy womb, Jesus
Oh, god, Vic, please.
Pray for us sinners now,
and at the hour of our death.
Our Father who art in heaven...
Jesus, stop.
Vic, stop. Please.
And lead us not into temptation
but deliver us.
J.J. Stop, Vic. Please.
Fuck.
Okay. We're all good now.
You can come
back to the fold, baby.
Everything can be healthy again.
Or I could pay Christine
and Lily a visit.
Save yourself
a heart attack, man.
God. Fuck.
Mm. Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck.
It's fine.
You just stabbed your employer
in the back twice.
You fucked up.
Get on it, goddammit!
Get the money
to Christine and Lily.
Fuck.
Lily?
Do you know that girl?
She's just a kid, dude.
Lily?
Hey, do you mind?
I'm trying to get
some shut-eye here.
What the fuck, dude?
I got us a ride.
Let's do this fucking thing.
What changed?
Nothing changed.
Meet me at the
bus station in Valdosta.
What time do you get in?
Any minute.
I know this guy at the bar,
and he's gonna get us
where we need to go.
Some guy in a bar is gonna
drive us fucking?
What do you want,
a fucking horse and carriage?
You still got the money?
Yeah, I still got it.
Five minutes.
Valdosta, comin' up.
Anybody for Valdosta?
I don't want you
to meet that guy.
I'm serious.
Why are you trying to
give me shit on my life?
Just don't meet him.
You trippin'.
Look.
I've been in your position
before.
Someone older gets in your head,
takes advantage of you.
It's messed up.
I want you to do
something for me.
See that man over there?
I want you to talk to him.
He's gonna help you.
I don't need help.
Just hear him out, okay?
Damn.
Where's your guy?
He ain't here yet.
Step off and let's wait.
Said your guy from
the bar is gonna drive us.
Where's your guy?
He's on his way.
Now get off and we'll wait.
On or off, son?
We gonna keep having this dance?
I ain't waiting out there.
You can't wait
five fucking minutes?
All right, I'll get on with you.
I'll tell my guy to meet us
at the next stop.
Get your ticket at the station.
What?
You get your ticket
in the station.
Like everybody else.
I gotta get
my ticket in the station,
just like everybody else.
Go ahead.
Much obliged.
Hey, miss me that much?
Put your headphones on.
Who's this?
Nobody.
She's cute.
You sure ain't.
So where'd you get clipped?
That's gotta hurt.
Hey, forget Valdosta.
Cairo.
Cairo. Get that? Mm-hm.
All right.
Okay.
So where's my guy taking us?
Hm?
Christine is going to meet us
in the parking lot
where she works.
Hm. You and her still a thing?
She's just doing me a favor.
Well, she's too good for you.
Always came running back.
Some chicks never learn
that the guys they're with
are bad fuckin' news.
I guess Mom did.
Psst. Hey.
Cream pie.
Where you going?
What?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm just talking to her.
How old are you anyway?
Take a guess.
Um, let's see.
Stop bothering us.
What do you...?
He was talking to me.
Now he ain't,
so just turn around.
What the fuck.
So you pinch that
from Vic or what?
Tell me what the fuck
you got me into or I'm out.
What the fuck
did you get me into?
It's Vic's.
How much?
Enough.
Well, that's
a ballsy move, my friend.
One you never made.
Mm-hm.
Why'd you take her shit?
I needed out.
Out? From what?
From her.
From all of this.
I'm just gonna start
something of my own.
And... and...
And what?
And there's something
for my daughter.
Hm. Yeah. Oh, shit.
The last time I saw her
was at... I don't know.
Don't act like you remember.
How old is Lily now, huh?
She's 11.
Hm. Eleven.
Goddamn.
You want to give her a future.
I get it, son.
I get it. I do. That's...
That's... that's noble on you.
Shit, half a mill.
That'll do it, am I right?
What did you just say?
I don't know.
You told me how much.
I didn't tell you shit.
Well then,
how else would I know?
You called her.
You called Vic.
You piece of shit.
You told her where we're going.
Let go, son. Let go..
Let the fuck go.
Okay.
Who oh.
We're just gonna sit here
quietly till we get to Cairo.
Vic's going to meet us there,
and she's gonna make
everything all right.
Hey,
what the fuck
are you looking at, huh?
Excuse me?
Why don't you turn
your fat ass around?
I wish things didn't
have to go down like this. I do.
I mean, it's... it's just the way
things are, I guess.
Listen, you know I know
that I fucked up
and I fessed up to that.
I've had to live with
the choices that I have made.
No. I've had to live
with the choices you made.
You sold out your own son
so you can get back with Vic.
Me and Vic are straight.
Once, maybe.
When you worked for her.
And then you let her take me
and seduce me
as a fucking child.
Hey, it got you
off that corner, right?
You gotta start somewhere, boy.
You should a protected me.
Protected you?
Protected you from what?
You... you idolized Vic.
She was like a mother to you.
I fucking gave you that.
You didn't give me nothing.
Oh, come the fuck off it.
When the fuck
are you gonna start taking
some fucking responsibility?
You just gonna blame me
for everything
in your motherfucking life?
Do you know what she did to me?
She kicked you out
because you were her bitch.
You followed her around
like a little dog.
Fuck you.
- "I love you, Vic."
- Fuck you.
- "I love you."
She always wanted me over you
and you hated me for it.
This wasn't about the money.
You did this so you can
get back with Vic.
But she's not gonna
take you back.
You're a rat.
And Vic kills rats for fun.
Fuck.
At least I had the balls
to take something for myself,
to start over.
"Start over."
Man, what the fuck
are you gonna start over?
I've seen monkey shit fights
at the zoo
that are more organized
than you.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Fuck me. You're a fake.
Everything about you is fake.
Your gold chain is fake.
Your fucking Timex is fake.
That is a real Timex.
Motherfuckers.
Get up.
Let him up.
Easy, bro.
Hey.
I'll snitch.
I will tell this prick
what you got in there.
Hey.
Cops could be here in no time.
Hey, I got it under control.
- Hey, hi. How you doing?
- Off the bus.
Oh, now. Wait, wait, wait, wait
a second.
You too.
Oh, come on, man.
He attacked me.
I don't want to hear it.
Both of you, off the bus.
Okay, yeah,
we'll... we'll get off. Come on.
We'll... we'll both get off.
Hey, timeout. Look.
This is what happened.
This guy,
he started all this shit.
And this guy,
he was defending her.
- Wasn't he?
- Yes.
He was defending me because
that creep tried to touch me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, son.
I never touched this girl.
Well, I saw him do it.
- He attacked her.
- No, no, fuck this shit.
They... they're trying
to set me up.
Hey, I know what I saw.
He tried to grab her
and that's a fact.
Oh, no. This is some bullshit.
He tried to grab me too.
Lying bitch.
Sir, shut the fuck up.
Ma'am, do you want me to
call the cops or not?
No. Throw him off.
Don't throw that guy off for
trying to protect me.
Let's go.
No. Wait a second.
- Wait a second.
- Sir, you'll notice
I have already
pulled the bus over.
My next move
is to call the cops.
Where we are, I figure
that'd take about five minutes.
They're friends of mine.
Okay.
Okay, brother. You're the boss.
I'm... I'm stepping right off.
You need my blood, right?
I don't want
your blood inside of me.
Go fuck yourself.
Get your fucking hands off me.
You think you're
the first crazy to ride this bus
that thinks he can push me
around and get away with it?
I deal with degenerates
like you every fucking day.
Come on.
Ain't you fuckin' Roger.
Hey. I got thrown off.
Come pick me up.
Pretty wild there
for a second, huh?
Let me get my piece back.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Take it, man. I don't want it.
I'm gonna go see
if I shit myself.
Next stop, Cairo.
That's Cairo. Last chance.
Lopez family.
Please report to
the nurses' station.
Lopez family. Please report to
I fucked up.
I'm in trouble.
I lost the blood.
I think I found some.
What?
Is it gonna be enough?
Enough to lose my job over.
Look, I'll meet you in the car
in the parking lot
like I said before, okay?
How long 'til you get here?
I'm gonna figure that out.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
Hey, Mom. Mom?
Lily? What are you doing here?
The movie's over.
Can I get a ride home?
Yeah. Come on.
Are you going to be okay?
Yeah.
Thanks...
for what you did.
Hey...
what's your name?
Rachel.
I'm Freddy.
How old are you really?
I'm 15.
I'm 14.
You really need a hospital, man.
Rachel, this is Will.
Hi.
- Hi.
I gotta go check this out.
Come on.
You want some help, man?
No.
Fuck.
Hey, you okay?
- Yeah.
Sit down there.
You like puzzles?
Looks hard.
Yeah.
Six.
Where are you, Freddy?
I need you to just listen.
What?
I'm... I fucked up bad.
That doesn't
change anything, Freddy.
I know.
I know. But I can change.
No.
You chose Vic.
Over me. Over Lily.
You never did anything for us.
You did everything for Vic.
You broke me, Freddy.
Why are you doing this?
I'm doing this for Lily.
Lily doesn't need
your money, Freddy.
Lily needed a father.
I want her to do
something good with her life.
Take the money.
Just get here.
Thank you.
Mm, nine.
Maybe eight.
- Maybe a three.
- Wrong number.
Hmm.
That's one.
Yeah. You're funny.
Nine.
You're funny.
Four.
Six.
Seven.
Try him again.
Uh-huh.
Motherfucker
works in social services,
finds a girl online.
Arranges a meet.
Then why's he tailing her?
Make sure she gets on the bus?
Keep a close eye?
The fuck do I know?
But she's already on the bus.
Why does he have to do that?
He's preying on her.
He gets off on it,
that's what these creeps do.
See, Smokie doesn't show up
at the bus station
like they arranged.
Now she's alone.
But this dude, Will? This kind
gentleman she met on the bus?
He can help her.
He swoops in.
He can play the hero.
Says it's getting late,
offers her a place to stay
I got it.
Oh, how about this?
This is fun.
Hey, Smokie.
I know what you're doing,
you fuck.
Sorry, wrong number.
- You okay?
- Mm-hm.
I'm gonna go check on him.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
You don't look so hot.
Leave her alone.
What you gonna do?
Call the cops?
Considering your situation,
that wouldn't be very smart
of you now,
would it?
So what do you want to do, huh?
You want money? How much?
You assume you know what I want.
Five thousand.
You ain't getting it, friend.
Now, look.
I appreciate you
putting in a good word
for me with Rachel,
but I'm not for sale.
Ten thousand dollars.
You can buy whoever
you want with that.
Just stay away from her.
You don't got it.
I do.
I tell you what.
How about...
Hm... she comes with me
anyway...
and when you die
from all that blood
that you seem to be losing,
I'll come back
for the money as well?
Hm?
Twofer.
If you will.
Hm?
You and me, it's over.
You need to come back.
You made a big mistake.
Do not fuck with me.
Freddy?
Chrissy,
I'm not going to make it.
What?
I got the blood, the drip.
No.
Look, if you can't get to me,
let me drive to you.
Where'd you say
you were going again? Cairo?
I said I'm not coming.
I don't need your help anymore.
I don't need you and I don't...
I got Lily with me.
No, Chrissy, please.
Here, talk to her.
Talk to him just once.
You don't gotta be nice.
Just let him hear your voice.
Hello?
Hi, baby.
You doing all right?
Yeah. You?
I'm trying.
I'm trying real hard.
I miss you.
I'm sorry that
I haven't been around.
Freddy?
I'm taking the money
and I'm leaving.
I don't need your help anymore.
You were Plan B.
You were always just Plan B.
So stay the fuck away.
You were right, Chrissy.
I chose Vic. I always chose Vic.
I love you, Mama.
I love you too, baby.
There's your Smokie.
What?
Will.
Will is Smokie.
He's playing you.
Nah. I think you've...
I think you've lost
a little bit too much blood.
Cairo in five minutes.
Five minutes to Cairo.
All right.
All right, I got an idea.
That's my boy!
An idea for what?
You gotta trust me.
Empty your backpack.
Fill your bag up with this.
Then put your stuff in mine.
Why am I doing this?
I need you to get it to someone.
Her name is Christine.
Take my phone.
Call her and get
the money to her.
Can you do that?
How do you know
I'm not gonna steal it?
Because I'm trusting you.
I told you before,
someone took advantage of me.
Look, what I lost,
I can't get back.
You gotta still believe
you're worth something.
Even when nobody else does,
you gotta believe.
You got your whole life
ahead of you, Rachel.
You make the right choice.
What do you want me to tell her?
Tell her...
tell her, when we were
at that state park...
on the water...
I knew right then
that I loved her.
But I didn't say it.
But I could never be a father.
So tell her I wish I'd said it.
Can you do that for me?
Yeah.
Tell her that I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look at me.
You're going to be okay.
You're gonna be fine.
We're almost there.
You're gonna tell her.
You're gonna be okay.
Okay?
Just give me my bag.
Put it here.
- Take this.
- Okay.
Go sit up front.
Hey.
Okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Hey.
You got this.
I got this.
Everything okay?
Yes.
Everything happens for a reason.
You got this.
Last stop, Cairo.
Rachel.
Thanks.
I've gotta get you out of here.
He's a very bad person
and I've gotta protect you.
You can trust me.
Good girl. Let's go.
Go ahead.
You too. Get out of here.
You with him?
Yes.
Run along, sweetheart.
Ah!
Not you.
Rach.
Don't worry about her.
Just open the bag.
Rach.
Where you going?
I said open the fucking bag.
Why?
Make sure it's all there.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
I'm not going with you.
I'm not going with you, Vic.
Oh, baby.
We good?
Get him the fuck out of here.
No.
What the fuck?
It's some fucking bullshit.
This is fucking bullshit.
Huh?
What the fuck.
What the fuck is this?
- Hello?
- Christine?
Who's this?
I'm Rachel.
I'm a friend of Freddy's.
He's dead, isn't he?
He asked me to tell you a story.