Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[static on radio]
[gunshot]
You're all clear.
[grunts]
DEA!
[shouting in Spanish]
[gunfire]
[shouting]
Secure the area.
[gunshot]
- [gunshot]
- [body thuds]
[DEA agent] Clear.
Throw down your weapon.
Throw down your weapon!
Down!
[DEA Agent 2]
¡Abajo! On your knees.
Hands up.
Turn around.
Turn around!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[DEA agent] Cap!
James.
We need him alive.
You gotta check this out.
[screaming]
[crickets chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
- Where'd you get that?
- You like it?
- Looks expensive.
- It was.
I mean it is. I...
I got it from a friend.
She didn't need it anymore.
Mom wanted you
to come down.
She said Dad
should be here soon.
All right,
I'll be there in a minute.
[car approaching]
[door opens]
Daddy!
[laughs]
Hey, sweetie!
- How are you?
- How you doin'?
- I'm good.
- [sighs]
Got a little banged up,
though.
- You okay?
- I'll be fine.
- [James] Hey, you.
- Hey.
[chuckles]
I remember you.
Why are you limping?
Uh, bug bite.
It'll be okay.
It's nice to have you home.
I feel much better now.
[men shouting]
- Watch your back, man.
- [inmate] Hey, Johnny.
I heard you were
getting out today.
We got some
unfinished business.
Oh, Jesus.
[groans] Listen.
I don't wanna have
any trouble, all right?
- I'm getting out soon and...
- [grunts]
[grunting]
Hey, bitch, here.
Fuck this, man.
[grunts]
[exhales]
I can't wait to get
the fuck out of here.
Jesus.
[parole officer] Aggravated
assault with a deadly weapon,
three counts
of first-degree armed robbery.
Do you take your responsibility
for your actions?
What I feel bad about is, uh...
[hisses] You know,
I killed somebody's husband.
His name was George
and he had two kids, and...
[sighs]
I took that away from them,
and I'm sorry about it,
but, um, I'll always be
sorry about it.
I'm just...
You know, I just wanna...
I don't know what I wanna do.
I just wanna
be the best man I can be.
You have quite the impressive
military record.
A Silver Star,
two Purple Hearts,
three tours of duty.
Afghanistan. Iraq.
I think that if anyone
deserves another chance,
it's you, sir.
I hope to God
I never see you again.
You know, honestly,
I could kinda tell something was going on.
Like, I could feel it.
And then Tom said
that he liked Serafina,
and I was like...
[indistinct chatter]
[screaming]
No, no!
Dad?
Girls, could you excuse us
for a second?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
I guess you don't wanna talk
about what happened.
- Talk about what?
- [chuckles]
I'm glad you're still
a sarcastic asshole.
Yeah, well, I try.
What's going on?
- Babe...
- Just...
Anybody up for some dessert?
[James] Wow.
[chuckles]
Look at that cake.
And I got you guys this.
Huh?
Open it.
Sunrose Cabins?
At first, I thought we could
all go together this weekend,
like old times.
But now I see that you two
need some "alone" time.
Where did you get
that money?
Serafina's mom got it as
a giveaway at some event,
and they couldn't use it,
so they asked if we wanted it.
Okay. Right?
Yeah, why not?
Thanks, babe.
[Mom]
Well, thank you.
[car approaching]
- Oh, goddamn!
- Johnny!
Oh, goddamn,
so nice to see you.
Oh!
Good to see you,
man.
Oh, it's been so long.
Been a long time.
You look good.
Thanks for the ride.
Let me get
your stuff, man.
- It's good to have you home.
- Johnny's back!
[car door opens]
Let's get
the fuck outta here.
Listen, I've heard
what you two have been doin'.
It's all over the tube.
Everybody knows
y'all are going straight now.
I did promise, uh,
Ma and Pa
I'd keep you
on the straight and narrow,
so you've just gotta,
you know,
do the right thing, lay low.
Keep our shit tight.
Well, you got
the money, right?
I knew you still had it.
Where is it?
Listen, I don't want you two
involved, all right?
We can get it in and out.
No problem at all.
Just tell us
where you put it.
If they catch your ass
with the money,
they're gonna send you
back there.
Oh, I ain't gonna worry
about that.
Ain't nobody gonna find shit.
Listen, I'm hungry.
Let's grab a hot dog somewhere.
Sounds good to us.
Our old house?
[Rudy]
Brilliant.
We looked everywhere.
Never thought
you'd put it in there.
[Rudy] You okay?
Yeah. I'm getting there.
Listen, here's a map I drew
where I put everything.
Piece of cake.
[Matthew] We won't let you
down, Johnny.
Listen, boys, the only thing
I really give a fuck about
is that ring.
Okay?
We got some serious shit we
gotta take care of, all right?
Don't let nothing fuck it up,
all right? You hear me?
- We got you.
- We got it.
Just keep it cool
until we get the job done.
- All right?
- Yes, sir.
All right.
[Rudy clears throat]
♪ I ain't gonna stop ♪
♪ Until the night is fading ♪
♪ Until the music's all gone ♪
♪ I'm gonna shine
With the moon and the stars ♪
♪ I'm gonna sing
From the bottom of my heart ♪
♪ My heart ♪
What are you doing?
Where are you getting
all this cash from?
Shh!
Can you keep a secret?
I found it.
You found
all of that money?
- Look.
- Holy shit!
- We have to tell Mom and Dad.
- We can't tell Mom and Dad!
You don't know
who this money belongs to!
Who cares who it belonged to?
It's ours now.
It's probably, like,
really old.
Like when this house
was first built, anyways.
The bank
is AGL Bank and Trust.
What do you mean?
Well, I found it,
so I'm gonna spend it.
It's my money now.
Here, take one.
I don't want it!
And it's not yours,
it's someone else's!
It was someone else's,
but I found it,
- therefore it's now mine.
- I don't want it.
- Just take some, have fun, spend it!
- No!
I have plenty of fun,
thank you very much!
- I'm not gonna steal...
- Doing what?
- What?
You don't have fun
doing anything.
You're always
being such a prude.
If you don't want it,
I'll take it.
Wow.
Good luck, Jen.
♪ Keep on moving
Keep, keep ♪
♪ Keep on smiling
[garage door opening]
[Johnny]
Look at this joint.
- '64 Malibu.
- Yes, sir.
- Nice setup here, bro.
- Thank you very much.
I was hoping
you'd like it.
Wow, this is tits.
- Cool, man.
- Let's have some beers, huh?
Let's go. Hey, brother,
did you get that done yet?
- Hey, you can't rush perfection.
- [chuckles] Yeah, right.
You gotta run
a tight ship, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- Keep everything tight.
As tight as my ex-wife.
From this night on,
no more sticking that shit up your
nose, all right?
Done.
You watch out for your
little brother, huh?
- I will.
- All right.
[Rudy] I promise,
we're not gonna let you down.
[sighs]
So, here's to freedom!
[laughs]
Here's to good-lookin'
snapper, boys.
Cheers.
- All right, little brother.
- Yeah.
Fuckin'-A.
Aren't you a little
young to be drinking?
Oh, go stick it, boy.
[chuckles]
[car door opens]
[James] You know, babe,
this could really be like
a second honeymoon.
Wow.
This place is really nice.
[sighs] Is something
on your mind?
I didn't recognize you
when you came home.
James Baker.
And you are?
Lisa Rodriguez.
Nice to meet you.
Babe, I'm still
the same man you married.
I don't want you working
for them anymore.
I'm not.
- Really?
- Really.
Why?
I'm just not.
What are you gonna do?
[sighs]
I don't know.
But I'm starting
to get an idea.
- [chuckles]
- Come here.
I got a bad fucking
feeling about this.
You'll be all right.
[footsteps approaching]
Just stay close
to me.
[sighs]
Four of them.
There's Daddy, Mommy
and their two daughters.
Piece of cake.
But hands off my two cupcakes.
'Cause they're mine.
We're just going in to
make sure it's all there.
We're gonna wait
until they're gone
to actually get it.
Ah, fuck.
Where's the fun in that?
Johnny wants it quiet.
And clean.
What Johnny wants,
Johnny gets.
Yeah. He does.
All right.
Come on.
- Wait!
- What?
Is he asleep?
[screams]
- Oh, shit! Go, go, go, go!
- Fuck!
James!
- James.
- Mom?
[Lisa] Go back to your rooms,
right now. Right now!
James.
Give me the gun.
[James breathing heavily]
Baby.
You've gotta get help.
I'm all right.
Oh, what the fuck?
We should have killed him.
I need to think.
Think? You're always
fucking thinking!
Stop thinking! All right?
Now we know who the fuck
we're dealing with.
Right?
So why don't we just
fuck off back home,
think of something else?
We'll come back later
and take care of business.
[breathes heavily]
Fuck.
Baby.
I need help.
What are we gonna do
about this?
I don't think we should keep
that in the house for a while.
Baby, I'd understand it
if you want me to leave.
Oh.
No, baby, no.
I'm not gonna leave you.
[doorbell rings]
Every night?
I knew you were having
a hard time, but I...
Yeah.
That's why I need you here.
I'm afraid
I'm gonna hurt my family.
Hey.
We're not gonna
let that happen.
You got me?
It'll just be
for a little while,
just till I get this
under control.
I am here
as long as you need.
Appreciate it.
[therapist on computer] There's
nothing wrong with you, James.
[James scoffs]
I'm serious.
What you experienced
is a normal reaction
to extremely
abnormal experiences.
[James sighs]
[James] So what
am I supposed to do?
How do I tell
from what's real
and what's... you know.
Start with one thing
you can see with your eyes.
The tree.
Then what can you hear
with your ears?
I can hear the buzzing
of my air conditioner.
What can you sense
with your skin?
My collar on my neck.
My watch on my arm.
What do you taste?
The coffee I just drank
on my tongue.
Now, what do you smell?
My perfume. Those flowers.
Focusing on your five senses
will get you out of your head
and back to the present.
Now, you try.
What do you see?
[therapist laughs]
You're going to have to try
a lot harder than that.
Um, Jennifer's drawing.
[therapist] Good.
Now, what do you hear?
[exhales]
[sighs]
[phone beeps]
- [cell phone ringing]
- Ah.
Hey. Talk to me.
What?
I don't understand.
What do you mean, "not yet"?
Look, look,
do what you gotta do.
We went over it, just...
All right.
I'll take care of it.
No worries. We got this.
All right. No, it's cool.
Bye.
[phone beeps]
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Yeah, honey, I got it all written down.
I won't forget the milk.
Milk, butter, cereal.
I got it, honey.
All right, I'll see you soon.
Love you too. Bye.
Wife busting
the chops again, huh?
Let me give you
a little marriage advice.
She's the boss.
Whatever she says goes.
Happy wife, happy life.
Here's the file
you asked for.
- You take care of that. I gotta run.
- All right.
Hey.
Well, goddamn! Goddamn!
Oh! What you doin'? Oh!
- Are you sneakin' up on me? Huh?
- Yeah.
- Mr. Policeman! Yeah.
- Yeah, well, look at you.
- Look at you, man. Filled out.
- Yeah, little bit.
- You look like a million bucks, brother.
- And you do too.
- Well, they finally let you out, huh?
- Yeah.
I was beginning to think they were
gonna keep your ass locked up forever.
Yeah, well, you know,
it felt like forever.
Listen, coz, uh,
I need your help
on something.
Well, must be serious, huh?
What's in it for me?
More money than you're making
doing what you're doing, bro.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I can cut your ass in
for 2% of three million.
Two percent of three million.
Let's see...
That's $60,000.
Well, it must be
something serious, huh?
Well, this is my career
we're talking about.
I'm gonna have to ask
for about 10% on that.
Deal.
You got it.
All right, man.
Let's make some money.
- Let's make some money.
- All right. Welcome back.
Let's make some noise, bro.
Let's go have a beer.
Yeah. Come on.
Let's go find us
a supermodel or two.
Now we're talking.
[both laugh]
[birds chirping]
Sometimes I...
I can't tell what's real...
or what's in my head.
There's nothing to
be ashamed of with PTSD.
You just have to take it
one day at a time.
It takes time.
Your brain is still processing
a traumatic experience.
The next time
you're in that compound,
here's an exercise you can do.
Every time
you look at your thumb,
ask yourself, "Is this real
or is this fake?"
Say it out loud.
Is this real?
Or is this fake?
Well?
Real.
Good. That's a good start.
Keep doing it
until it becomes a habit.
[therapist] You're still going
on vacation with your wife?
[James sighs] I don't know.
[therapist] You should. I think
it'd be good for you two.
She needs you too, James.
Just as much as you need her
right now.
Don't shut her out.
[knocking on door]
Mr. James Baker?
- Hello.
- Hey.
Well, I appreciate you
coming down here, sir.
Yeah.
So how can I help you, Sheriff?
Well, it seems we've got
ourselves a little problem.
What kinda problem?
Well, it's probably
not gonna amount to much.
I know you're DEA
and all that.
Well, I got a warrant here
with your name on it.
James Baker, yeah?
"Breach of Peace"?
This is bullshit.
- I just got here.
- [chuckles] Well...
it must have followed you
from San Antone.
- This makes no sense.
- Hmm.
Listen, I got a buddy
in the government.
He sent me your record.
Hope you don't mind.
But I gotta tell ya,
I'm very impressed.
DEA, military. Phew.
But it also says that you
were just diagnosed with PTSD.
Post-Traumatic Stress.
That's a terrible thing.
See, I was in
the service myself,
and, well, let's say
I knew a lot of guys
who pretended they were sick
so they could get a little
extra on their pension.
That's a shameful thing
to do.
What the fuck?
This is signed
by the attorney's office.
There's no judge's signature
on this.
There's not?
No. No.
Let me see
that goddamn thing.
Well, I'll be damned.
You're right. [laughs]
I don't know
what you're trying to pull,
but next time you try
to bring me down here,
you contact my superiors,
my RAC,
and don't waste my time.
Hmm.
Deputy, will you show
this gentleman out?
What the fuck did you have me
come down here for anyway?
[chuckles]
[groans]
[receiver clatters]
- [line ringing]
- [exhales]
Yeah, he just left.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[groans]
They're leaving.
This is
an in-and-out job.
No more problems.
This ain't your average
snatch and grab, boys.
We gotta make this one
calculated.
- We'll see about that.
- Yeah, we fucking will.
You gotta keep your head
in this one, man.
Well, let's fucking see.
Ho! Let's go!
What are we waitin' for now?
Fucking Christmas?
Dominic, relax. What if
they forgot something?
Forgot something? What the fuck
are they gonna forget?
Let's fucking do this!
Man.
Keep your fucking head.
[whispers] Ah. Fucking head!
[tapping on dashboard]
[Rudy] You wanna knock
that the fuck off?
[dance music playing
on speakers]
Mom and Dad
are gonna be pissed.
They'll never know.
Isn't that what they say in the
movies before they get caught?
Then they won't be surprised
when they catch us.
You. Catch you.
Catch me. Whatever.
I had nothing to do
with this.
It's not like I invited
the whole school.
Hit that shit!
[rock music playing
on radio]
Oh!
[chuckles]
Didn't get the invite.
It's melon ice.
Yo, yo, yo.
Kiwi's the best flavor, no cap.
Tom, that's so cap, bro.
You're like 50% cap,
50%...
- What?
- [all laugh]
Naughty!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's fucking go!
Let's go, let's go!
We're doing this,
Tommy boy! Whoo!
Why you so riled up,
Tom?
Why you so riled up
right now?
Good job, bitch!
- So, uh...
- Her parents are gone.
- But what about Natalie?
- Don't worry about her.
Look, I'll handle her,
you handle Dyana.
All right.
[chuckles]
[door bell ringing]
I'll be in my room.
You know, maybe
if you were nicer to people,
you'd have more friends.
Maybe if you weren't,
people wouldn't think
you were so vapid.
[footsteps departing]
[all] Hey!
Whoo!
Okay, okay.
Somebody gonna get it
in tonight!
- Somebody gonna get it in!
- [laughs]
The more, the merrier.
[screaming]
[whispers]
Is this real? Is this real?
[James clears throat]
Are you gonna tell me
what happened?
Are you sure you wanna know?
Of course I wanna know.
[sighs] If we can...
James.
Just tell me.
Okay.
Pull over.
[turn signal clicking]
[muffled dance music playing
on speakers]
[muffled chattering]
Are you kidding me?
[grunts]
Damn it.
What?
There was a firefight.
We exchanged gunfire.
After we'd taken the...
the men down...
[exhales]
...there was...
We saw blood
coming from
underneath a closet.
And when we opened the closet,
there...
there were...
a mother
and two daughters.
[Lisa gasps]
They had been killed
by our gunfire.
Uh...
[groans] Babe, I see them.
I see them.
It was an accident.
It's not your fault.
That's just it.
It was. I...
- Baby...
- It was just a mistake.
[sighs]
It was my mistake.
[sniffles]
[sighs]
I love you.
You know that, right?
I love you too, babe.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
It's okay.
Ah, come over here.
[typing]
Fuck!
Who is she?
[Dominic]
There's a bit of totty for me.
[pop ballad playing, muffled]
[vehicle approaching]
[whispering]
What the fuck?
[engine turns off]
You just scared me.
[laughs]
What are you doing hanging out outside?
[chuckles]
I see you weren't expecting me.
He just looked at me.
Did he just fucking look at me?
[Sebastian]
You okay?
Yeah.
Your dad just asked me
to check on you, so...
That's not my fault.
Oh, now we're blaming
our sister?
You know me.
I know.
Can I show you something?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll fucking rub you,
you fuckin' cunt!
We need to figure
this shit out, man.
Natalie, what's going on?
Where did you get this?
I found it
under the floorboards.
I think my sister
found some money too.
I was doing some research,
and I found this.
"Was arrested
for a string of robberies
that terrorized the city
and sentenced to 15 years,
maximum federal
penitentiary."
None of the money
was ever recovered.
Okay, okay.
We don't know it's his.
Let's not jump
to any conclusions.
This money has been here
for a long time.
We don't know any of that.
We don't know anything.
Put it back.
Just put it back.
- Have you told anyone else?
- No.
Good.
Have you spent any of it?
Seriously?
I mean, what are we gonna do?
Mom and Dad aren't
even here right now.
And she's downstairs
acting like a crazy...
- Calm. Nat... Natalie.
- ...wild child!
It's not against the law
to find money.
Okay? We're gonna figure
this out. Not a problem.
Just put it back.
Let's go talk to Jen.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Okay.
[pills rattling]
What the fuck
are you doing?
Fueling the fire.
Fueling my calm.
See, this
is the calm
before the storm.
And it's gonna be
a big fucking storm.
Oh.
[exhales]
[groans]
You gotta be fucking
kidding me.
Johnny wanted us
to bring this guy?
Are you gonna
keep it together?
- Rip off your beard!
- Get the fuck off me, bro.
- Chill the fuck out.
- You'll be okay.
[chuckles]
Bro, are you gonna be
the fuck all right?
We got shit to do,
and you gotta have your
fucking brain together, man.
[clears throat]
[exhales]
Let's fucking do it.
Let's fucking do it. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
It's time to play.
Can we fucking play?
Please.
Hey!
Where's Jen?
What's your problem?
Where's my sister?
I don't know.
I think they went to her room.
I'll get her.
I'll check the back.
[pop music playing]
[knocking on door]
Jen.
I need to talk to you.
I'm kinda busy.
It's important.
- Can it wait?
- No.
Fine. What is it?
[whispers] I found
something in my room.
Congratulations. You found
something in your room.
I'm so proud of you.
Now get the fuck out my room.
Where were we?
Let's see what
everyone else is doing.
But, Jen...
There's more important
things going on right now.
- Like what?
- Put your clothes on.
Look, Jen, just 30 minutes.
[chuckles]
Like you can last that long.
Why not?
There's nothing going on
downstairs.
I have stuff to do.
Get dressed!
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
And your boxers?
Fireworks, dude?
Are you, like, 12?
But...
But I love you!
[line ringing]
Pick up. [sighs]
This is Captain James Baker.
Please leave a message.
Dad. Call me.
I need to talk to you.
It's important.
[engine starts]
Fuck it. It's time.
Finally.
Come on.
[Dominic] Hey.
Look at me.
[sniffs] Look at me.
Have I ever let you down?
Pills or no pills?
No.
[Dominic] ...problem.
What are you worried about?
Lighten up. Have a bit of fun.
[claps]
For my brother, man.
You gotta take it cool.
Brother, shmother.
Let's just fucking
have a bit of a laugh, eh?
Fuck it.
[exhales]
[Dyana moaning]
Hey, y'all. I'm here
for the ménage à trois!
[laughs]
[grunts]
Stop!
[grunting]
[teen]
What? Who the fuck?
- Who the fuck are you?
- Shut the fuck up!
What? Run!
- No!
- Run!
No!
- [teen] Run!
- [Dyana] No! No!
[whimpering]
Another one
hits the dust.
- [grunts]
- No!
[teen] No!
You're a sick fuck,
you know that?
No!
[retching]
Really?
Aren't you gonna tell me?
He's playing hard to get.
- So annoying.
- I know.
Where's Tom?
He went outside to pee.
- Why didn't he just use the bathroom?
- Boys.
He's been gone
for a while now.
Hey, hey. Party's over.
Go home, go home.
We need to talk.
[exhales]
[urinating]
Hey.
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm here for the party.
You dirty bastard!
[grunts]
Fuck!
Keep that in your pants
next time!
Fuck!
Oh.
Pretty thoughtful,
a refreshment.
Not bad, son. Not bad.
Off to the party.
Nobody fucking move!
- Who the hell are...
- Sebastian!
- [gunshot]
- [screaming]
You psycho piece of shit!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Why did you do that?
It helps.
[screaming]
You could've fucking
shot me, man!
[sobbing]
Can't leave
the ladies waiting.
[crying]
Matthew.
Why don't you come over here
and help me clean this shit up?
[cell phone ringing]
Could you answer that?
That's Natalie.
Okay.
Hello?
Dad! Dad, you have to come home.
- Hello?
- Dad! Dad!
Hey, Nat, I can't hear you.
I'll call you back
- when I can get some reception.
- Fuck! Fuck!
Hello?
- Try again.
- No service.
Daddy, Daddy.
Hi, this is Lisa.
You missed me.
Leave me a message.
Dad! Dad, you need to come home.
There's some guys in the house.
- Dad, please hurry! There's...
- [door opens]
Ah! The bedroom.
There you are!
[screaming]
- I'll be your daddy!
- No, no, no!
[Natalie] No! No!
- [zipper opens]
- [Dominic whooping]
[James]
Finally, some reception.
[Natalie] Dad!
Dad, you need to come home.
There's some guys
in the house. [crying]
Dad, please hurry! There's...
[James] I see them.
[Dominic] There you are!
[Natalie screams]
[James] It was my mistake.
What's wrong?
Leather.
The smell. You're here.
What happened, James?
Babe.
[Natalie] Dad! Dad,
you need to come home.
There's some guys
in the house.
Dad, please hurry! There's...
- This is real?
- Yeah.
You can hear this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What... Okay...
- [screaming]
- What...
- Call Sebastian!
- I'm calling Sebastian.
He's not answering.
We gotta turn back.
Stop the car
and let me drive.
[Lisa]
We need to call the cops!
[James] Cops get
hostages killed. Get in.
We got a fucking problem.
This doesn't look
like a problem.
Yeah, it's a fucking problem.
Because we don't have
Johnny's ring.
Who gives a shit about a ring
when you got all this money?
It's his fucking
dead wife's ring.
She died when he
was overseas.
And we're
a hundred grand short.
I'll find the money,
you find the ring.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
[Rudy] It's the only fucking
thing he has left of her.
[whimpering]
Where's the money?
You live here, right?
Tell me where the money is.
I swear, I only took
a few hundred.
No, no, there's more
than a few hundred missing.
All right, listen.
I don't wanna hurt you, okay?
I don't.
But my brother and Dominic
won't think twice about puttin'
a fucking bullet in your head.
They're upstairs right now doing God
knows what with your fucking sister.
One more chance.
Where's the money?
[muttering]
[grunts]
[Matthew] Get the fuck off!
[grunting]
[gunshot]
[grunts]
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
Hey.
Hey, Johnny.
[clears throat]
It's Matthew, man. He's, uh...
He got fucked up, bro.
[Johnny] What?
Holy shit.
[cheering, shouting]
[glass breaking]
What are you fucking smirking
at, you fucking scrawny prick?
[shouting, cheering]
Your sister's
a fucking fat cow.
All right.
Let's go, motherfucker.
Come on.
[both grunting]
[laughs]
Ray. Come on now, Ray!
Who's a faggot right now,
you skinny prick?
[both grunting]
[laughs]
[cheering continues]
Come on. Hit that fucking
fat bastard!
Come on. Lay that
motherfucker out!
[motorcycle revving]
Fuck! Are you fucking
kidding me?
I know.
It's been a little bit too long.
I know. Come here!
Hey, brother.
You always knew
how to make an entrance.
Oh, shit, wow.
It's good to see ya.
What's going on over here?
Remember my little brother Ray?
He ain't so little anymore.
[crowd cheering]
Come on!
Hey, Ray. [whistles]
Hey, Ray!
Ray.
- Remember me?
- What's up, amigo?
Hey, you ain't skinny
little Ray no more!
- Look at your ass, man.
- How you been?
Wow. You been taking care
of your little brother?
Oh, yeah.
He's doing good, man.
- Still fightin' every day, huh?
- I'm tryin'.
Fuckin'-A.
Gotta do something for a living.
So, listen, you ain't exactly
supposed to be here.
You just got out. This is
the last place you should be.
Yeah.
Oh, shit, you know.
Shit went sideways.
Matthew got killed.
Matthew?
Your brother Matthew?
When?
[shouts]
Who killed Matthew?
Let's go. We got some
business to take care of.
Come on, come on.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[whimpering]
- [Sebastian groaning]
- [knife slashing]
[crying]
[groans]
[Jen crying]
[knife clatters]
[cell phone ringing]
[Johnny] Is this Daddy?
Who the fuck is this?
I swear to God, man,
you put one hand
on my daughters,
I will fucking make sure
you die.
Well, it's a little too late
for that.
Here's the deal.
You walk away right now,
and I won't kill you.
Well, like I said, you're just
gonna have to kill me then, boy.
You got something
that belongs to me.
[phone clatters]
[crying]
[gasping]
Baby, don't worry.
I'll get our daughters,
and I'll make this motherfucker pay.
Are you sure
it's not gonna...
No. I'm built for this.
It's civilian life
I'm not used to.
- Okay.
- You still have the gun in the house?
I got rid of it.
Shit.
Fuck.
Don't worry.
I'll get this motherfucker.
[car engine revving]
Shit! Get the fuck in here!
- Where is it?
- [grunts]
Enough with the games,
sweetheart.
Give it up.
Today! Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Get the fuck out! Move!
Okay, babe.
I'm gonna go in from here.
- You stay outta sight, okay?
- Okay, babe.
Be safe.
[car door closes]
Did you see that?
I don't see shit.
I'm gonna check it out.
Hey, what's going
on back there?
[grunting]
[gunshot]
I think I'm gonna go outside
and check on the boys.
Well, I hope you're
fucking quick about it.
[cell phone chimes]
[grunts]
[neck snaps]
[body drops]
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
All right, let's find
the rest of it.
[cell phone ringing]
Yeah?
You're kiddin' me.
All right, I'll be right there.
Shit.
[Jen] Dad!
[Jen sobbing]
- Where's your sister?
- She's upstairs with them.
Okay. Where's Sebastian?
They killed him.
They stabbed him
over and over.
My friends!
- How many are there?
- Like five or six.
Okay. Your mother's
waiting in the car.
I want you to run
as fast as you can.
[James] Go, now.
[grunts]
[gunshot]
All right,
they're here.
Let's go.
Let's kill 'em all.
You got it.
Get this shit
and get out of here.
[gun clicking]
[laughs]
Missed me,
motherfucker!
Oh, God!
[body thuds]
[doorknob clicking]
[grunting]
Oh, shit!
[gunshot]
[biker] Motherfucker!
Move the fuck... Come on!
Fuckin' bitch!
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
Don't fucking move!
Gun down!
I said put the fucking gun down!
[Natalie sobbing]
It'd be a real shame
to put a hole
in her pretty little face,
wouldn't it?
[screaming]
[Natalie sobbing]
You killed
my fucking brother.
Know what the difference is
between you and me?
- I got nothin' to...
- [gunshot]
[loud sobbing]
It's okay.
It's okay. Okay.
Sweetie, sweetie.
Listen. Listen.
I'm gonna need you
to be strong, okay?
Now, your mother's downstairs.
I need you to go to her.
- No.
- Yes, and I want you to use this,
if you need to, to get away.
You can do it.
- Dad, no.
- Baby, baby, just go downstairs.
You can do it.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Are you ready? Okay.
Go to your mom, all right?
Go on.
You can do it.
Go ahead, baby.
All right.
Hey, Johnny!
It's James.
It's just you
and me now.
Are you listening
to me?
Let's make a deal.
I know what you want.
I'm comin' in.
Don't shoot.
Drop that shit.
[gun thuds]
Don't worry.
Some things bullets
won't satisfy.
Hey, we could make a plan.
[growls]
All right, motherfucker.
This is for my wife
and my daughters...
and Sebastian!
You gotta go.
[sheriff]
I wouldn't do that.
Shoot him.
Goddamn it, motherfucker,
shoot him!
You work for me.
Shoot him!
I don't think
you're getting it, Johnny.
I think that silencer says
he works for himself.
Ain't that right?
That's not
a department-issue gun, is it?
And that's your money he's got
right there in that bag, Johnny.
Am I right?
With everybody dead,
you get all the money.
All you gotta do
is kill one more.
But if you kill me, there's
gonna be an investigation.
But if you take out
poor Johnny here,
well, the good guys win.
"Local sheriff
and DEA agent take out
criminal home invaders."
All we gotta do is figure out
how to split up the money.
The money that nobody
but you and me knows about.
You piece of shit,
I'll kill you!
[gunshots]
Now, let's talk
about that deal.
- Sheriff.
- [groans]
I see you found our gun.
Among other things.
[sirens wailing]
[sirens continue wailing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull