Calm down!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Calm down. Calm down.
Relax. You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
Look at me.
Thank God.
I was getting so worried.
Vitals clear.
You're not doing
anything crazy, are you?
Am I gonna do anything crazy?
I don't know.
Do you remember
how you got here?
No.
Do you remember
being in a car accident?
No.
Do you remember me asking
you the same questions yesterday?
You are suffering from
post-traumatic amnesia.
Can you tell me your name?
Of course I can.
- My
- Hm-mm?
What is it?
John.
Your name is Cain.
John Cain.
Don't worry. Everything
will come back. Okay?
We are doing everything we can.
The best thing for you now
just to relax.
I'll be right here.
I'm sorry, but
Who are you?
I'm your wife.
You're my wife?
Just try to relax. Okay?
What-what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Isotonic saline
to cope with your blood loss,
along with morphine
for the pain.
You will love it.
Can we take these
off now, please?
It's a fucking disaster.
Oof!
Is it Cain?
Not sure.
The body's too burnt to tell.
We're pulling dental.
We'll get it soon.
Yeah.
What the hell is this?
A way down to the city
electrical conduit tunnel.
This party took
months to plan. Maybe years.
- Did any of you know about this?
- No, sir.
Didn't? Great job.
Great fucking job!
I ought a fire all of you!
What do you want us
to do about this?
I want you to find
the motherfucker!
I'm sorry.
Things have been difficult.
It just would have been nice
to know what you were up to.
How am I supposed to know that?
I don't even know who I am.
I mean, do I have a birthday?
Do I have parents?
Dr. Garza said everything
will come back eventually.
Just try to relax, okay?
December 2nd, 1972.
You were born
in Boulder, Colorado.
Your father's name is
Ernie. He's in France,
finally taking
his European vacation.
I spoke to him last night.
He's doing his best to get here.
My mother?
It's just me and you, Cain.
It's just us.
Where's your ring?
There he is.
How you doin', buddy?
Cain, this is Eddie.
Do you remember him?
I can't say that I do. No.
Yeah, Anna told me you got
a memory thing going on.
No progress?
- No.
How do I know you?
You're one fucked-up dude,
you know?
I didn't realize
it was this bad.
On any other day, you're usually
the sharpest guy in the room.
Okay. Let me introduce
myself again.
I'm Eddie.
Cain, nice to meet you.
You're like a brother to me.
And you better goddamn
believe that I'm gonna do
whatever it takes to make
sure that you're alright.
You know why?
'Cause you owe me money.
Like five dollars
from a poker game.
- Como estas?
- Bien.
Okay, things will start
looking up soon, Cain.
I got the best of the best
coming here to help you out.
You know? I'll get you
back to normal
so you can remember everything
you need to remember
in no time at all. I promise.
Can I speak to you for a moment?
Actually, I should get going,
but I'll call you later.
My friend.
Excuse me!
He seems fucked.
Not what I paid for.
I already told you.
He's not ready.
Time's up, Garza.
Don't think too much.
Don't hesitate.
Just do as you were told.
Listen, please!
I need that case.
So I thought I'd pay you
a visit to remind you
that all our lives
are depending on this.
Just just remember one thing.
Who loves you?
- Yeah.
- No, no, no.
I want you to say it.
Who loves you?
Eddie loves me.
Claro, cabrón!
I love this guy.
I know.
I love you so much I even
send you hearts in our texts.
I'm not in the mood, Eddie.
Okay. Who's texting you
right now?
Someone who loves you.
Ves, cabrón?
We tried your way
with this fucking drug,
but it's obviously not working.
So now you're going to use
anything and everything
until his fucking memory
comes back!
That's your boy?
So pretty.
Don't worry, Garza.
I won't touch him.
You know that's not my style.
My style is way colder
than that.
I'd rather kill his dad
right now.
This little guy
won't have a chance.
Sin papa, he will grow
up loveless and confused.
He'll try to sell drugs,
but quickly he will realize
that drugs
don't make much money.
So he'll turn to worse ways
to make money.
And he'll cry himself
to sleep every night
because he and his mom
can't afford heat or food.
But most of all,
this little guy will cry
because he won't
be able to figure out
why his father disappeared.
Why his father
didn't love him enough
to leave a fucking note
before he disappeared.
Just do as you were told.
Let's go.
- Here.
- No, I got
Let me help you.
You're very pretty.
You don't remember anything?
Yeah.
I remember hospital food
tastes like shit.
Wow. I remember that.
You've never let me do this.
What? Feed me?
Why would I?
First time.
I want to know what happened.
How it happened.
You've been gone for days.
I thought
I thought maybe
you changed your mind.
Change my Why would I change?
Ready to move around?
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, breathe and take it slow.
- Okay.
Your feet first.
- Oh, man.
Okay. Breathe.
Okay.
Okay, do you feel nauseous?
- I'm fine.
It's the saline, okay?
Sometimes it has that effect.
Good, Cain.
Okay. Okay.
How are you feeling?
- Good. Time for tests?
- No.
Que pasa, Doctor.
What do you mean by that?
Who the fuck am I?
If you make a sound, I'll put
a fucking hole in your head.
Do you hear me?
Now you better tell me
what the hell's going on.
This is only gonna
make things worse.
What things?
These are dangerous people. Okay?
It's not just them
you gotta worry about.
Yeah? Does that include you?
Get in.
- You need to understand this.
- I understood completely.
You're not my wife.
Fuck!
He's in the elevator.
Shit.
We're not moving.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I have no clue.
Main elevator is frozen.
They ain't going nowhere.
We can go up.
Chinga.
Cain
I just wanna talk.
Yeah, you should have
thought about that approach first.
Where are you, Cain?
What do you want from me?
You have something of mine.
Is that so?
You don't want to do this, man.
You have no idea
who the other players are.
This runs far deeper
than you can imagine.
Cain, where is it?
Cain!
- Cain!
- Go fuck yourself, Eddie.
First guy to find him
gets a serious fucking raise.
Pull up the camera feeds.
I know you don't want to,
but you need to listen to me.
Sit.
- Can we just talk for a second?
- Sit down.
I want you to
tell me everything.
Everything, from the beginning.
- I don't know the details.
- Why am I here?
You and Eddie, you're close.
You close
all kinds of deals together.
He even treated you like family,
and that doesn't happen
with him often.
But then, then you disappeared.
- Hands here.
And now we're here.
So we're like what?
Like like weapons dealers?
Drugs.
I'm a drug dealer?
More than that.
You work with Eddie.
- In the cartel?
- Yeah, in the cartel.
Holy shit.
- Yes.
- Oh, fuck.
I could have been a lawyer.
I could have been
a football player.
a fucking carney.
I could have worked
in the carnival, but no.
I have to wake up and be
a fucking cartel member?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Cain, think.
Where is it?
Where is what?! I don't
know what you're talking about!
I don't remember anything!
I don't even know
if I believe you!
I'm pretty sure you know.
I'm not bullshitting you!
Your gut's gotta be
telling you something.
Not about you and Eddie.
This us
This is real.
I do remember
that there was somebody.
I'm starting to put together
the bits and pieces,
and it was not you.
Your mind's not
processing right now, Cain.
- No. No. No.
- You're not yourself.
It's all gonna hit you.
And when it does,
you're gonna feel awful.
You need to trust me.
This wasn't my choice.
This is not how
I wanted it to play out.
Eddie thought that if you
woke up and saw me by your side,
that you'd tell me everything.
You need to trust me.
No. No.
No, I'm gonna go find
some answers for myself.
Shit!
There's gotta
be something in here.
John Cain.
Motherfucker.
Alright. Bring it.
Come on.
Take it. Take it!
Oh my god, Mr. Cain, what
are you doing out of your room?
Are you okay?
What are you doing
out of your room?
I don't have a room. Come.
Come. Come on, Mr. Cain. Come.
Let's go to your room.
- No. No. No. No. No. No.
- No, no, what?
You go. You go.
There's some people.
There's some people
who are very injured
who need your medical attention.
What? No.
Let's go together.
Go. Go.
Fuck.
Cain. Cain.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. It's me. It's me. It's me.
Dr. Garza.
I can explain,
but we need to go.
I found you. In just
a matter of time, they do.
Come on.
They probably
gave you a sedative.
But let me help you.
Why should I trust you?
How do I know you didn't
try to kill me earlier?
You don't understand.
They come here all the time.
They use this space
and we always do what they say,
or Eddie threatens our families.
We don't have a choice.
I'm not proud,
the things I sometimes do.
Well, I do what I can
when I can.
Why am I here?
Why am I in this hospital?
They want whatever
you have in here.
You stole a case
from General Mondejo.
He's head of the army and
the cartels all report to him.
They tried to test memory drugs
to get you to remember
where you hide case.
But I shot you up with B12
so they got nothing from you.
Let me help you.
No. No. Are you
fucking kidding me?
I want you to win.
I hate these fucking people!
Give me the fucking shot.
You better not be
fucking with me.
Okay.
Let everyone know we kill
the power on everything.
Better lock down all the doors.
Last name.
Cain.
Standby.
Cain?
- Who is this?
- It's McCoy.
What the hell's going on?
What happened?
I don't... I don't know.
You've been
out of pocket for days.
What do you mean,
I've been out of pocket?
Yeah, out of pocket.
Off the map.
Off the fucking grid.
You know where I'm standing right now?
No.
In front of your house.
Yeah. There was
a cooked body inside.
We're waiting
on the test results.
We thought you were dead.
Who's we?
The DEA. Jesus Christ,
Cain, come on.
What's going on?
I was in a...
I was in a car accident.
Yeah?
Well, where were you headed?
I don't... I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
Hello?
Oh, shit.
- Hello?
- Connection lost.
- What happened?
- He's on a sat phone.
Sats are rotating,
we'll get him back.
Why in the hell
is he on a sat phone?
Can you trace it?
That's the fucking point
of a sat phone.
Oh.
No, thank you.
Fuck.
I just found a Mexican cocaine
factory inside this hospital.
Start talking.
Hospitals need to
pay the bills too.
Tell me everything, now.
What are you?
Want me to make something up?
I want you to stop lying.
Tell me. Come on.
Cain, I don't know what you did,
but you clearly pissed off
a lot of people
that seem very intent
on killing you today.
So you and Eddie obviously
knew each other before me.
Yeah.
What about you and me? I
mean, if there is a you and me.
Of course.
I'm not here for Eddie.
I'm here for you.
I love you.
I know that you know that.
No. I don't know that.
It's simple, Cain.
Eddie wants what
you took from him.
You and Eddie work
with General Montejo,
and were supposed to
deliver a valuable case.
But you went missing,
and showed up here days later,
no memory of what happened.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Put it down.
Take it easy.
Just take it easy.
Go! Go!
Holy shit!
It's empty.
Oh my god.
You're hurt bad.
Let me look at it.
I'm gonna find something
to help, okay?
Okay.
Goddamn it.
Yeah.
- Cain?
Yeah. Hey, I want you to
write something down for me.
It's Joe's Café.
Tucson, Arizona.
0830062499.
What is it?
I don't know.
I'm just hoping that'll give me
some answers. You're DEA.
Maybe you guys
can look into it for me.
Cain, you are DEA.
Jesus, you're not one of them.
You've been undercover
for the past five years.
You're one of
the best agents we have.
No. No, that can't be.
You're fucking
ex-military, Cain.
Not some goddamn drug dealer.
I don't know what they did
to your head, but I promise you
I'll get you
out of there safely.
Why the fuck am I here?
I don't know what happened.
You check in every three weeks.
That's your routine.
The last one was
supposed to be two days ago.
Today, you pop up out of
nowhere and now we're here.
Alright, just get me
the fuck out of here.
Find him.
He could be anywhere.
Use your goddamn head,
Jacobs. How many 6 foot 3 Ken dolls
just show up
with bumps on their heads
within a 100-mile radius
of Tucson,
south or north of the border?
Come on! For Christ's sake,
what do I pay you for?
I'll figure it out.
- Everything okay?
- Yup. Yup. Yup.
This should do the trick.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
- Here. Hold it.
- I got it.
Aren't you gonna thank me?
- For what?
For saving your life.
You gonna thank me?
Let's just get outta here.
Okay. Alright. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hey, Cain!
Fuck!
Shit.
Cain.
Here, Cain.
Come on. Come on.
We'll find him,
McCoy. We'll find him.
Oh, Christ.
He's out there on his own.
He doesn't know what's going on.
We're trying, sir.
Well, try harder!
Cain.
Hey, Cain!
Did I ask you to do that?
That's Eddie's voice.
I'm sorry.
Come on, Eddie.
Fuck.
Diego!
- Pendejo.
- It wasn't me.
Let this motherfucker
know we're not playin'.
Then he'll show up.
He couldn't able to go anywhere.
He's in the ceiling.
Cain!
I know you can hear me.
Let's see how many
good guys it takes to kill
before you come down here
and face me like a man!
I know you have
a soft spot for people.
Get him!
No! No!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Que les pasa!
I want him alive!
I need my fucking case!
Hey! What the
fuck are you doing here?
Get out!
Get up.
This is not the way
I thought this day would go
when I woke up.
Don't try to charm me.
You're dead, motherfucker.
I know all your tricks.
Exactly. Yes. You know me.
Yeah. You bet I know you.
You betrayed us, motherfucker.
Tell me why
everybody's after me.
The money was transferred,
but you didn't turn it over.
So you stole the money
and the fucking case.
Account number please.
0830662499.
Money has been transferred.
Twenty million dollars
deposited as of 3:15 p.m. today.
So they found out
you were gonna skip town.
And the order went out.
To kill me.
The Sinaloan...
Fuck Sinaloa, pendejo.
You think we're
here for some small shit?
We're here for the case, cabrón.
Call Eddie.
I want to talk to him.
He's well past talking, asshole.
Call him.
Where the fuck are you, Diego?
Diego?
Diego? Diego?
It's me.
What do you want?
I want to talk.
On the roof.
Just you and me.
I'm going up to the roof.
I'm dealing with
this asshole myself.
What's the plan?
Okay, when I go like this,
you kill the motherfucker.
Okay. I will put a bunch
of snipers on the rooftop.
Don't worry, Eddie.
Yeah.
I'm going in
and pulling Cain out
of that hospital.
He's in too deep.
And the cartels are onto him.
Cain is three hours
from the border
in a small cartel-run hospital.
So I'm going to need
a security clearance.
We can't authorize that.
Cain is too far undercover.
We need to burn him.
Cain's a fucking war hero.
Settle down.
I'm going down there and
pullin' his ass
out of that hospital.
I'll consider it,
but I want wires in that car,
cameras across the way
so nothing goes wrong.
No. No wires. No cameras.
We're on a foreign soil here
and we're trying...
It's not going to happen, McCoy.
If something goes wrong
everybody in this room
gets the blame.
We're talking about Cain here.
You've been trying
to protect Cain
since you first
brought him here.
So I'm recommending that
we dump fire on that place
and be done with it.
You got six hours.
And then with or without you,
we're gonna burn
the fucking place.
Let me tell you
how this is gonna go.
If you burn him,
if you burn Cain, you burn me.
Alright
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Tequila. Wait.
You remember anything yet?
Yeah.
Apparently I'm DEA.
No shit.
I know that.
You double-cross motherfuckers.
Actually we did it together.
Bullshit.
Bullshit. You're lying.
I can tell when you're lying.
Oh, now you're remembering shit?
Yeah, you could
you could tell me
anything you want right now.
You could tell me
fucking Santa Claus was real
and I'd probably believe you.
You can think
whatever the fuck you want
about Santa, but
everything I just told you
is the truth.
We were playing all
these motherfuckers together.
But you went off book,
and you stole
something without me.
The General's fucking case.
We have to return it.
You see, when you
go outside of this,
that's when the problems come.
You fucked over
the only two organizations
that can save you.
DEA and the cartel.
What's in that case?
The best thing ever.
- The best thing ever?
- Our golden ticket.
DEA, cartels, fuck them.
Fuck them all.
We'll beat all of them.
Come on. Come on.
The best thing ever?
The golden ticket.
Above the cartel...
I mean, come on.
What the fuck is
that supposed to mean?
Huh? Why am I here?
Who the fuck am I?
Am I a good guy
or am I a bad guy?
Because I'm starting to feel
like I'm not such a good guy.
I just stole this gun
from some dude
and I kicked his ass
out the window.
That's not good!
You killed Diego?
- Yeah.
- Fuck.
Yeah, Diego's probably...
He's probably
not going to make it.
Sorry.
Okay.
You really wanna know?
You're a good man, Cain.
But it doesn't matter.
The only thing that matters
in this country is power.
Power.
And you can pick
a side after we get it.
If you wanna go and
save the rainforest, go ahead.
I mean
if it makes you happy
But now I need you to tell me.
Where is it?
You gotta remember something.
- I remember something.
- You do?
A tunnel.
Okay. What else did you see?
You carrying something?
A steel case.
I'm guessing it was the case.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
The case.
Where did you leave it, man?
I need more information.
Give me more. Give...
You dick!
Okay, stop it!
If you had any clue
what I've done for you, man.
We must kill Cain.
And you're all agreed on this?
I mean, what's
the profit and loss here?
Really?
He stole from us, Eduardo.
And how many of you
have stolen from each other
over the years?
But we are La Raza.
Cain's a fucking gringo.
It's been decided, Eduardo.
End of conversation, okay?
Okay.
If you do this,
you better pray
to God you don't miss.
'Cause if you do,
I'm surrounded by dead men.
- Salud.
Oh, what have you done for me?
I'm outta here.
Where do you think you're going?
I gotta get the fuck outta here.
Cain. Cain.
Hasta la vista, you dick.
Cain! Cain!
Fuck.
Yeah?
We found the tunnel, Cain.
The number you gave came back
traced to an off-shore account.
Last transaction, two days ago.
How's the memory?
I did some bad shit.
I'm pretty sure of it.
We've been
friends for a long time.
How's your pop?
- Traveling. Always traveling.
- Yeah?
Anything he can do to avoid me.
Well
No, your dad and I lost
a lot of brothers in the war.
When you went down
and signed up,
it flipped a switch in his head.
When your best buddy
is bleeding out in your arms,
it's hard to imagine
that your own child's gonna go
through that experience.
You know, sometimes it's better
not to feel love, you know?
Not to hurt.
So, I'll ask again.
How's the memory?
Look, I'm sorry
for whatever I did.
I'll turn myself in
and I'll cooperate.
The most important thing
is you have to come find me.
We have a serious
hostage situation here.
Multiple cartel members
have swarmed this place.
And they're about to start
dropping innocents like flies.
Hostages? This
is a federal issue now.
I'm ordering 18 eggs,
extra jalapeños.
I'll bring the spice,
you stay put. Capiche?
I'm assuming you found me.
You're in a Mexican hospital.
We'll be there soon,
so stay alive till then.
Just get to the back end
of the hospital at sunrise.
I'll make sure you
get treated respectfully.
I'm not sure what
to say right now, Cain.
I guess I put
too much faith in you.
This one hurts.
I'm not gonna lie.
We're ready to move out.
Let's go!
We'll pull Cain out at the back
before this shit goes down.
I don't want any mistakes!
You always understood me
better than he did anyway.
There's nobody
that understands you
any better than your pop.
You know, I'm the asshole
that took you out
there by the shed
and taught you
how to smoke cigarettes.
And you turned green,
and threw up.
- I remember that.
- Yeah?
Yeah, there was a few
nudie magazines back there.
I never said you were
a good influence.
No.
I said you understood me better.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you want?
I'm done playing around.
- What? No.
- No problem.
No! No! No!
Everybody, shut the fuck up!
Get on the fucking floor!
Cain?
Hey, Cain!
Shit.
Oh, come on.
Cain.
Cain!
I have hostages in the lobby.
And I'm gonna start
killing people in 15 minutes.
Cain.
You could end
it right away, Cain.
They're all gonna
die because of you.
Cain.
Your memory?
It's fuzzy,
but it's getting there.
That's convenient.
Not having a memory
and 20 million dollars,
and a grab bag of information
that can actually
destroy the government.
Cain.
Who are you really with?
Juarez?
Zetas? MS-13?
How funny.
The only three you name
are the exact reason we're here.
You know who I work for.
It's you I'm beginning
to worry about.
Just finish
the fucking job, Cain.
Come on, Jacobs. Let's go.
We're going too slow.
Please no! Please no!
No! Please! No.
CIA?
If this is a game
you're playing...
Answer the fucking question.
I'm CIA. You know I'm CIA.
I work with people
you thought were rumors.
Who?
Like deep state?
Illuminati?
It's a 3-D chess game, John.
The DEA, they play checkers.
But you know all this.
This is why you agreed
to get the case for me
in the first place.
You recruited me.
You knew that I was
an agent for the DEA.
"You can't stop people
from snorting and shooting.
They've been doing
it since Adam and Eve."
That's a quote from you.
Give me the case.
You can keep the money
you stole.
It's dirty anyhow.
It's not about this deal.
It's not about the next deal.
It's about order.
When you went off the grid,
you fucked up that order.
And now I gotta fix it.
You can't stop the crime.
But you can
control the criminal.
John.
I need you.
You can trust me.
Give me the fucking shells.
I have a walkie.
Be careful.
You want me to trust you?
You stay right the fuck there.
You don't move.
Eddie.
Cain.
Meet me on the fifth floor.
Let's get this over with.
If I'm not come back in ten,
start the slaughter.
Oh my god, this is different,
huh?
This is so funny.
We used to be friends.
Cheers. Dear friend,
for your life, old friend.
My friend.
You know
you can trust me, right?
I know.
It's been a privilege
to have a friend like you.
We're gonna make a deal.
You making deals
is the whole reason
we're standing right here.
Make a deal.
Or I put a bullet
right between his eyes.
There.
Out of your conscience.
Now, let me tell you...
Just tell me.
Did you bury it?
Did you mail it to your mom?
Come on, man.
Just put him out of his
fucking misery, would you?
Cain!
We made such a great team.
It's so sad that
it's gonna end like this.
Cain!
You are so pretty.
Time's up.
Motherfucker!
Chinga tu madre!
It's so sad it's
gonna end like this.
It's so sad, Cain.
'Cause I really love you.
Uh?
It's you.
It's been you the whole time.
You changed your hair.
That's what we do.
I love you.
I love you too.
You found the case.
Yeah.
I found it in
Dr. Garza's office.
He must have taken it
when they brought you in.
Garza always hated Eddie.
I think he was
planning on selling it,
getting out of Dodge.
Let's get out of here.
I don't know whether to
hug you, Cain, or shoot you.
Yeah, it's good
to see you, too, McCoy.
I can only imagine the
shit storm you just ran through.
I feel young just
sitting in the car next to you.
I know what needs to happen.
So if I can just get a shower,
maybe a cheeseburger and a beer,
I'm happy to turn myself in.
You bet. I'll get
you over to the embassy
and we can raid their fridge.
You know?
Is that it?
- Yeah.
What the fuck!
- Whoa, whoa, Cain.
- What the fuck was that?
- Cain. Cain.
- What's going on?
You just assaulted
a federal agent.
Whoa. Take it easy. Cain. Cain.
Cain.
You know, that
case in your lap there
it's never gonna see the
light of day. Forget about it.
You fucking rat.
Squeak, squeak. You got me.
You're supposed to
be one of the good guys.
What the fuck is going on?
You really hit that head
of yours hard, didn't you?
What's in this case that's
got everybody so excited?
What's in the case?
The whos, the what's,
and the wheres.
The puppeteers and the puppets.
The leaders and the members.
The avatars and the aviators.
What the fuck
is he talking about?
Presidents,
dictators, elections.
Broadway theater.
It's all fucking rigged.
It's all placed.
So let me get this straight.
You're telling me that the names
and addresses of the Illuminati
and Moses' tablets
are in this case?
Are you fucking serious?
Well, I don't know
about the tablets.
But from where I'm sitting, son,
you are a true hero
that deserves
an honorable death.
Perception.
That's what we manage.
Ask Anna here.
She knows all this.
Oh, so you guys
are on a first name basis.
So you obviously
know each other.
I really wish
you had your memory.
It's getting kind of annoying.
You told me that
I could trust you.
Love hurts.
You know, I have
this recurring dream
that I die at the beach
with a drink in my hand.
I guess it's not
gonna be that way.
So, just get it over with,
will ya?
I think I'll let God decide
how you go, McCoy.
Yeah, I remember enough
to know that I used to like you.
Adios, amigo.
Attaboy.
Goddamn!
Son of a bitch, you shot me!
You're goddamn right I did.
I just did you a favor.
If I didn't shoot you,
you'd sure enough be dead.
Think about that.