The forests of Pandora
hold many dangers.
But the most dangerous
thing about Pandora,
is that you may grow to
love her too much.
We sing the song chords to remember.
Each bead, a story in our life.
A bead for the birth of our son.
Neteyam!
A bead when we adopted our
daughter, Kiri,
born of Grace's avatar, -
a daughter who's conception
was a total mystery.
A bead for the first
communion with Eywa.
The people say we
live in Eywa, -
and Eywa lives in us.
The great mother holds all
her children in her heart.
Happiness is simple.
But who would've thought
a jarhead like me could crack the code.
When I met your father...
... I tried to kill him.
It was love at first sight.
Before I knew it, we had four.
When we sent the sky people back to
Earth, a few of them stayed.
Science guys loyal to the Na'vi.
And then there was Spider.
He was just stuck here.
Too young for a cryocapsule.
You wild man.
Hey Norm.
Orphaned by the war,
he was raised by the lab guys.
Spider, take your spare!
I'm just going to the village.
He wasn't part of our family.
He was like a stray cat just always around.
Inseperable from our kids.
To Neytiri he would always
be alien. One of them.
He belongs with his own kind.
It's mine!
I had it first!
Why do I have to give it to you?
Took a few years to get the language -
- through my thick skull.
- It's mine!
Lo'ak, you liar! Give it to me!
But now when I hear it,
might as well be English.
I hate you!
I hate you times infinity!
Lo'ak! Penis face!
Hey, hey, that's enough.
Don't make me come over there.
He's gonna come out from behind
those big rocks.
There he is.
There you go. Go get it.
Neteyam, the mighty
fisherman. Good boy.
- It's a big one.
- By the rocks, right where you said.
How tall is he?
He's that tall.
Goes by too fast. Like a dream.
- Kiri.
- Come here, bro.
Smile, skxawng.
Happiness is simple.
Like date night,
time away from the kids.
But the thing about happiness.
It can vanish in a heartbeat.
A new star in the night.
That could only mean one thing.
Ships decelerating.
Sky People returning.
One Year Later
Pulse 168
Okay, here it comes.
You're fine.
Stay calm.
Good pupillary reaction.
Colonel, can you hear me?
Colonel?
You need to lie back down, sir.
Sedate him! Sedate him!
Get outta here! Go! Go! Go!
- Get security.
- Grab him!
Hold him! Calm down, Colonel!
It's me, Corporal Wainfleet!
Lyle? That you?
Yes sir, and Z Dog.
And Fike.
Alright, let me go.
I'm alright.
Well, ain't this a bitch.
Stand By. Two minutes
to Pandora insertion.
Secure for Delta V.
Alright, umbilical cord is gone.
Pulse Ox: 89.
In case you haven't figured it out yet,
you are Colonel Miles Quaritch, -
only younger, taller,
bluer and not nearly as good looking.
In two hours I fly a mission
against the Na'vi stronghold.
Powers that be thought it prudent
that I do this backup.
Just in case.
And if you're watching, well it means
I did get my ticket punched.
Hey, Parker, just what the
hell am I supposed to say now?
Just remind him how this works.
Here.
So see this, this is all
your memories and your personality.
We're gonna send this back to Earth.
Where you are growing in a lab
as we speak.
We're gonna imprint you with it.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Am I doing this,
or are you doing this?
- Hurry it up.
Anyway, the idea is,
to get the minds of the
saltiest on world operators.
Yeah, like Corporal Wainfleet over
there and your humble narrator into your -
recombinant bodies.
You are a recom now Colonel.
Loaded with my memories and my charm.
What you won't remember is my
death because it hasn't happened yet.
And it ain't gonna.
Damn right!
Hell yeah.
Well whatever happened, if you're any clone
of mine, you'll be looking for some payback.
And Jake Sully would be
at the top of that list.
Remember kid, a Marine
can't be defeated.
You can kill us, but
we'll regroup in hell.
Semper fi.
Ground team, go!
Here, go!
Let's go, two minutes people.
Let's go.
- Bro, we have got to get down there.
- No way, Dad will skin us.
Come on. Don't be a wuss.
Lo'ak, get back here you!
Taking the whole case,
We're taking mags, the RPGS, the stingers.
- Bro let's go, come on.
- Lo'ak!
Take it. Take a weapon, kid.
Lo'ak, you don't even
know how to use it.
Dad taught me.
Gunships inbound! Fall back!
Come on bro!
Lo'ak, where are you? Neteyam!
Are you okay?
Where is your brother
- Over there.
- Get outta here.
Neteyam!
Oh no.
Dad?
- What are you doing here, boy.
- What the hell were you thinking?
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sir.
We're not in Kansas anymore.
We're going to Pandora.
I know you are all asking
yourselves the same question:
Why so blue?
For our sins of our past life, we have
been brought back in the form of our enemy.
That gives us their size, their
strength, their speed.
And with our training,
That's a pretty potent mix.
- We have a mission yet?
- Indeed we do.
Our mission is to hunt down and kill
the leader of the Na'vi insurgency.
The one they call "Toruk Makto".
Jake Sully.
Attack, attack! Got you!
Come on now, Tuk.
I'm definetly faster when I'm blue.
You skawng.
Seriously, and the animals respect me more.
- They don't think of me as human.
- Wait, you're human?
Ha ha.
They are coming!
THE FORTRESS OF THE OMATIKAYAS
They're coming! Kiri! Spider!
The war party is coming back. Come on!
Come along.
- Mom!
- Tuk, Tuk, Tuk.
Fall in.
You're supposed to be spotters.
You spot bogeys and call them in.
From a distance!
Does that sound familiar? Jesus, I let
you two geniuses fly a mission
And you disobey direct orders.
Kiri, can you go help your
grandmother with the wounded.
My brother is wounded
- Tuk, go with her.
- Father, I take full responsibility.
Yes, because you are the older brother,
you gotta act like it.
- MaJake, your son is actually bleeding.
- Mother, it's fine, I -
Go and get patched up.
Go on, dismissed.
You do understand that you
almost got your brother killed.
Yes, sir.
You're grounded.
No flying for a month.
Now see to the Ikrans. All of them.
And get that crap off your face.
- Aw! A little kiss on the boo boo.
- Give him this.
- I would use yalnabark.
- Oh you would? And who is Tsahik?
You are, grandma, move. You
are, grandma but yalnabark is better.
- It stings less.
- Mighty warriors.
What is it?
Neteyam and Lo'ak try
to live up to you.
It's hard for them.
I know.
You are hard on them.
I am their father.
That's my job.
This is not a squad.
It is a family.
I thought we had lost him.
- Hi there.
- Hey, Spider.
- Your ass is mine.
- I'm right here.
Avatars only. Go around.
- The blue stripes don't make you any bigger bro.
- I can still kick your ass.
- Hell of a day.
- Home run.
Yeah, haha. Real hysterical guys.
You know what really sucks though.
You can breathe Earth air for hours.
I can only breathe
your air for like ten seconds.
Yes, monkey boy. That really sucks,
For you.
- Hey, Max.
- Hey, kids.
Hey, what's up Max.
Lo'ak.
Hi Mom.
Maybe I'm just losing it out here
but I see real evidence -
of a systemic response
on a global level.
I can not...
I will not use the
word "intelligence".
"Awareness" is
probably a better word.
It's as if the entire
biosphere on Pandora -
is aware and capable
of this cognitive response.
Oh crap, I can't say that.
They'll crucify me.
So, who do you think
knocked her up?
- Pretty sure it was Norm.
- Totally.
- You don't deserve to live.
- Think about it.
He is the teachers pet.
He's out at the lab with her all the time.
I would kill myself.
I would drink acid.
Bro, you're right! He's like in every shot.
Look, he's giving her the looks!
Hey!
See, I'm thinking their two avatars
together out in the woods…
... All alone.
Gross!
Guys, I mean, Sometimes it's not
so great to know who your father was.
Whatever. I don't
even remember him.
No, Spider...
Dude.
Spider...
You are not him.
BRIDGEHEAD CITY
Go! Go! Go! Inside the terminal!
No stay! Go!
Masks off.
Colonel, it's the general.
General Ardmore.
Nice to meet you, Colonel.
I hear good things.
But a lot has changed since
your last tour here. Walk with me.
The new command center,
it's over here, that just came online.
The sworn assemblers can put up
a building in six days.
We have done more here in a year
than in the previous thirty years.
We are not here to run a mine, Colonel. As on world
commander, I have been charged with a greater mission.
Earth is dying.
Our task here is to tame this frontier.
Nothing less than to make Pandora
the new home for humanity.
But before we can do that, we
need to pacify the hostiles
Sully's raids are becoming
bolder and more frequent.
His attacks are well executed. Got tight
coordination between his ground and air assets.
These forces are hitting our outline sites.
Mines, Pipelines, cutting off our supply chain.
They hit a mag
train two days ago.
- Any intel on Sully's base of operations?
- Yeah. Bring up the mountains.
It's a cave system in
the Hallelujah Mountains somewhere.
But every time we send our forces
up there, we take losses.
Our hardware really
stirs up the hornets nest.
We only get ten minutes in enemy
airspace they are all over us.
Colonel, we believe your blue team
will be perceived as indigenous-
and will not trigger
the immune response.
And how might we test
that hypothesis, General?
The hard way.
Outstanding.
- We are entering hostile airspace.
- Copy that.
- Go, monkey boy!
- Guys! Wait up!
- Tuk, come on.
- Okay, okay.
Bro why did you bring her anyway?
She's such a crybaby. "I'm telling. You're
not supposed to go to the battlefield."
I'll tell mom if you don't let me come."
Don't pick on her.
Come on.
- Oh sick!
- Are there any dead bodies up there?
No shit.
Kiri? Kiri.
Kiri. Kiri...
- Are you okay?
- I was doing that thing again, wasn't I?
Yeah, you were.
Tuk - Kiri!
Lo'ak - Kiri!
- Kiri, we have to get back.
- Come on.
What is it?
We're always supposed
to be home by eclipse.
- Way too big for a human.
- Avatars?
Maybe, they're for sure not ours.
- What are you doing?
- Shh, I'm tracking.
Watch your six.
Clear.
Moving up.
Damn.
We are never supposed to come here.
Dad is going to ground you.
- Dad is going to ground you.
- Shhhhh. Stop.
For life.
Bro, we have got to
check this out, let's go.
Bro, that's where your
dad and my dad fought.
- That's your dads actual suit.
- Holy shit...
Lyle, see if you can pull
some data off that dashcam.
- Thing is deader than shit, Colonel.
- So were we.
- Better call this in.
- No bro, we're gonna get in trouble.
Let's go.
- Devil Dog, This is Eagle Eye, over.
- Eagle Eye, send your traffic.
I've got eyes on some guys.
They look like avatars-
but they're in full camo and carrying
AR's. There are six of them, over.
What's your pos, over?
We are at the old shack.
Who's we?
Me, Spider, Kiri...
and Tuk.
Son, you listen to me very
carefully. Pull back right now.
Do not make a sound.
- Get the hell out of there. Move, copy?
- Yes sir, moving out.
See I told you.
Dad, I know a quick way!
- You're going to be in so much trouble.
- Kiri, stop.
Guys, come on.
It's almost eclipse, come on.
- Put it down or I'll shoot you!
- With me.
- Drop it!
- Right now!
Put it down, put it down.
Get over here. Down on your
knees! Stop fighting.
- Check them for weapons.
- Kiri!
Be calm.
Shut up! Don't move.
What have we here?
Look, Colonel. Check it out four
fingers, we've a half-breed.
Shit.
Show me your fingers.
You're his, aren't you?
You're his alright.
Where is he?
Unfortunately I
don't speak English -
with assholes.
Where is your father?
Really? You wanna play it this way.
Shut up!
- Kiri!
- No! Stop! Hey! Hey! Don't touch her!
Don't hurt her please.
- Don't move.
- What's your name, kid?
Spider, Socorro.
Miles?
Nobody calls me that.
I'll be damned. I figured
they sent you back to Earth.
You can't put babies in cryo, dipshit.
What do we do, boss?
Iron Sky, Blue on Actual
- Blue on Iron Sky, send your traffic.
- We are standing by for extract, over.
- Take us in.
- Dragonfly coming left.
We are go for extract.
Be advised. We're bringing
high value prisoners.
Let us go!
Shut up!
- Sit tight, we're inbound.
- Bingo in ten.
We're on the clock.
Lyle, get me some audio on this.
- It's Sully's woman.
- She's a wild animal.
Give up, Quaritch.
- Sully.
- It's all over.
Nothing's over
while I'm breathing.
I was hoping you would say that.
- You stay with the Ikrans.
- Dad, I'm a warrior like you.
I'm supposed to fight.
Neyteyam.
I won't say it again.
Yes, sir.
There is nothing after that.
Should we salvage the remains?
Blue 1, we'll be there
in three minutes.
Three minutes.
Watch our 6.
Shut up!
Shut up.
Contact made!
Lo'ak!
You little shit!
- Tuk, come on!
- Race!
Come along!
In cover!
Come now!
Is that you, Mrs. Sully? I
recognize your calling card.
Come on out, Mrs. Sully. The
two of us have some unfinished business.
Demon! I will kill you as
many times as I have to.
You and the Corporal have been
pretty busy, haven't you?
Got yourself a whole
litter of half-breeds.
Na'vi!
Go! Go! Go!
Are you okay, boy?
Follow me. Ready?! Ready?!
Move!
Come on!
- Go! Go! Go!
- After them!
Spider?
- Spider!
- Kiri!
Come here!
Spider is down there!
- Then we are ahead. We have ten minutes.
- Blue 1, back to the collection point.
- Blue 1, fall back.
- Back!
Back, back! Take off!
Kiri, come on! Come on!
Run, run, run!
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm fine.
Tuk, are you hurt?
There we're clear.
Is everyone okay?
Tuk!
It's okay.
Thank you, Great Mother, thank you.
Where is Spider?
They took him. They took him.
Take it easy, honey.
He's a tough kid.
He'll be okay.
We're all gonna be okay.
Let me out!
He's completely ferile.
He thinks he is one of them.
This thing, this Quaritch, whatever he is,
he can walk right in here under Eywa's nose.
- This is our family. This is our home.
- This is our family. It's about our little ones.
I can not. You can not ask this.
I cannot leave my
people. I will not.
He's hunting us. He's
targeting our family.
You can not ask this. The children, everything
they've ever known, the forest. This is our home!
He had our children. He
had them under his knife.
My father gave me this bow
as he lay dying.
He said to protect the
people. You are Toruk Makto!
This will protect the people. Quaritch
has Spider and that kid knows everything.
- He knows our whole operation.
- He can lead them right in here.
If the people harbor us,
they will die.
Do you understand?
I got nothing. I got no plan.
But I can protect this family,
that I can do.
But I know one thing.
Wherever we go,
This family is our fortress.
- Where's Jake Sully?
- I do not know!
- We know, you know.
Form a picture in your mind. Is
it one of the floating mountains?
- Let me outta here!
- He's fighting this, give us a minute.
Form a thought, and we'll see it.
- I do not know!
- I don't like this anymore than you do.
- Which clans would be harboring him.
- I don't know! You're gonna have to kill me.
Watch this he's peaking all over.
It won't stop until you
give us something.
Where is he?
I don't know, you butt holes.
I don't know!
General, let me try the personal angle.
He is not your son.
Easy, tiger, easy.
We good?
Kid, you got heart. The science pukes
leaned on you pretty hard -
but you gave them nothing.
I respect that.
I thought you might want this.
This is Colonel Miles
Quaritch. Deceased.
Killed in action.
I'm not that man.
But I do have his memories.
Enough to know that -
well he wasn't always the
best father.
But that is not an apology.
I'm not your father. Technically,
you and I, we're nothing to each other.
But I can help you. I
can get you out of here.
I won't ask you to betray Jake Sully.
You would never do that. You are loyal.
And I admire loyalty.
Now just ride along.
Otherwise I gotta give
you back to the lab coats.
This is like stones in my heart.
Tarsem is young but wise. He
will become a strong olo'eyktan.
The leader must die...
so the leader can be born.
Toruk Makto will disappear.
The people will be safe.
A father protects. It's what
gives him meaning.
One life ends.
Another begins.
Oh, Tuk...
The sea clans inhabit a world of
their own. Thousands of islands.
An unknown area where we will be
able to disappear without a trace.
Are we there yet?
AWA'ATLU, IN METKAYINA-VILLAGE
Hey, leave it.
Follow me.
Tuk.
Behave nicely.
Take it easy. Just be cool.
Look, what is that?
Is that supposed to be a tail?
It is then too
small to swim with.
Do not, Rotxo and Ao'nung.
Hey.
Tonowari was chief of the
Metkayina, the reef people.
- I see you, Tonowari.
- Jake Sully.
I knew him as a tough leader.
But it wasn't Tonowari
that worried me.
I see you, Ronal, Tsahik of the Metkayinas.
I see you, Ronal.
- Why do you come to us, JakeSully.
- We seek Uturu.
- Uturu?
- Asylum for my family.
We are reef people. You are forest
people. Your skills will mean nothing here.
So we will learn your ways, right?
Their arms are thin.
Their tails are weak. You
will be slow in the water.
The kids aren't even true Na'vi.
Yes, we are.
There is demon blood in them!
Look.
I was born of the sky people and
now I am Na'vi. You can adapt.
We will adapt.
My husband was Toruk Makto.
He led the clans to victory
over the Sky People.
This you call victory?
Hiding among strangers?
It seems Eywa has turned
her back on you, Chosen One.
I apologize for my mate.
- She has flown a long way and is exhausted.
- Do not apologize for me.
Jake.
Toruk Makto is a great war
leader. All Na'vi people know his story.
But we Metkayina -
Dad
are not at war.
We can not let you bring
your war here.
I'm done with war, okay?
I just want to
keep my family safe.
Uturu has been asked.
- Do we have to go?
- Shh, it will be okay.
Toruk Makto and his
family will stay with us.
Treat them as our brothers and
sisters.
But they do not know the sea.
So, they will be like
babies taking their first breath.
Teach them our ways so that they
do not suffer the shame of being useless.
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
(quietly) Thank you.
My son Ao'nung our daughter
Tsireya will show your children what to do.
- Father, why?
- It has been decided.
Come, I will show you our village.
This way.
Tuk, let's go.
Just up here.
This is for you.
Your new home.
Yeah, this will work.
This is great.
It's nice right.
Okay, Sully's fall in.
Remember? Family meeting.
- Come on, take a knee let's go
- Kiri.
What?
I need you kids on your best behavior.
I mean it.
Learn fast, pull your weight,
don't cause trouble, got it?
Yes, sir.
I want to go home.
Oh, Tuk...
Tuk, this is our home now.
We're gonna get through this.
We're gonna get through this if
we have each others backs, right?
What does your father always say?
Sully's stick together.
That's right, Sully's stick together.
This time with some feeling.
- Sully's stick together.
Come on!
Swim together with us.
What's wrong with them?
They are bad divers.
Stop.
They're learning.
- Are you okay?
- You're too fast! Wait for us.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
You are not good divers. You may be
good at swinging through trees.
- Come on, bro.
- We don't speak this finger talk.
We don't know what you're saying.
I will teach you.
Where is Kiri?
Kiri?
Who?
Kiri.
- Where is Kiri?
- Did you see her?
Get on the ship, find a seat,
and keep out of the way.
Let's go. Chop Chop.
Whoa, whoa, hold on there hotshot.
Listen up. There is a tracker
built into that mask.
We hit the ground and
you take off.
I'll have you back in 2 minutes.
And I will give you an old-school
ass whooping. Understood?
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- We up?
- Teams up.
Listen up. Jake
Sully has gone underground.
Don't matter, wherever
he is, we'll find him.
And his bat shit crazy wife too.
To do so.
We go Na'vi.
Full tilt all the way.
That means we eat Na'vi.
We ride Na'vi.
We think Na'vi.
And that starts with
speaking the languiage.
You call that speaking the language?
You sound like a three year old.
Alright, smart guy.
You just went from being our
monkey mascot to official interpreter.
These are Ilu. If you want to
live here, you have to ride.
Make the bond gently.
Feel his breath.
Feel his strength.
Hold here.
- Look at his legs.
- Hold on.
Everything alright, forest boy?
This is a warriors mount. Not easy to
master Perhaps you should start with an ilu.
No, this one.
Now remember, when you dive
back in, good position, very important.
I got this.
Yes that's it.
Steady.
I love her already.
Breathe in…
And breathe out.
Imagine flickering a flame.
You must slow down your heartbeat.
Breathe in.
Breathe from down here.
Breathe out slowly.
Lo'ak, your heartbeat is
fast. Try to focus.
Breathe in…
And breathe out. Let your mind go clear.
You are learning to breathe.
Come on, keep up losers!
I got this.
What?
Na'vi kids younger than me do this
with their bare hands.
- Jake Sully do it the hard way?
- What do you think?
What do we do, Cololnel?
This is going to be good.
Alright, move up.
It's you and me, cupcake.
Did I mention you're supposed to tie
the mouth shut first?
Thanks a lot, kid.
Move up! Move up!
Can you see them?
Come on, we have to move on.
Let's go.
Yes, that's right!
- That's right, Colonel!
- Get some!
Whose up next.
The way of water has
no beginning and no end.
The sea is around
you and in you.
The sea is your home
before your birth...
and after your death.
Our hearts beat in
the womb of the world.
Our breath burns in the
shadows of the deep.
The sea gives and the sea takes.
Water connects all things.
Life to death.
Darkness to light.
- I got it! Tsireya!
- You did it.
This will help you breathe underwater.
What is she doing?
- I don't know.
- She's just looking at the sand.
What did you say?
Are you some kind of freak?
He asked if you were a freak.
No.
Are you sure? I mean, you
are not even real Na'vi.
Look at these hands.
I mean look at them.
Hey!
Back off, fish lips.
- Another four-fingered freak.
- Look at his little baby tail.
- Leave us alone!
- He's not normal.
Look at his tail.
It is very cute.
You heard her. Leave them alone.
Big brother coming to-
Back off. Now.
It's your choice. And from now on,
I need you to respect my sister.
Let's go.
Bye bye!
Look at them, they are freaks
the whole family.
- Lo'ak...
- I got this, bro.
I know this hand is funny.
Look, I'm a freak.
Alien.
But it can do something cool. Watch,
First I tie it really tight.
And then…
It's called a punch bitch. Don't
ever touch my sister again.
Hold on!
Stop it!
That's too stupid!
Ow, my tail!
My ear! Let it go!
He's got my ear!
- What was the one thing I asked. The one thing.
- Stay out of trouble. Right.
- It was my fault.
- I don't think so, you've gotta stop taking the heat for this knucklehead.
Look dad, Ao'nung was picking on Kiri.
He called her a freak.
- Go apologize to Ao'noung.
- What?
He is the chiefs son. Do you understand?
I don't care how you do it.
Just go make peace. Just go.
- So what did the other guys look like?
- Worse.
- That's good.
- A lot worse.
Get outta here.
What is wrong?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Why should I not be fine?
Why can't I just be
like everyone else?
Oh, Kiri.
What's tree boy doing here?
Sorry, I hit you, so many times.
We should be friends.
Come hunting with us outside the
reef. It's where the men hunt.
- No way, I'm not allowed.
- I must be asking the wrong brother.
Let's do it.
Come on!
Keep up, forest boy.
Three Rocks Brothers
- You lived.
- That was insane cuz.
This way, I know a good spot.
Call the fish.
What a moron.
Hey, guys!
Hey!
Ao'nung!
Come on, this isn't funny.
Holy shit.
You are a tulkun.
You saved my life. Thank you.
Thank you.
Buddy, I have no idea what you said.
They hurt you, didn't they.
I'll try to pull it out.
Trust me.
Friends?
Yes, we are friends.
Bro!
I am sorry.
What is it baby girl?
Do you miss Spider?
Yes, but that's not it.
Okay. What is it then?
I can feel her, Dad.
- You feel who?
- Eywa.
I can hear her breathing.
I can hear her heartbeat.
She is so close.
She's just there...
like a word about to be spoken.
I know you think I'm crazy.
You're not crazy, honey.
So what does Eywa's
heartbeat sound like?
Mighty.
Tell him what you told me.
Do you like looking at the stars?
My father came from a star.
The one right there.
- Lo'ak!
- I'm in trouble.
Go. I will see you again.
- The boy has been found!
- The Sully boy, we found him.
Let's have a look at you.
He's fine. He's fine. It's
just a few scratches.
I pray for the strength that I will not
rip the eyeballs out of my youngest son.
No. My son knows better than to
take him outside the reef.
The blame is his.
Okay, let's go.
No. It's not Ao'nung's
fault. It was my idea.
Ao'nung tried
to talk me out of it.
- Lo'ak.
- I'm sorry.
Come on.
I got this one.
- Is this true?
- Ao'noung, what were you thinking?
Dad you told me make
friends with these kids.
That's all I was trying to do.
I don't want to hear about it. You
have brought shame to this family.
- Can I go now?
- Any more trouble, I'll tie a knot in your tail.
- You read me?
- Yes sir. Lima Charlie.
- Where were you?
- Yeah, what happened to keep an eye on your brother.
I'm sorry sir.
Why did you speak for me?
Because I know what it's like
to be one big disappointment.
Wish I had been there.
The ocean blessed you with a gift brother.
The tulkuns have not returned yet
and anyway no tulkun is ever alone.
This one was.
He had a missing fin.
Like a stump on the left side.
Payakan. It's Payakan.
- Who is Payakan?
- A young bull who went rogue.
He is outcast, alone and has missing a fin.
- They say he is a killer.
- He killed Na'vi and other Tulkuns.
- Not here, but far to the south.
- No, he's no killer.
- You're lucky to be alive.
- I'm telling you guys, he saved my life.
- He is my friend.
- My baby bro...
The mighty warrior who faced
a killer tulkun and survived.
You guys aren't listening.
- I'm listening.
- Lo'ak, come back.
You skxawng.
Payakan!
Good to see you.
Why are you outcast?
What happened?
It's too painful.
I trust you. You can trust me.
Bro, that's disgusting.
Faster!
We are here.
This is the cove of the ancestors,
our most sacred place.
Eclipse is the best
time of day to be here.
This is it. This is The Spirit Tree.
My beautiful daughter.
Hi Mom.
I'm so happy to see you.
But you look troubled.
Shhh, Shhh, Shhh.
My sweet girl.
- What is it baby?
- Why am I different?
What does the Great Mother want for me?
Who was my father?
Oh, my god...
- Come on!
- Kiri!
Kiri!
- What's wrong? What is it?
- It was a seizure.
Is she breathing?
- Get her to the village.
- Lets go!
- Good to see you.
- Neteyam, keep them back.
- How is she?
- Still unconscious.
There's no bleed, no fracture.
No signs of Hypoxia.
But there is interictal
activity in the frontal lobe.
She definetly had a seizure.
We can rule out toxins.
- I see that I am not needed here.
- You are Tsahik.
- Remove these things.
- Out! You have done nothing!
- Come on, let's just take a break.
- Hold on I have to take her IV out.
Tuktirey.
She said she could feel
Eywa, she could hear her heartbeat.
- That is classic frontal lobe epilepsy.
- Epilepsy?
You see visions and experiences religious
ecstasy like the one she described.
Plugging into The Spirit
Tree is some sort of a trigger.
You definetly can't let
her do that anymore.
What? Ever?
Jake, if she seizes
underwater again, it could kill her.
Kiri, you are awake.
Kiri, my sweet child.
My sweet little girl.
Okay this one: "I see you."
That's what I just said, isn't it?
Not Naati. Ngaati.
Okay, it's going out
through the nose or something.
Boss, one of the patrols picked
up a radar hit. A rogue gunship.
- Where?
- Eastern sea, 2 clicks north.
Hang on.
The signal disappeared
out over the open sea.
But if you project the track,
it hits this island group.
That's hundreds of islands.
That's a big search box.
Lots of villages.
This is our guy. Give me ships and aircraft
I will bring you with his scalp.
- Bogeys, inbound.
- Skipper.
- All stop.
- Yes.
Hey.
Are you Scoresby?
Are you the asshole
who's commandeering my ship?
That would be me.
The target is pretty much
this whole island group.
I've never been up there. You know those
waters Doc. What kind of indigenous we got?
Metkayina mostly. Some Ta'unui,
maybe 50 villages.
Uh you are? Who?
Ian Garvin, marine biologist.
50 villages, 100 villages I don't care
we'll search them all.
I hunt tulkuns. That's what
I'm rigged for. That's all my guys do.
I have quotas to meet..
I'll be nice once, and then I won't.
If you can't get out of
it, get into it.
- All crews at their stations!
- Hey, don't touch.
- Now bring her up, flight speed.
- Flight speed ay.
- What was that?
- What's going on?
The Tulkuns have returned! Everybody, our
brothers and sisters have returned.
In their endless cycle of migration.
The Tulkun had come home.
- Kiri, come on. Come on.
- Tuk, leave me alone.
- What do you want?
- Look!
- Come on.
- Let's go meet them.
Look, It's my spirit sister.
Sister, I see you.
I see you, sister. I am happy.
Your son is very beautiful.
Thanks. How is your baby?
My baby is strong.
I met a boy.
It was a time for stories of
their season apart.
Of death and births.
Of old friends and new loves.
TA'UNUI-VILLAGE
Be calm.
We are looking for weapons,
radios, technical equipment.
Down on your knees!
Shut up!
We know this man resides somewhere
here on the islands.
Here in this village?
We are a totally different clan. The man
in the picture is from the forest.
- What is he saying?
- They never saw him, these are sea people.
Forest people don't come here.
I ain't buying that.
He must search in the forest
if he is to find that man.
They don't know anything.
Shoot that animal.
What the hell are you doing?
Be calm.
Are your ears working now? Now
you have seen what these can do huh.
Jake Sully. Toruk Makto!
He already told you he knows nothing.
Put her down.
Stop! Stop!
You make it real clear for him. If he
doesn't give up Sully, we'll kill the Tsahik.
No, I'm not doing that.
- That right? I don't want to be part of this.
These people don't know anything.
Are we really going to kill her?
You must not do that. What you
are doing here is so wrong!
Please.
- Burn the hooches.
- Hey, light them up.
Light em up.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Stop this madness.
- I'm sorry.
- We're out of here.
Don't touch me!
I'm sorry.
Let's go. Saddle up.
- What's wrong?
- Sky people.
They're looking for you JakeSully south.
They have a human boy who speaks Na'vi.
- Did they kill anybody?
- Not yet.
They threaten, but the villagers will
not tell them where you are on my order.
We must hunt this demon.
Trap him, kill him.
We've gotta be smart
If we attack Quaritch, they are gonna know where we are,
and they're gonna come here with everything they got.
Then what is our plan.
We are looking for Toruk
Makto! Has he been here?
- This shit ain't working.
- Nah, they're stone walling us.
If we turn up the heat he's just gonna
keep running. We have to draw him out.
I'm over it. I've got quotas to meet.
Do you want to
hunt? Let's hunt.
What? Here? Not here. There's
too many villages.
No no no.
Respectfully sir. You do not understand the
kindred bonds between the Tulkun and the ocean -
Na'vi. It would
be like murdering a member of their family.
If we start hunting here, the
hostiles will come after us.
Exactly. One hostile in particular.
I know how you feel.
I feel all alone too.
Tell me. Why are you outcast?
I am sorry. I'm so sorry.
It is okay.
You allowed this.
You allowed him to
bond with the outcast.
Tsireya... You
disappoint me, daughter.
And you are the son of a great warrior.
Who has been taught better.
Payakan saved my life sir.
You don't know him.
Sit.
Sit down!
Hear my words, boy.
In the days of the first songs, the
tulkuns fought among themselves -
for territory and for revenge.
But they came to believe that
killing, no matter how justified
only brings more killing.
So, killing was forbidden.
This is the Tulkun way.
Payakan is a killer and
so he is outcast.
- I'm sorry sir, but you are wrong.
- Lo'ak, you are speaking to the Olo'eyktan.
That's enough!
I know what I know.
That's enough.
I'll deal with this one.
The storm will pass.
Lo'ak, I saw something today.
I saw a forest boy
chosen by Tulkun.
I am very proud of you.
Payakan didn't kill
those boys. I saw it all.
The demon ship killed his mother right in
front of him, so he gathered the young bulls -
and the reef boys together to attack the
ship, and they were all killed.
But by the Sky People
not by him. He's not a killer.
No, Lo'ak, By the Tulkun way he is,
he bears those deaths.
Will he have to pay for it for the rest of
his life? He knows what he did was wrong.
He would never do it again.
- We must tell my father...
- No. No. I'm in enough trouble with my dad already.
- Your father will understand.
- No. He won't. He doesn't understand anything.
The whole clan hates me. Demon
blood, alien. That's all they see.
I see you.
You are brother of Tulkun.
You are one of us now.
- You got my mother?
- Mother and the calf, strong signal, range 4000.
- Bring it down in the hull.
- Coming down on it.
Sub teams, two minutes!
Let's do this. Let's get in there.
Hatches closed.
Come on!
Hustle! Hustle!
Crews to their boats!
2 minutes, let's make some bang.
Boat crew. Get ready.
All boats in!
Go!
We're rolling.
Standby, depth charges in.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
What's that? What are they doing?
There are echolocation sensors,
with which they navigate.
They keep them afloat
so they don't go deaf.
Picadors, get in there!
They're gonna cut the cow from the
rest of the pod using the sound cannon.
They target the mother because the calf
swims slowly and she won't leave the calf.
- Do they ever fight back?
- No, never seen 'em lift a fin.
Tough bastards to kill
though. Submarine teams, go!
- There we have the lady.
- Target in sight. Harpoons ready.
Here we go baby.
So we go in from below, where
there's gaps in the armor.
- Okay, that's it now.
- Get me really close.
- Hold it steady.
- Arm one.
- Armed.
- And rolling,
- Good strike.
- Arm two.
- Booyah!
- 3-6, you owe us a beer.
The bags slow her down and pull
her up towards the surface.
Bring me closer! Very
close. 30 meters.
Explosive tarpoon
10 meters. Get me
all the way in there.
Keep the boat
steady! Wait, wait.
Hold on to your ponytail, Colonel.
- Full power back!
- Yes.
Hold her!
She takes an explosive harpoon to the
chest, but she keeps running. Beautiful.
We can only get to the gland from below,
so we drill up through the palate -
and into the brain.
These are highly intelligent beings.
Probably smarter than us.
- Not smarter than me.
- Then the bar is set low.
I'm the one with the harpoon.
And yes.
- How do you know they are smarter than us?
- They have more neurons, more pathways.
Not only are they smarter,
but also deeply emotional.
More spiritual.
The area here corresponds
to our emotional center, -
but is proportionally
much larger.
They have music,
philosophy, mathematics -
and a complex language.
- Okay, here we go.
- Show me the money.
- So that's what this is all about?
- That's it. Amrita.
Bad luck for the big guys. This stuff
just happens to stop human aging.
Like stops it
Ounce for ounce, the single most
valuable substance known to man.
This little vial here is worth
like 80 million.
Think fast!
Do not do that.
It's never funny.
Amrita is what's paying for everything
here on Pandora now.
- Even your research, Dr. G.
- That's why I drink.
That's all you take?
You just waste the rest?
Drop the bags.
Let's sink her.
No, leave the bags alone.
I want them to know it was us.
I charge extra for being used as bait.
Her name is Ro'a.
She was my spirit sister.
She was the composer of songs.
Much revened, we would sing together.
She waited many breeding cycles to have
this calf. The clan was so happy for her.
What's is this, Tonowari?
What is this?!
My spirit sister and her baby have
been murdered by the sky people.
The war has come to us.
We knew about this
hunting of our tulkun people-
but it was over the horizon far away.
Now it is here!
You have to understand
how the sky people think.
They don't care about the great balance.
Now listen to him.
The Sky People are not gonna stop.
This is only the beginning.
You've got to tell your Tulkuns to leave.
You gotta tell them to go far away!
Leave?
You live among us, and
you learned nothing.
We will fight to protect
our brothers and sisters!
No no no.
If you attack, if you fight.
Then they will destroy you.
They will destroy
everything that you love.
Hear my words! Hear my words!
Stay calm.
Now listen to my father.
-Damn it. He speaks the truth.
Tell the tulkuns, -
that if they are hit by one of
these, they are marked for death.
Call for me and I'll silence it.
Saving their lives, that's
all that matters, right?
Saving your family.
Tell the Tulkun.
Go. Go.
We must fight.
MaJake... I will not stand and do nothing.
It's a trap, they want us to hit back. They
aren't hunting Tulkuns. They are hunting us.
- You're not going anywhere, little brother.
- I have to warn Payakan.
No. You've got to keep
your skxawng ass here.
He is outcast. There's no
one else to warn him but me.
Bro, why do you always have to make
things so hard.
No, you mean why can't I be perfect son
like you? The perfect little soldier.
Well I'm not you, okay?
I'm not you. He's
my brother. I'm going.
Is he your brother?
No, I'm your brother.
Lo'ak!
Let go of me.
Lo'ak! Come on, he's
going to Payakan.
Come back!
- There's Lo'ak.
- Loak!
- He's going to find Payakan.
- Wait up.
Hold on.
All crews to stations. Come,
let's make some money
Payakan! Brother!
Lo'ak!
- Lo'ak!
- Wait!
What's wrong?
Shit!
Stay calm. I got this.
Lo'ak!
Bro, help me! Hurry the ships coming.
Bro, come on.
Come on bro.
Call Dad! Call Dad!
Just go, do it.
Don't go, wait!
Dad... I mean Devil Dog.
Do you read me?
- Did you see where they went?
- Outside the reef.
- Lo'ak?
- Yes.
We are with a tulkun who
is under attack.
Gunships inbound.
- It is 2 clicks out.
- Who is with you?
All of us, Ao'nung and Tsireya too.
We're at Three Brothers Rocks
Get to cover and do not engage. Alright?
You hear me? Do not engage. We are coming.
- Yes, sir.
- It's getting closer!
3, 2, Pull!
The kids are under attack. They're
defending a tulkun. It's your kids too.
- The Demon Ship?
- Yes!
We gotta go!
Weapons! Sound the alarm!
- You should stay back.
- I'll ride!
Submarines, close the
hatches! Two minutes!
- Ao'nung!
- Hurry up bro!
Bro, hurry up.
Go! Go! Go!
Take it off!
All at the same time!
I'll be damned. Sully's kids.
- Let's roll. Not you.
- Saddle up.
700 meters. The signal is clear.
- Pull harder!
- Pull!
- It came out!
- Go, Tuk.
Come on! Get out of here.
Go that way I'll draw them out.
- Okay.
- Lo'ak, come.
Payakan, go! Go!
Tuk, grab on!
- 300 meters.
- Depth charges ready.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
No depth charges. The kids are worthless
to me dead.
Hold your fire.
Circle them. Launch
the submarines.
Sub teams, get wet.
Crabs, turn right.
- Don't lose them, stay on them.
- Blades up, I'm going in.
Oh hell yeah!
On lock.
Where is Tuk? Did you see her?
Tuk!
Target in sight.
- It is coming!
- We have to go.
Reset. Switching. Fire.
Hang on!
- Beware! Move your hand!
- Hurry up!
Hey kid, get back here!
- Drop your weapon!
- Put it down!
Stay down.
Get him, get him!
Put the weapons down!
- Drop the knife!
- Drop it!
- Hey, hey! What are you doing stop!
- Stop! Don't hurt them!
Stop moving!
- Spider
- Bro, are you okay?
Yeah, great cuz, never better.
Get back to the bridge.
Keep him there!
I'm going, I'm going.
Yeah, I remember you.
Cuff them to the rail, all of them.
Let's go.
Let's go, move.
- Over here.
- Watch them they bite.
Get on your knees.
Give me your hand.
Now the other.
Be brave.
Na'vi inbound!
Weapons up!
Dad!
Lose left, spread out.
Stop! Stop them!
It's Sully.
300 yards.
They have our children.
Your daughter, Tuk, Lo'ak...
Jake, tell your
friends to back off.
If you want your children,
you will come forward alone.
You know better than to test my result.
I took you under my wing,
Jake, and you betrayed me.
You killed your own. Good men and women.
I will not hesitate to execute your kid.
Just wait one.
Hold here.
They are killers of Tulkun.
They must die. Here, today.
It's me that they want. That's what all this has been
about right. The hunting Tulkuns and taking of our kids.
You brought this upon us!
You!
Then, it is me
who has to do this.
Offers fixing to expire.
What will it be?
Check your fire. I am coming out.
MaJake, what's going on?
MaJake?
Stay tense everybody.
All weapons.
- Easy shot.
- You hit him now, they attack.
Wait until he's on board.
Payakan!
Open fire! Open fire!
Brother!
Come about! Get me round.
Get me a shot! Now, now!
Switching rounds, go! Go! Go!
Get in there. Go! Go! Go!
Down!
Bloody hell.
Open fire! Open fire!
Sully's inbound
Keep an eye on him.
Come on, sit up!
Somebody shoot something!
Stop!
After them!
Leak! Masks on!
Get him out!
Hurry up!
- Damage report?
- Rooms 2 and 3 are under water.
Are you ok
- Port for the bow!
- Hard to port!
Get me a shot.
Got you.
- Get us away!
- Not responding.
- Cut the cable!
- Who has the harpoon now?
Full power behind!
Let the harpoon!
No cable, you idiot!
We are wrecked.
- Take your water pumps on.
- Man your weapons!
- Otherwise, I thought you were so clever.
- Close the food gap, Garvin.
Where did you go,
you cunning Satan?
You probably think
you're cunning, huh?
Because!
- The pumps don't work.
- All men aboard!
Get him on board a
boat! Hurry up, guys!
- Neteyam!
- Do you need help, little brother?
Now clap in and cut us free.
- Get Tuk out of here.
- Hurry up!
Who is the mighty warrior?
Say it. Let's get away.
Lo'ak!
They have Spider. We have to save
him. Come on, we can't let him down.
Let go of me!
No!
Se!
- Let's go buttercup, get up.
- I'm not your buttercup, you perv.
- We've got to go back for her.
- Tuk, wait!
Sully's stick together.
Wait, wait! Ready for departure!
- Check your mask, make sure it's tight.
- I'm good dumb-ass.
Hurry up! There
is an evacuation!
Tuk, this is not a good idea.
Cut here. Come on.
I got her.
We can still get this done.
Hell yeah.
I can't believe I'm tied up again!
- Come on bro.
- Let's go.
Thanks, guys.
Go! No!
Go! Go! Go!
Give me that.
- Go, go go!
- This way!
Take cover!
See them?
Bro, that was insane, cuz.
- Get on!
- Come on bro.
You skxawng.
I am shot.
Shit! Give me a hand!
- Keep him up!
- I got him.
- Grab him.
-Bro, I got him.
- Holy shit.
- Hold him up!
Bro, come on.
- It's okay bro, I got you.
- Go, go, go!
They have Kiri and Tuk.
I can't go back.
Dad! Help! It's Neteyam!
- Hurry!
- Here take him.
It's Neteyam, he's hurt! Shit, bro.
Hurry please!
Bro watch his head.
Watch his head.
Come on.
Just watch his head.
- It's okay, bro, we've got you.
- Oh no.
Pressure. Get pressure on it.
- Dad...
- I'm here.
No, no, no, no.
I want to go home.
I know, I know, we're going home.
It's okay, it's okay.
Dad, I-
Neteyam.
No no no...
Neteyam!
Neteyam! No, great mother...
Please.
My son! My son!
No!
My son!
Can you hear me, Corporal?
Yeah. I think you can.
I got your daughters.
Same deal as before.
You for them.
Where are your sisters?
- Your sisters!
- Where are they!
I do not know.
Where are they?
On the ship. They
are tied up on the ship.
They are at the moon pool.
On the well deck, amidships.
- What?
- Come, I'll show you.
Answer me, Corporal. Spit it out
or there will be consequences.
I have heard you.
Come on, we have to go. Come on.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Listen to me. They
have our daughters.
They have our daughters.
I need you with me
and I need you to be strong.
Right now. Strong heart.
Strong heart.
Let's go get our daughters.
- Stay with your brother.
- I want to go with you.
- You have done enough.
- Dad...
Hold fire.
Let's go.
He's coming.
I'm good, go, go!
Let's get this guy.
That's why we came here for.
- Stay with him.
- No!
Be careful, guys.
Go.
- Where are they?
- The middle deck.
There is like a pool in the center.
They are at the fort railing.
No, stay here.
Talk to me, Corporal. The ship is sinking
and your girls are going down with it.
Your son didn't have to
die. It was your own fault.
You thought you could protect
your family, but you can't.
Only one way to keep em safe.
So let's get this over with
before you lose another kid.
Get down!
- Who is affected?
- Zdinarsik, copy?
Clear.
Prague, are you there?
Look up!
Forward!
To the left!
To the right. Surround her.
Who's got eyes.
MaJake!
It's mother!
That's right.
They are coming for you.
Dad!
- Where is your sister?
- That way.
Stay behind me.
Kiri!
Running out of time here, Corporal.
You already lost one kid today.
You really want to lose another?
Do not test me!
Just kill him, dad!
Kiri!
- Put down your weapons.
- Don't do that!
Kick them away.
Do it!
No...
- Cuff yourself.
- No. No. Don't hurt her okay? Don't
Stay there! Don't
come one step closer.
- Handcuffs on!
- You son of a bitch.
Please, don't hurt her.
Release, or I cut.
What, you think I care about some kid?
He is not mine. We are
not even the same species.
Please don't, don't hurt
her. Let her go.
Please, listen to me. Let her go.
- Mom, don't kill him.
- A son for a son.
Please, don't hurt her.
- I cut.
- Now just let her go.
No!
Kiri, Kiri...
- Spider!
- Get them out of here.
- Come with me.
- I owe you a death.
Mom, come on. Mother!
You're not leaving, are you,
Jake? You know I never give up.
I will come and kill
your whole family.
Dad!
Then let's get it done.
Jake!
- The fire is coming!
- Back to the ship!
Stay close to me.
Tuk!
Mother, take my hand!
Mom!
Come on, Kiri, we have
to get out of here.
Climb up!
Come on, Kiri. Go.
Swim! Climb up, Tuk!
Mom.
- Mom!
- Go, go, go!
Keep climbing, go.
I got you.
Give me your hand!
Open it up!
- Open it up!
- Back, back!
Come on!
Tuk!
Up! Come on.
Climb! Get up!
We're rolling over!
Kiri, keep going.
This way!
Open it up!
Mom!
Come on!
Further, Tuk.
We can't get out!
- We'll stay together, okay?
- Yes.
Oh Great Mother help us!
Kiri!
- Bro.
- Mom and dad are down there.
- Grab on.
- I'm ready.
Okay.
Jake!
Dad?
Fuck.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
- Breathe, Dad.
- Neteyam?
No, it's Lo'ak.
- Oh, Lo'ak...
- Sorry.
- Neteyam's death is my fault.
- Just focus on getting out.
The air pocket disappears. We
have to go out. Come on, Dad.
- You know your way out.
- Yes, but Dad it's gonna be a long breath hold.
I can't make it. But
you can. Hurry out.
I can't lose you too, Dad.
Mom, I'm scared.
It will be OK. Stick
with me. Stick to mom.
It's okay.
You just need to calm your
heart and be completely calm.
Breathe from down here.
The way of water has
no beginning and no end.
The sea is around
you and in you.
The sea is your home before
your birth and after your death.
The sea gives and the sea takes.
Water connects all things.
Life to death.
Darkness to light.
- Hi.
- Kiri!
It'll be fine, little
sister. Mom, I'm gonna give this to you.
It will help you.
Dad, you can do this.
Trust me. Calm your heart.
Deep breaths.
Last breath.
Follow me.
Hang on. Just breathe.
Thank you.
I see you, my son.
MaJake!
Dad! Dad!
Come. Come here.
- Tu k!
- I have you.
Brother.
Sully's stick together.
That was our greatest weakness -
and our great strength.
Thank you, Great Mother. Thanks.
Let's move out.
My son..
Come with me.
Spider!
Monkey boy!
Spider.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Come here.
A son for a son.
Every song chord
must have a last bead.
A father protects. It's
what gives him meaning.
The people say that all
energy is only borrowed.
One day you have
to give it back.
Eywa holds all her children in her heart.
Nothing is ever lost.
Neteyam!
My family and I are
leaving tomorrow.
Far away from here.
Your son lies with our ancestors.
You, are metkayinas now.
And there it was.
We are sea people now.
This is our home.
Dad! Look what I caught!
Wow, that's a big crab.
It was over there by the
rocks, just like you said.
What's the matter, dad?
Why are you crying?
I'm just happy to see you.
I'm happy to see you too.
You try.
Okay.
- Have you left me any?
- Maybe.
Yeah, check that out!
I see now. I can't save
my family by running.
This is our home, This is our fortress.
This is where we make our stand.