Hey, let me out.
Open up!
Hey, open up!
This is Ryan. Leave a message.
Little Swann, it's me.
We haven't talked much
in a while.
Wanna give you some advice.
You wanna be
in this fucked up business,
you need a partner
to watch your back.
Yeah, I had a guy once,
Robbie Cole.
Wish I trusted him,
it's a little late for that now.
You are a good kid.
Yeah, I love you, son.
I gotta go.
Put down your weapon!
Now!
The 1873 Supreme Court
ruled when bail is reached,
the bail bondsmen can exercise
the rights of the court.
My name is Ian Swann.
This man is my prisoner.
Hold your fire!
Thanks.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Here you go.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Wow, beautiful. Thank you.
♪ I used to think
I could rule the world ♪
♪ Then God know
That I've tried ♪
♪ I've been down
So many roads ♪
♪ Then lost my reasons why ♪
♪ Thought I had it
All figured out ♪
♪ But deep inside I do ♪
Hi, Robbie.
What are you doing here?
Hey, Nikki. Have a seat.
Just working.
On your bar tab?
That too.
I got a jumper
on an auto theft rap.
Supposed to be
on the beach today.
Well, if you're looking
for Koa Kahale
you're not gonna find him here.
Well, you know him?
I know his family.
His mom works at the club.
You know where he is today?
Well, I might.
But I want something in return.
Oh yeah,
what do you have in mind?
Six bullets.
What?
Koa's a good kid.
Getting busted might just be
the wake up call he needs
but I don't wanna see him
get hurt.
Look, I'm a pro, Nikki.
I've never lost a client yet.
The bullets, Robbie.
You serious, huh?
Alright. Here you go.
You happy now?
He's trained to fight MMA today.
They're set up down the beach
by the banyan trees.
MMA fighter, huh?
This should be interesting.
You can have these back later
tonight.
Drink's on me.
That sounds good,
but if I have a problem,
unarmed, that's on you too.
It's another beautiful day
in paradise.
It's WB Radio Maui.
Morning news local businessman
Thomas Kane in today's...
just reminding you all
to get out there and vote.
Nobody near the cages unless
they want to get their ass beat.
Now, where's your
Aloha spirit, bro?
I'm just here to deliver
a little something to uh...
Koa Kahale.
Yeah, that's him.
No, no, no.
Not now, not today, man.
I know this guy.
He's not even a real cop.
Manu. You still collecting
outstanding warrants?
Those ain't lotto
tickets, buddy.
We're protected.
Take one more step
and see what happens.
Well, here I am.
And here's my protection.
Your fighter is now under
my legal jurisdiction. Period.
How bad do you want him?
Me? Not that bad.
But Maui PD, they want
the idiot who uh, skipped bail
before joy-riding
in their cruiser.
My mom's got heart problems.
I had to get her to the hospital
and that cop car
was just sitting there.
I was like,
what's the big difference
between an ambulance
and a cop car?
That is so incredibly dumb.
I actually believe it's true.
Come on. There's a UFC scout
coming, man. This is my day.
Look, you're either gonna come
with me now
or I'm gonna call it in.
But Maui PD ain't gonna let
you leave this beach
without tearing your ACL,
that's for sure.
Maybe, just maybe,
you let the kid fight today.
Then after, he comes in
without a fuss.
Think you can do that?
Maybe.
One question.
You gonna win in the second?
Get it on.
Let's hear it
for our beautiful ring girl.
Round Two. Fighters in position.
Hey.
Put another 20 on Koa.
And let's fight!
Hit him, hit him.
Koa is dancing.
The less experienced fighter
feeling the veteran out.
Come on, Koa!
This is the kid
I told you about.
Will be good to have
on our crew.
Kahale's in trouble.
Let's go! Finish him.
Goddammit, finish him!
Whoa. There it is.
Kahale has broken in
a choke hold.
Koa has taken out.
The match goes to Koa Kahale!
Let's hear it for Koa.
Nice, Koa.
Beautiful.
I'm so proud.
It's all for you, ma.
- Time to go, Koa.
- Police!
Koa Kahale!
Hands where I can see them.
Easy, honey. He's my collar.
Don't call me honey, Robbie.
Savannah, you know the drill.
Alright?
You can't arrest him
if he's already in my custody.
Then why isn't he in cuffs?
I got this under control.
Yeah, I'm with him!
This is bullshit, Robbie!
You give your profession
a bad name.
Says the cop pointing a gun
at an unarmed perp.
You got a warrant? Show it
or get the fuck out of my ring.
If this is your ring,
then you're harboring
an escaped felon.
I can pull your license
and shut down
this little shit show for good.
Guys, take it down...
Look, you spooked him!
Don't even blame me!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
Hey!
Hey, relax. Hey, relax!
One move and I'll light you up
like New Year's Eve.
Hey!
I saw you in pursuit.
Looked like you needed a hand.
Oh yeah? No, I had him. Thanks.
I'm the arresting officer.
You're Robbie Cole, right?
You knew my dad.
Who is this?
You're Ian Swann's son?
Alright, Bernie,
Koa Kahale was my bounty.
Tell the paymaster
to have my check ready.
Your commission
is a standard 10% of bail.
That's 100 bucks, man.
What? 10% of
10,000 is a grand, buddy.
There was a typo.
His bail is actually a $1,000.
I mean, the kid
is not exactly El Chapo.
Happy now?
No. Barely covered my bar tab.
Ryan, meet Savannah Tui,
homicide detective.
Don't get fooled
by her pretty face.
She's a real pit-bull.
I love you too, Robbie.
So, you're Ian Swann's son?
I'm sorry for your loss.
I've been on the case
from the start.
Then you must have
some idea who did it.
Look, Ryan, your dad and I
used to work together.
He made a lot of enemies
on this island.
Yeah. He had that effect
on people, so?
If anything, what we've got
is too many suspects.
Yeah, well gimme a list,
I'll run 'em down.
You're not a cop.
Yeah, I'm better than a cop.
Fewer rules.
Oh, shit.
Another bounty hunter?
This island's way too small
for another ass-kicking cowboy.
Yeah. Well, if that's
what you thought of my dad,
then you've got him all wrong,
which means
you'll never solve shit.
Hey.
Savannah's the last cop
on this island
that actually gives a damn.
You're gonna want her
on your side.
Give us a little time, Ryan.
Why don't you take
a couple of days off
and enjoy our beaches, okay?
What did dad do to get himself...
Hey, you got daddy issues?
Don't talk about him here.
I know a good, quiet place.
Hannah's bar.
You're a smart kid,
you'll find it.
Meet me there at four.
Go ahead.
Oh, jeez.
I know. Sharks.
That... that isn't much
of a body.
It's... it's just...
The body wasn't recovered
for at least 24 hours.
The DNA was a match
to his Chicago PD records.
They recovered a few things
from his car,
including his ID.
It's over there.
Yeah. Yeah, that's uh...
that's him.
♪ Accusations ♪
♪ Tribulations ♪
♪ Irritations ♪
♪ Liberations ♪
So, he left you a message
same day he got killed?
He must have known
he wasn't gonna make it.
Told me to contact you.
That figures.
He always thought
I owed him one,
but he was wrong
about that shit.
What do you say
we make it interesting?
Wanna 20 to the winner?
Nice.
Thanks.
Your dad was the real deal.
Little hard to handle sometime.
Yeah, tell me about it.
He was hell of a bounty hunter,
though.
Best I'd ever seen.
And a good partner.
'Course, then there was
that little misunderstanding
about your mom and I.
Wait, that was you?
I ain't proud of it,
but shit happens.
Hey, shit happens.
They got divorced over it.
You know that, right?
You... you ruined my childhood.
It was nothing, okay.
Your dad over reacted.
Your mom was half his age.
I think she just wanted
his attention.
What, am I just supposed
to agree with you?
Like I said,
I ain't proud of it.
I fucked up.
I lost a great partner
and a friend.
Do you know why my dad
came back to Hawaii?
Your dad hadn't talked to me
in over 10 years, man.
Word was, he was tracking
a real whale.
A big ass bounty.
I figured he must have died
trying to collect it.
You ever hear
of Terrance Billford?
Yeah.
Biggest bounty on record.
Set at eight figures.
Here's why.
Took out three cops
execution style.
I think Dad was obsessed
with him.
Well, he wasn't the only one.
I mean everybody in the game
knows Billford's story.
He skipped bail on murder,
drug trafficking charges.
I mean, the son of a bitch
was El Gringo Narco,
biggest meth operation
in the Midwest.
I mean, he killed cops,
even his own kin.
I mean, who allows bail on that?
Judge set the bail
at 10 million.
He didn't even think
that Billford
or anybody else
could ever pay it.
Billford paid in cash, man.
Then he walks straight
out of the court.
Nobody sees him again.
I don't know...
I think dad might have
finally found him.
It's a small jungle, kid.
I mean, if there was a tiger
that big on the island,
I'd know about it.
Yeah, whatever happened,
I'm not leaving until
I find out who killed him.
- Nice game.
- Yeah, thanks.
I mean, you let me win,
and we both know it.
But I'm keeping this anyway.
So uh, who's helping you
organize everything?
Organize what?
Funeral... the stuff.
Right, yeah. Look um...
yeah, that's me.
I guess, I uh...
There's not much left
of him to bury.
They gave me some things
they found in his car.
Including this.
Lelani Arms, yeah.
I know the hotel.
Yeah, if dad had
a lead on Billford,
I might still find
it here, right?
Look, your dad was a harder
man than both of us.
Whatever he was on to
got him killed.
What are the chances
I can convince you
to just stay out of this?
Look man, I didn't
come here for a tan.
Right.
Well, don't think I'm letting
you score a bounty
like Billford
right under my nose.
Without splitting it 50-50.
You wanna get to work or not?
Let's do it.
Mr. Buckley.
Oh, hello. How are you?
Wonderful to see you.
What a fabulous affair!
Now, my husband is telling me
that your plans for Maui
will make it a new
international business hub.
Well, I know your husband.
He's a very wise man.
And that's not
just because he chose you.
Oh, thank you.
Now, you love Hawaii,
I love Hawaii.
We all love Hawaii.
But, being said,
we have to diversify.
We have to expand.
And, with due respect,
these grandfather laws,
I mean really, it's like
every third banyan tree
is a sacred tribe.
We know. It's like the word
"profit" is a dirty word.
Exactly. And that's why,
I'm supporting Thomas Kane.
It should be our privilege
to expand opportunities
for all of Hawaii.
- Here, dad.
- Oh, good. Time for a toast.
Excuse me.
Everyone!
A toast to Thomas Kane.
The next great senator
of Hawaii.
- And who is this handsome young man?
- Mm.
This is my son, Ern.
And this is Mrs. Tilly.
- Pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
- Well, it's always a pleasure
to meet
a well-mannered young man.
And, his mother's here tonight?
No, his... his mother
passed away a few years ago.
But we're healing, doing fine.
Well, it would be our pleasure
to have you two
for dinner one night.
You just name the evening
and I will have our chefs
whip up some fine
Louisiana cooking.
That is an unexpected
invitation.
- Hmm.
- What do you think, son?
Yeah. Yes, I am.
Let's do then.
So, what's the plan?
There's too many eyes
at the front desk.
Let me give you the tour.
Yeah, it's me.
You know that bastard, who used
to partner with Ian Swann?
He just showed up.
- Jesus.
- Holy shit.
Well, whatever
they were looking for,
- I doubt they found it.
- Why do you say that?
Because they would've stopped
before they trashed everything.
Hey.
Whoever was here,
we must have just missed them.
We'll try to think like
your old man, alright?
He had evidence
on these bastards,
where would he hide it?
One of my guys spotted
Robbie Cole heading upstairs.
Cole?
That's not
a fucking coincidence, is it?
Is one of our men
still in the room?
Fuck no.
Hey, hey. Check it out.
Billford.
Yeah. He looks dead.
I can't let Cole find something
you fucking idiots missed.
Housekeeping.
No thanks.
Turn down your bed, sir?
Uh, bed's already turned down.
Hey!
Get down!
What the fuck!
She's gone. Stay low.
Fuck, Nikki!
Shit!
It's gone to shit.
Jam the police band.
Copy that.
What's happening?
The guy jumped overboard.
From the tenth floor?
Is he dead?
I can't tell.
He hit the goddamn pool pond.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm so sorry.
There's been a disturbance
next door
and I'm told that we need
to evacuate immediately.
I apologize
but please allow Maui's best
to escort you to your cars.
And have a wonderful night.
Don't forget to...
to vote for Thomas Kane.
What the fuck is happening?
I think he still might be
under the water.
Well, finish him. And don't
stop till the fucking body floats.
Freeze!
Ryan Swann!
Let's go, come with me.
Somebody wants to talk to you.
Get in.
- Where am I going?
- Nowhere.
Now, get your ass in the car
or go back in the cell.
Doesn't matter to me.
Coffee?
No thanks.
Oh, that's a shame.
Double espresso.
Vanilla spiced, seasoned huh.
I'm Buckley.
Pleasure to meet you.
Hey, you wanna tell me
what I'm doing here?
Well, it's just
a friendly conversation,
that's all.
Do you know
why I have a double espresso?
Because I didn't sleep
last night.
Those fireworks in the hotel
were spectacular.
I thought it was a goddamn
fourth of July.
Put an early end
to a party of mine.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Hm.
And I understand that
you are lucky to be alive.
It's funny I don't feel lucky.
I wouldn't either.
You lost your father.
Very sorry about that.
My sympathies.
Did you know him?
Well, I met him once only
but he did made quite
an impression on me.
Mr. Buckley?
The gentleman over there
just told me
to put his drink on your bill.
You know him?
I have no idea who he is.
So, why don't you go over there
and ask him who he is?
And if he doesn't have
the right answer,
make sure that
he doesn't bother us again.
Your man needed some fresh air.
Do you mind?
Well, let's see you have managed
to invite yourself to my table
and interrupt my dinner.
Now, who the hell are you?
My name is Swann, like the bird.
Now, why would I buy you
a drink, Mr. Swann?
I'm looking for a friend
of yours.
I have no idea who this is.
And if I did,
why the hell would I tell you?
Now, if you don't mind,
I would like to go back to
my delicious Wagyu steak.
You're funding a candidate
for Senator.
If this man is anyone near you,
you need my help.
Are you saying that
this man is dangerous?
The FBI thinks so.
What about you, Mr. Swann?
Are... are you dangerous?
Not to my friends.
Well, that's too bad.
Because I have enough friends.
Funny, he said
the same kind of thing.
Thanks for the drink.
You find out everything you can
about that son of a bitch.
You got it, boss.
Ah, such a tragedy, really.
Did he ever um, tell you why,
he came to Hawaii?
No. No, we ah... we lost touch.
Well, that's a shame,
now that he's gone.
Now, what... what transpired
last night though?
I want to forget about it.
It's kind of hard to forget.
People died.
I mean yes, but there's...
there's surveillance
cameras there
and I'm told,
that it was self-defense.
They fired at you first.
And now you wouldn't wanna
make a mountain
out of molehill.
I would just leave it...
leave it alone.
You're free to go.
May I ask you uh,
what your plans are?
I don't know.
I'm thinking of sticking around.
Yeah, someone killed my dad.
I wanna know who.
Hm, of course.
You will, you'll find out.
I mean, we're on it.
This is Hawaii's best
looking after this.
Why do you care?
Well, because I believe that
there's some bad players involved
with your father's death.
I liked to see them
come to justice.
Yeah, so do I.
Yes.
Now, a word of advice,
I would leave this island
and not come back.
You've got a bright future,
but it's on the mainland,
not here.
If you stay till tomorrow, I...
I can't promise
I can protect you.
Protect me from who?
I don't know.
Maybe... maybe yourself.
Oh, and by the way,
there's a midnight flight,
Hawaiian airlines,
and I understand
that they actually serve a meal.
Well, who knows
they might throw in
a complimentary pineapple
or a coconut.
Something like that.
Have a good trip.
Ryan! What's going on?
I heard you just got arrested.
Well, they haven't even
charged me
thanks to some guy
named Buckley.
Oh, of course.
He has a lot of influence
on this island.
So, I noticed.
So, I've been taken off
your father's case.
Apparently being seen with you
is bad for my career.
None of this makes any sense.
You know,
what I'm really worried about
right now is Robbie.
I've been looking for him.
Was he with you last night?
Yeah, last time I saw him,
he had a bag pulled
over his head.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, we have to do something.
Look, right now the police
are no help.
The whole case
has been put on ice.
But there's another way we can
find out what happened to Robbie.
There's some friends of mine
I want you to meet. Come on.
Welcome to the Rip Tide Club.
Nice place.
It's kind of above my pay grade.
Don't worry,
your money's no good here.
This is Nikki's club.
When I need intel
the force can't get,
she always comes through.
I'm about to show you
how we know
what's going on in this club
way before the cops do.
This way.
Gentlemen,
I need you to clear out.
Drinks on the house at the bar.
Ladies, ladies, gather around.
These ladies have given me
more leads than the entire MPD.
Sooner or later,
every bad boy on this island
winds up on this club.
And after a few drinks,
they just love to talk
to the girls.
Damn right.
Kai may look sweet,
but don't cross her.
She did two tours
in Afghanistan.
Semper Fi. Muah!
Oh, it's nice to meet you. Oh!
Hey, I like the vibe back here.
Relax, baby.
You look like a rabbit
in a fox den.
We wanna get a line on Robbie.
You can trust everybody here.
They're devoted to the cause.
What cause?
The locals, their land
and their families.
You taken him
to Paradise City yet?
What's that, another club?
It's better than any club.
It's the most beautiful place
on the island.
And we want to keep it that way.
The only problem is Buckley.
I take it you're not a fan?
Oh, hell no!
Mining is off-limits in Hawaii.
Especially the sacred mountains.
There are clan Elders
who control Home Land resources.
And Buckley,
bought off all of them.
What... what that's
gotta to do with...
with Robbie? Or my dad?
Maybe nothing.
Or maybe that's what
last night was all about
and the reason why Buck
is so interested in you.
Okay, ladies.
You've all heard about the hit
at the Lelani Hotel.
I need you to go out there
tonight, work the floor.
Find out who wants to brag on
what happened to Robbie.
- We got it.
- Alright. Go, girls.
- I love you, Ma.
- Bye, Ryan.
Go. Go, girls go!
Bye, Ryan.
Get out there.
That was a nice place.
It was only the lunch crowd.
I know, right.
I know it's only been 24 hours
since you've been locked up.
How you holding up?
I'm feeling kinda nuts,
to be honest, you know?
Back at the hotel, it was crazy.
Tell me about it.
I've never killed anyone before.
I put a guy in a wheelchair
once in Jersey,
but never killed anybody.
I know. I pulled your file.
Non-lethal force.
I admire that,
as long as you don't
get yourself killed.
You know, Robbie's gone.
I should be in jail,
but I'm not.
And as far as I can tell,
nobody else is.
Law doesn't work that way here.
Buck will spin it.
Yeah, well he already has.
Local news just claimed
that a gas main blew
at the Lelani,
nothing about a shootout.
Can you believe it?
He's that deep into this town?
Yes, and worse,
word is one of the Elders
was a hold out
on Buck's mining scheme.
One day he just disappeared.
There's no body,
so no investigation.
But there were rumors...
That the Elder was still alive
when they dumped him
into Haleakala.
You think that's
what happened to Robbie?
Ah, no.
Don't you count Robbie out.
He can take care of himself.
Okay still, we can't just
here and wait for a lead.
What do you have in mind?
I, uh...
can you... can you take me
to the crime scene?
Where they shot my father down.
There's not much to see,
the waves have them washed away.
But yeah, what are you doing
tomorrow morning?
Free as a bird.
Great.
Yeah. I'll see you.
It happened in this cove.
There were shell cases
everywhere.
And your dad's rental car
was up there.
It was shot to pieces.
He must have put up
a good fight.
Yeah, he always did.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Just ah, just give me
a moment, yeah?
What's that?
It's a very sophisticated
piece of equipment.
That's a beach ball.
It's about to become a part
of an underwater metal detector.
$19.99 on Amazon.
It's... it's brilliant.
- It really is.
- Yes, it is.
The dive team combed
this entire cove.
But you know what,
I think it's worth a try.
Little Swann,
we haven't talked much
in a while.
Just wanted to give you
some advice.
You wanna be in this
fucked up business?
Drop the gun! Now!
Yep, you're a good kid.
Yeah, I love you, son.
I gotta go.
Hey, what do you got?
I'm not sure.
Sleep is so important.
And it's something that
I did not get any up last night.
How did you sleep?
Ain't that California King
something?
I think it's the uh,
the memory foam.
Ain't nothing like in the world.
The bed was fine.
But the doors and the windows
were bolted shut.
That's a precaution.
Now, old buddy, old pal,
did you attack my people
at a hotel last night?
Did you kill Ian Swann?
I... I don't know.
What... what is an Ian Swann?
What about his son?
I think that my guys
dropped you on your head
when they were bringing
you here.
The kid you were with last night
was picked up by the cops.
But because they're friends
of mine, I let him go.
Why make enemies
when you could make friends?
But you... you're here
as a professional favor.
Oh, so you did me a favor
by kidnapping me?
Kidnapping! Sir...
That's what this is.
Oh, great.
Voila.
You are free to go as you wish.
Word is you got a lot riding
on this Kane getting elected.
Why didn't you run yourself?
What's the number one rule
of Hawaii?
Everyone's family.
Everyone is family
except for us.
We've been here for years
and you know what, the locals,
still think of us as...
as tourists, as colonizers.
I can raise a fucking
mountain from the sea,
name it after myself
and still...
You'd still be a tourist.
Still.
But there is a...
There is hope for these people.
A lot of untapped resources.
Yeah, and you'll get
quite a slice I'm sure
if he gets elected, right?
What's good for me,
is good for Hawaii.
You must be hungry.
Are you hungry?
Please.
Well, here.
Suit yourself.
You know,
my guys did some extensive
background research on you.
And you know what,
it was a page turner.
I... I couldn't put it down.
Well, don't believe
everything you read.
Mm-hm. Chicago, what about
Chicago? You left the force.
A great pension. Why?
Why would you do
something like that?
I didn't love bein' a cop.
But bounty hunting,
it's a whole different animal.
There's no rules, no superiors.
And I can learn a lot
about the scum I'm chasing.
You know,
there's a story
going around about you.
Oh good. I love a good story.
Especially if it's about me.
You're no billionaire,
although you'd like to be.
And this whole act of yours
is being bankrolled
by Terrance Billford
and his cartel buddies.
That's what I hear.
Ern, go upstairs and fire up
your video game.
I'll be right up.
Now, that is a good story.
Now, who is this?
Who is this Blifferd...
Billford...
Who is this?
Well, real piece of shit,
slung meth.
Big time operator back in the
day though. Made a fortune.
Well, I'm sure he didn't
force people to take drugs.
If they did, it was on them.
You're right to be scared.
Cause it wouldn't take much for
me to blow the whistle on you.
You know, see if you're running
this campaign
with laundered drug money...
The only thing
that I'm scared of is me.
And I am me, so...
There's nothing to be scared of.
But what about you, Robbie?
Maybe it's time that you tell me
where you heard this good story
and who else knows about it.
And why the fuck
would I do that?
Any luck?
The FBI gave us this tech.
It's supposed to help
reconfigure damaged data.
What about water damage?
We're about to find out.
Here we go.
Hey, let me see.
They're on the beach.
Do you recognize him?
I can't see his face.
Dad's body is bleeding heavy,
drawin' in the sharks.
Fuck. He never had a chance.
That's just weird.
What's weird?
That beach hasn't seen
a single shark attack ever.
There's no access.
They get hung up on the coral.
He's dead. I saw the body,
the blood tests.
I think there are people
who might be able to help us.
They watch over this part
of the island.
A watch over?
They still honor the old ways.
Well, where do they live?
This place Buck calls
Paradise City.
Look, I'll take you there
if you promise
you'll behave yourself.
Behave myself?
Uh, they're pretty touchy
about strangers.
Yeah?
I just saw that guy
you asked about...
Swann.
Where did he go?
I don't know, but he's headed
to Paradise City.
Right, I got it.
It's just beyond
these mountains.
I thought you said
this was a shortcut?
It is to me.
Come on, it's worth it,
I promise.
Oh, you're gonna walk
through there barefoot?
Yup. You ought
to try it sometimes.
Connects you to the earth.
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty
connected to my boots.
Fine, suit yourself.
When I was a little girl,
we never wore shoes here.
This is considered sacred land.
You grew up here?
Yup. My mom and her sister
raised me here when I was a kid.
I never knew who my dad was.
But that didn't matter,
'cause this place, the people...
it's all the family
I ever needed.
Are we almost there?
Just few more minutes.
Okay, well just give me a sec
to return some of my sacred
water back to the earth.
Oh, shit.
Holy shit!
Whoa! Hey, hey guys...
Sorry, I was just ah...
Shut your mouth, haole!
What you doing here?
He's with me! He's with me.
Savannah!
Yeah.
Hey! Auntie, look who's here.
Savannah!
My little girl,
so glad to see you.
But why you bring this
smooth talking haole over here?
I came to this island to find
out who killed my father.
His name's Ian Swann.
Is that true?
You're a friend or foe?
I was a fighter but yeah,
I'm feeling really peaceful
looking at that Remington.
Do you think you
could just ah...
Yeah, that's nice. Thanks.
We can always use
another fighter.
But you don't try fighting
with me, okay,
because you no can't win.
Ah-huh-huh.
Who's hungry? Let's eat.
After you.
No, okay. That's fine.
Come on.
Welcome to Paliuli village.
Locals call it Paradise City.
Lives up to the name,
don't you think?
Yeah, I can see that.
They're the only homestead that
refused to be bribed by Buck.
They're the resistance.
What's he saying?
He said he wants you to prove
that you're Ian Swann's son.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, no. Not that kind of proof.
Charlie's an old school Kahuna.
One of the last in the islands.
So, what does he want?
He'd like you to sit
with him for a while.
Cause he has a way
of knowing your truth.
Just the boy.
We can save him a plate.
Do I get to ask
what's in this first?
No.
Ah, something tells me
these aren't portobello.
Cheers.
Hey, we got to restock
the whiskey.
Robbie?
Robbie!
It's been nice.
I think I'll be going.
Thanks for sharing
your stash and I uh...
and I hope I passed the test.
- No.
- Yeah.
Be still!
Think of your father.
What did he teach you,
to help you become a man.
Not much.
Think of something.
I uh...
He taught me
how to handle a gun.
And after he left home,
I swore
I'd never touch one again.
I had to do things my way.
Hey, what more proof
do you need, man?
I can't just sit here.
No more words.
Picture him in your mind,
then we'll both know
whose son you are.
Go ahead, Ryan.
First, the barrel.
Not that hard, go easy.
I'm not like you!
I don't need to use a gun.
It might save your life one day.
I'm never gonna kill
anyone, ever!
Ryan, pick it up.
Ryan! Ryan!
He is your son.
It's safe to show your face now.
What the hell, Charlie?
I could have told you
that myself.
It's not just your life at risk
if you're found here.
It's the whole settlement.
How strong is this dope?
Because I... um...
It's me, Ryan.
I wouldn't blame you
if you'd rather see me dead.
You're alive?
Yeah.
Took a couple of bullets
but I'm fine.
You listened to my message.
That's a first.
Is that all you can say?
I... I thought you were dead.
I dropped everything.
People tried to kill me.
Easy, kid. Come here.
I'm sorry, Ryan.
Charlie,
what the hell did you do?
Old style lie detector.
Shit.
Better brew up some coffee.
Make it strong.
Your father first came to us
to learn about
that evil man, Buck.
So, the enemy of my enemy
is my friend? That kind of thing.
More than that. If Mr. Buck
wins, all of Hawaii loses.
We helped Ian that day,
because he was helping us.
They saved my life.
Oh. Not just us.
It was the island herself
that wanted you to win.
The tide dragged him under,
away from his enemies.
And we saw him
and pulled him ashore in time.
But what about that body
they showed me at the morgue?
It was a drowning victim,
borrowed from the morgue.
- Sorry.
- Yeah, but why?
I needed Buck to think
I was dead
at least 'till I got back
on my feet.
You said you had evidence
on Terrance.
I did.
And his trail led me to Buck.
I had all the proof I needed.
Yeah, whatever you had,
your intel is long gone.
I figured that.
I had a backup on my cell phone.
That's somewhere
under Honolulu Bay.
Well, maybe not.
That's a hell of a trick.
Now, let me show you a trick
Terrance played on all of us.
I got these from a surgeon
who lost his license,
working for the cartel.
Holy shit!
So, Terrance is Buck!
The devil may change his face,
but the spirit of evil
is the same.
So, that day at the cove?
I had Buck in custody
and proof that he was Terrance.
And it all went off the rails.
So, what we're dealing with
is more than just a land grab
by some dirty politicians?
I mean,
Buck is a stone-cold killer.
He's tied to the cartels.
He'll strip mine the land
and make Maui
the international drug port.
That's what they dream of.
Oh, wait. It's Nikki. Hey.
Robbie...
What? Okay, okay.
Look, whatever we do,
we better do it fast.
Robbie's being held
at the Golden Throne.
What's the Golden Throne?
Buck's own little kingdom
isolated on the far side
of the island.
Well, we've gotta get
Robbie out.
It's not that easy.
He built it like a fortress.
That's good.
They'll never see us comin'.
There is no us.
I do this on my own.
Yeah, isn't that how you
started this mess on your own?
Look, like it or not, Dad,
I'm pretty fucking good
on my job.
That's not the point.
Yeah, maybe this is.
I am going to Golden Throne.
I'm getting Robbie out
and you can either come
and help me,
or you can stay here eating poi.
Hey, we all need to calm down
try to work together.
Or Robbie's gonna end up dead
if he's not dead already, okay?
You're right.
She's smarter
than your last girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend.
Not with that attitude.
We're loading up the truck
to get you guys back in to town.
May your journey be a safe one.
Thank you.
Come on.
I love you, auntie.
Thank you, auntie.
I'm so worried for them.
Maybe they have a chance, maybe.
I'm sending them
a blessing of protection.
Auntie, let's go!
We must get the kids
to the school house.
I know who you are!
Just a coward with a bullet.
That bullet for me?
Burn this place down.
Hey, check it out.
The shit just got deeper.
Hawaii has suffered
yet another tragedy.
The Ninth Reservation,
sacred Home Land territory,
has been claimed by a fire
from faulty gas storage tanks.
No!
...part of the territory.
Six lives have been lost
with at least
two dozen reported injured.
To the Ninth.
A hui hou kakou.
Until we meet again.
Hui hou kakou.
Gas tank fire!
This is bullshit!
We have no way to prove that.
We don't have to prove it.
You gotta jack it
on Terrance Billford
and proof he's Buck.
That's all the proof we need.
No. Not after a hit like that,
they'll be ready for anything.
I know a guy
who can get both of you
to a safe place in Bali.
Yeah, we wish you could get
rid of us that easy.
Let's think about this.
Buck will be busy
throwing a big victory party
tomorrow for his donors.
There's too many eyes on there.
No, no, no, no.
She's onto something.
Maybe we can uh,
we can Trojan horse our way in.
It would be the last night
he expects.
You get Buck,
we get Robbie out alive.
Your call, kid.
You still in?
Are you ready for this?
If Robbie's in there,
we'll find him.
You got 30 minutes.
After that, get out.
It'll get ugly
when I take Buck down
When we take him down.
Just get Robbie out safe.
I'll take care of the rest.
Hey, don't mind him.
He still think he's in charge.
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Base keep ♪
♪ And the base
Keeps knock away ♪
Just keep smiling.
Spread out.
Check for any sign of Robbie,
okay?
Bye.
Drivers wait in the back.
Well, I'm their security. They
don't go anywhere without me.
You know, I'm pretty sure
your boss will be pissed
if the girls leave.
Stay right here.
Yeah.
♪ And the base
Keeps knock away ♪
Oh, we should definitely.
He's going live. Take a look.
I wanna thank the great people
of the great state
of Wailuku for electing me
to represent them!
- So, I wanna say...
- Thank you.
You have my...
And thank you so much.
Off to Washington!
You got your boy in office,
Terrance.
You sure he's gonna play ball?
He has no choice.
Don't ever call me Terrance.
He's dead, he's gone.
I'll call you whatever you like.
As long as can move
the type of volume
you're talking about.
As a matter of fact,
I feel a little placed out
here myself you know, post op.
Well, if you're serious
about that,
you have to acquire a piece
of property that you...
you might be interested in.
Everybody, raise your glasses.
A toast to Senator Kane.
And the new Maui,
which I have officially
renamed "Heaven",
because from now on
everybody's wishes come true.
Cheers!
Don't you ever doubt me,
mother fucker.
Thanks.
Hello, car door boy.
My ears are still ringing
from that time you
smack me in the head...
Yeah, as I recall,
you ran into my car,
not vice versa.
Yeah.
Nice get-up.
You think this shit
will fool anybody?
Your about to get your ass
killed in here.
Now, I thought
they had you locked up.
Guess they let
all the animals out, huh?
Buck pulled some strings,
charges were dropped.
Buck holds more power over
these islands than anyone.
And with the fall
of Paradise City,
there's no one left
to keep him in check.
Am I right?
Some of the best people
on this island... motherfuckers!
You don't seem too happy
about your boss's success.
He's not my boss!
I had family in Paliuli, okay?
He's sure as fuck not my boss.
You know it was no accident.
Buck's try to run them
off their homestead.
If you're here
to give Buck a headache,
I wouldn't say no
to your helping out.
And I wouldn't say no
to your help.
They're holding Robbie Cole
somewhere on this property.
If Robbie's alive,
he'll be somewhere
in the underground.
The word is Buck built tunnels
underneath the property.
Do you know where?
I can take a look around.
I'll get caught
if I'm seen with you.
Give me a few minutes,
I'll meet you back here.
Hey, this is a private party.
What the hell...
Swann's kid.
Die, haole...
Come on! Let's go, Savannah.
Come on, come on!
Come on...
My God, you think he'll drown?
If we're lucky. Come on.
I thought you guys were playing
on the down low. Not brawling.
Your pal Manu didn't give me
much of a choice.
This way, you guys, come on.
Guys, they know who we are now.
I have to warn Nikki and
the others they are in danger.
Meet us on the north end
of the property.
Koa and I will take
a last look for Robbie.
- Be careful, alright?
- Okay.
This door leads to a part of
the property they keep off-limits.
I've seen Zyatt go
from this door
and literally disappear
for hours.
Okay. Hey, hey,
let's try this the easy way.
Move, haole!
Hold it!
What are you waiting for,
Christmas?
How did you get down here?
Tunnels under the house.
Cowards always leave a way out.
You make a friend?
I'm a friend
of this island, sir.
I've heard you were too.
Good for you. Let's move.
Keep moving. Look at your six.
Oh, shit.
We're too late.
If you'd shown up
a few hours ago,
you could have watched him
jump start me
with that fucking car battery.
You wanna give me a hand here?
Oh, I got it, Robbie.
Koa, what are you doing here?
He's a mutual friend.
Ian!
Jesus, you're still alive.
You too.
Like an old cockroach.
Can you still walk?
I should be asking you
that question, old man.
I swore the next time I saw you,
I'd punch you
in the fucking face.
Wait, how did you manage
to stay alive down here?
Told Buck I had proof,
Billford was funding him.
Took a wild guess.
You're wrong just like usual.
Buck is Billford.
What the fuck?
You're always bullshitting me.
Shut up, Robbie.
Or I'll tie you back up.
Will you guys please shut up?
Now, Dad I get it.
That he hooked up with mom
on Thanksgiving.
Get over it.
And you, apologize.
I have apologized.
Ian, I'm sorry man.
I'm fucking sorry, okay?
I want that in writing.
I... I can't take this.
Let's get the fuck outta here!
Do you even know
where you're going?
Keep moving.
Shots been reported
in the basement.
Robbie Cole escaped.
Make sure he's dead
before he leaves this property.
You heard him, boys.
Hunt to kill.
Get the boat.
I'll get my son.
What the hell is going
on here, Terrance?
Calm down.
It's being taken care of.
I thought
you had this gangland bullshit
under control, Terrance!
Come on! This way!
This way, this way.
Come on. Come on.
Stay low. Stay low. Come on.
Go, go, go!
Hey, man,
I'm just looking for valet.
Don't shoot the guests.
Come on! Let's go. Come on.
You alright?
Alright, you guys go first.
We're gonna lay down
some cover fire. Okay?
- Move fast, stay low.
- Alright.
Alright. One, two... now!
Better reload.
Okay. I get the two on the left.
I got the two on the right.
What about the guy
in the middle?
Dealer's choice.
Now!
Come on!
Zyatt Dean!
Hands where I can see them.
On your knees now!
Make a move
and I won't hesitate.
I got 20 armed men out there.
What do you think
you're gonna do?
Arrest me and walk
out of here alive?
Who said anything about
arresting you?
If I shoot you,
it's self-defense.
And the world
becomes a better place.
Now, drop the bag
and keep your hands
where I can see them.
That wasn't so tough, was it?
Don't try it! No!
Where's the boat?
Boat's coming. Just off
that point in five minutes.
Hey, game's over!
Drop your weapons.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Koa!
Where are we going, dad?
Well son, someplace new.
You think of it...
Think of it as an adventure.
And don't you worry
about anything.
Hello, Terrance.
Sorry, did I shock you?
Drop the gun.
Drop the gun, now!
You piece of shit.
Are you too stupid to die?
You've been chasing me
for ten years. For what?
I'm a little OCD.
I gotta finish what I start.
I gotta admit,
changing your face threw me off.
Once I had your prints,
I knew I had you.
I have no idea who this is.
I'm taking you in.
No, I got other plans.
And what are you gonna do?
What are you gonna shoot me
in front of my son?
Doesn't need to get messy.
Just tell the boy to step aside.
You go, son. You go to the
boat, I'll be right behind you.
- No.
- No, no...
I'm not going anywhere
without you.
You go.
I got him covered,
he's not gonna hurt you.
Your dad's right.
I won't hurt you.
But he already has.
Worse than you know.
Don't you listen to him.
Did he ever tell you
how your mom died?
They found his prints
on her throat.
He's a fucking liar.
She threatened to leave
and take you with her.
He killed her,
changed your names,
stayed on the run.
Don't listen to him.
Just don't listen to him.
Sorry kid, it's true.
Go to the boat!
Just go to the boat. Go!
No.
Ern!
- Come here. You're safe.
- Come on!
- You're safe. You're safe.
- Here you go.
Dad! Dad! Come on.
Dad.
Just let me be.
Get down!
- Fuck!
- No, no, don't move.
Don't let that bastard
run again.
Take the shot for me.
Take the shot.
He's almost out of range.
Take it!
Kill him, Ryan!
I said I'd bring him in.
Dad? Dad! Dad!
He's gone. He's gone.
Come on.
Get up.
Sergeant.
Savannah, what in God's name
is going on here?
Mr. Arlene Buckley is not
who he pretends to be.
How you doing?
Dad will be proud of you.
I'm proud of you too.
A blessing, to all our friends,
both old and new.
You are a part
of Paliuli Village now.
Today, we honor those
who gave their lives
to protect us.
Our beloved Kahuna Charlie,
the young warrior Koa,
and your father, young Swann.
May he live on
through your good deeds.
For donating your share
of the bounty
so we can rebuild our village
and care for the families
of the victims.
We are all in your debt.
- Mahalo.
You did that, Ryan?
Ah, it just felt like
the right thing to do.
I mean, I kept 10%.
Leaves me enough
for a new start.
But what about you?
You okay now
after all we've been through.
I'm a little shook up
but every time I come back here
I just feel at peace.
At least Buck can't terrorize
anyone anymore.
So, now that this is all over,
are you and I still friends?
Well, that would be boring,
wouldn't it?
Ah, shall we?
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Well your mother
Just caught ♪
♪ And said that you
Had gotten involved ♪
♪ With a pretty woman
You knew right away ♪
♪ Your sister and a mister
Told me he was a quitter ♪
♪ When it come to loving you
You'll never stay ♪
♪ Now I'm out here all alone ♪
♪ You said that you loved me
But my heart is blown ♪
♪ I packed my bags
And I'm moving on ♪
♪ Cause there's too many things
Just going wrong ♪
♪ There's too many things
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ So been a long time
I sat her ♪
♪ We were dozing through
The attic ♪
♪ Headed to a really big show ♪
♪ One drink cause you left me
A bottle full to the rescue ♪
♪ To give me
Where I needed to go ♪
♪ When I woke
With a feeling in my chest ♪
♪ I knew she stole
With the thing that was left ♪
♪ Can't catch your brakes ♪
♪ So, I think you're gone
♪ There's too many things
Just going wrong ♪
♪ Look out ♪
♪ Mama said you boy
You better settle down ♪
♪ Now papa said
Son, you don't know ♪
♪ One day you're gonna drown ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ Hear my line ♪
♪ Hear my heart ♪
♪ Hear my soul ♪
♪ When I'm alone ♪
♪ There's too many things
Just going wrong ♪