Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
No. No!
No! Stay away!
My son.
Little Liu Kang.
Tell him...
Tell him he was loved.
The front gate!
- Hai!
- They will not take this temple.
- As long as we stand, it stands.
- Hai!
As long as
we stand, it stands.
Hai!
Ahhh!
Come get some!
You're late.
I picked up a straggler.
Stryker, Kung Lao.
Kung Lao, Stryker.
Did that thing have wings?
Did I shoot
something with wings?
What the hell is going on?
He's new. Where are they?
Where do you think?
Shit.
General.
What is it?
Spit it out!
We've broken the temple gates,
but...
We're experiencing
heavy losses...
We will mourn our dead later.
Reiko, Kintaro,
move to the front.
Push in from the opening.
Jade, Baraka, take the TaiGore
through the sides.
Leave no one alive!
Wow. That...
That seems a bit harsh.
There! In the trees.
Finally.
Yeah, I've been
up here forever,
it's about time you saw me.
Oh, my back.
Shit!
Whoa.
Whoa! Okay.
What do you want?
I've come to negotiate
a surrender.
The tiny humans
wish to surrender?
Tell him "no,"
so that we may crush them!
What are your terms?
See? A lady with smarts.
No wonder you're in charge.
Plus, that leotard suits you.
A little airy
for my tastes, but...
Nevermind. Kill him!
Wait! Sorry. I get distracted.
A few too many energy drinks.
Okay. So, pull everyone back.
Drop your weapons. And then...
We'll make sure you guys
make it out of this alive.
Uh, you're confused. I get it.
I usually leave this sort
of thing up to my agent,
but I fired him after he sent
me to that weirdo death island.
Now he's getting
ten percent of nothing. Right?
You wish...
for us to surrender?
Well, yeah. I mean...
Come on, you guys.
That's what... One, two,
three, four, five.
...Carry the four.
A couple of thousand of you
versus... me. Johnny Cage.
International action star.
It's hardly fair.
Kitana, he is obviously
mentally unwell.
Let me kill him
and be done with it.
I have a counterproposal.
Kneel. Kneel and pledge
allegiance to Shao Kahn.
Pledge allegiance?
Lady, I don't pledge allegiance
to anything
except the red, white,
and blue.
Then you shall die.
Let's do this!
Wah... Yah!
Bruce Lee!
Ooh.
Yeah.
I forgot.
I brought my girlfriend,
and... whoa,
let me tell you,
she is pretty good
with a rifle.
So? You guys gonna surrender,
or what?
Yah!
Whoa! Didn't I kill you?
Whoa! A little help here!
Nah. A lotta help. Now!
Huh?
I'm not your girlfriend.
- Well, not yet
- Ugh.
Give up now.
The two of you
can't hope to defeat
Shao Kahn's army.
Two? Who said anything
about two?
- Did you say two?
- Nope.
Well, I didn't say two.
If it was just two of us,
well, I mean,
that would be stupid.
Crazy even!
Lord Raiden... The chosen one!
Oh, great.
Now I'm getting second billing.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
Still on the wrong side?
I don't have
much of a choice.
And if you did?
Ahhh!
Shao Kahn.
Lord Raiden.
Huyah!
Ahhh!
Impudent.
Stand back, Liu Kang.
I have this, Lord Raiden.
Stand back!
Wise to listen to your Master.
Besides,
I didn't come to fight.
Of course. No.
You didn't come to fight.
I mean, these soldiers are
probably some sort of flash mob.
What are they going to sing?
"Thriller?"
That would be great.
Johnny Cage!
I could continue
to destroy your realm.
I have untold legions
that will die for my cause.
But... I offer an end
to the bloodshed.
Permanently.
You and I will travel
to the Elder Gods,
petition them for
another tournament.
The final Mortal Kombat.
Listen, shithead.
If you think
Raiden's going to agree
to another tournament
after we just kicked your ass
on that whacked out
island of yours,
you're an even bigger idiot
than I thought.
We've got another
1,000 years
before that has to
happen again...
Agreed.
I'm sorry.
Uh, maybe it's being kicked
in the head
by assholes
from another dimension,
but I thought
you said "agreed."
I did.
You can't be serious.
We're holding them off
on various fronts.
We can win this!
And then?
We may win for a time.
But Outworld is a place
of vast resources.
He will return to his throne,
rebuild his army and
attack again.
Why place the responsibility
of survival
on your children's children
when we can do
something about it now?
We should discuss this.
No. I have made my decision.
If we have a chance
to end this now, we must.
It's not fair.
It rarely is.
But such is life.
I accept your offer.
Then we shall go
to the Elder Gods
and petition them together.
- Be careful.
- And you.
All of you.
Mama!
No. No!
Papa! Why didn't you save me?
Ahhh. Good.
You've arrived.
Now... We can begin.
The island... Quan Chi.
He was a fine servant.
You have a lot to live up to.
Netherrealm has claim
to your soul.
And your soul...
It has something I need.
It was with you when you
perished on the island.
That type of magic...
is not so easily destroyed.
The key and your soul
are intertwined.
You and the key
are one.
My soldiers will escort you
to Earthrealm.
To the Temple of Elements.
You will open the gates
and bring me what's inside.
Then, my brothers and sisters
will see how "mad" I really am.
Or?
Or I will flay you alive
until you perish,
and then bring you back
to do it again.
You cannot escape me.
I can try.
Find him.
But Master,
he has escaped us before.
Then find me someone
who can do it for you.
Soon you shall
rise again,
and finally, the realms
will be no more.
Ahhh!
You've gotten better.
Not good enough.
You're too hard on yourself,
Kuai Liang.
You are a great fighter.
Good enough... for this.
With Outworld
attacking Earthrealm,
and Cyrax and Sektor
still missing,
it is time for you
to take your brother's place.
The mantle
of Sub-Zero is yours.
No. Not yet.
The Grandmaster requires
your presence.
Kuai Liang, Smoke,
I'm sorry to interrupt
your training,
but we have a new mission.
We live to serve,
Grandmaster.
We've been hired
to find someone.
Someone dangerous.
It will take the combined might
of the Lin Kuei
and even then...
Our target is a member of
the Shirai Ryu.
The Shirai Ryu are dead.
So we thought,
but I'm afraid one remains.
Hanzo Hasashi. Scorpion.
Where?
I will find him, Grandmaster.
I will find him and kill him
for my clan...
For my brother.
No. He's to be taken alive.
Alive? He killed Bi-Han!
Know your place, Kuai Liang!
This Scorpion...
is said to be
the deadliest warrior
the evil Shirai Ryu
has ever produced.
In order to catch this mad man,
you will have to be faster,
and better than
you've ever been.
We will not fail you,
Grandmaster.
No, you won't.
You can't.
I've made sure of that.
The Lin Kuei
have been experimenting
with something new
for some time.
And the results have been more
than we could have hoped for.
Cyrax! Sektor!
Cyrax? Sektor?
What have you done?
What we must.
The mortal body is fragile,
weak.
So, we enhanced them.
Technology and skill combined
to make the perfect warrior.
The perfect monsters!
They're the future, Kuai Liang.
And the future is now.
So, who's first?
You cannot run,
foolish children.
Bring them back.
Ahhh!
Smoke!
Go, Kuai! Go!
After you.
Lord Raiden.
Emperor Shao Kahn.
What is it you seek
of the Elder Gods?
Oh great, and benevolent...
We seek your permission.
Permission?
Yes. In your wisdom,
you have created Mortal Kombat
to prevent Outworld
from merging with Earthrealm
without a fair fight.
What do you propose?
A final tournament.
And the protector
of Earthrealm agrees?
Yes. Enough blood
has been spilled.
It's time to end this... now.
You would be wise
to know your place
and respect the gods.
And become a spineless welp
such as yourself?
Your petition is granted.
Then the realms are
as good as mine.
One more request.
I wish to enter the tournament
on behalf of Earthrealm.
Impossible.
It is called "Mortal Kombat."
Or have you forgotten.
You are a god and...
I do not have to be.
You are willing
to sacrifice your godhood?
So be it!
Ahhh!
Go. We await the outcome
with great interest.
You are a fool, Lord.
No... just Raiden now,
isn't it?
You are a fool, Raiden.
Before this is over,
you will beg
for your godhood back.
They're just sitting there,
waiting.
It's super creepy.
I say we call in an air strike
while we have the chance.
They're retreating!
Calm down, Stryker.
Yes, they are. But why?
To get ready
for the tournament.
Lord Raiden!
Lord Raiden, what's wrong?
You look...
I am fine, Liu Kang.
The Elder Gods have agreed
to our request.
A final tournament
that will determine
not just the future of our
realm, but the others as well.
A tournament? Like a... What?
Karate tournament?
It's a whole thing.
I'll explain later.
We must journey to Outworld
and defeat Shao Kahn's
mightiest warriors
to save Earthrealm
and countless lives.
Nevermind. That sums it up.
We won't let you down,
Lord Raiden.
I hope not...
Because I will be fighting
alongside you.
You?
But... No...
You haven't.
Haven't what?
What are we gasping
in horror at?
I have relinquished
my godhood
to compete in the tournament.
But without your godhood...
I am still a warrior, Liu Kang.
Where do you think the Wu Shi
learned their techniques?
Lord Raiden,
I am more than capable...
Indeed you are.
I am... How do
the Americans say...
"hedging my bets."
When do we leave?
Now.
Well, then. Uh...
Ladies first.
The guys at the station
are not gonna believe this.
Come on, Toto.
We don't have all day.
Huh?
There is no use hiding.
I know you are there.
I am impressed.
You have escaped Netherrealm
once again.
It was surprisingly easy.
I am sure Shinnok would like it
to appear so.
Why are you here?
The key...
From Shang Tsung's island.
Shinnok says its magic has
intertwined with my soul.
So...
You are the only one
who can open the door
to the last Kamidogu.
Kamidogu?
Remnants of the One Being.
After the Elder Gods rebelled,
they split him,
and hid the pieces
throughout the realms.
And if Shinnok gets them all?
The One Being will reappear
and begin to unravel the realms
until nothing is left.
Why would Shinnok want
to destroy everything?
Revenge.
Insanity.
He is called the "mad" god
for a reason.
Then take the key out of me!
Destroy it!
I cannot.
What do you mean
you cannot?
- You are a god.
- No longer.
What then?
Run. Hide.
Do not let them find you.
And if they catch me,
what then?
Maybe I should open the
door for them...
End it all.
You have long straddled
the fence
between light and dark, Hanzo.
It is time you pick a side.
I believe that is what your wife
and child would have wanted.
Not ominous at all.
Welcome to the fortress
of Shao Kahn!
Shang Tsung.
You will have
your chance, Liu Kang.
Still yourself.
Yes. Heel, young pup.
Continue to do
what your Master says.
Follow me.
The emperor's waiting.
Greetings, warriors
of Earthrealm.
Welcome to Outworld.
Over the next two days,
we shall determine
who will be worthy enough
to be called the champion
of Mortal Kombat.
As such, the rules state
that none shall be harmed
outside of the tournament
itself.
You may roam freely
within the fortress,
but not beyond.
Raiden, are you ready to begin?
We are.
Damn. And me without my bug spray.
Okay!
You know New York.
Unique New York. You know
you need unique New York.
She makes a proper cup of
coffee in a copper coffee pot.
I slit a sheet a sheet I slit
and upon the slitted sheet I sit.
Fight!
Aah!
Ooh!
That... was... my move.
I can't breathe.
Don't be such a baby.
It's just a kick in the nuts.
Easy for you to say.
You... don't... have nuts.
Lucky shot. Let's see you...
Come on, Johnny.
Unfair!
No!
Your boyfriend
is weak.
Like all those from Earthrealm.
Winner, D'Vorah.
What happened?
Bug babe just kicked your ass.
Are you okay?
I, uh... I think so.
I could use...
What?
What could you use?
Some mouth to mouth?
- Ugh!
- Ow!
Where... Where are you going?
I'm super injured.
You will be if you
keep acting a fool.
Come on.
Raiden...
I hope you fare
better than your champions.
Aah!
Whoa!
Let's see if these metal arms
rip as easily as flesh.
Yeah, you do that.
Hurts, doesn't it?
Enough!
Let us retire for the evening.
Guards!
Take them to their chambers.
Ooh. Well, look at that,
someone's a little testy.
Must mean we're winning.
Resistance will be met
with extreme force.
What?
You shall pay
for my brother's death.
Smoke.
Nice! The thunder god
bringing the thunder!
It would seem.
- Lord Raiden...
- I am fine.
Place your hand
on the door.
You don't know
what you're doing.
You open this door,
you've doomed us all.
Place your hand
on the door.
Objective achieved.
Eliminate Shirai Ryu.
Forgive me, Harumi.
No one kills him.
Except me.
Hey, where's the food court
around here?
Do you have a menu?
I could also use a spa,
I wanna work out
after that ass kicking
I was handed.
Okay, dick, nice chat.
A couple of beds in here.
Think I'll get some shut eye
while I can.
If I can.
Because I'm on another world.
In an evil dictator's castle.
Totally normal.
He's right. I'll see you
in the morning.
Wait.
Right. Right. Right...
Not without permission.
So... Maybe we could uh...
Could what?
I don't know. Hang out.
Talk.
I'm going to bed.
You know, there was a time
no girl could withstand
my charms.
Listen, Jack attack,
you know her best.
Could you put in
a good word for me?
You want a chance
with a lady like that,
it'll take more than some
expensive veneers and perfect hair.
It's never
failed me before.
Yeah... You look like
a collection
of great life choices.
Women need to be wooed, Johnny.
Pursued. Not coerced.
Isn't that the same thing?
Good night, Romeo.
You should rest,
Lord Raiden.
Thank you for your concern.
- I'm fine.
- Are you?
Is there something you want
to say, Liu Kang?
It's just that...
Lord Raiden, your fight
from earlier...
I'm worried that...
I appreciate your concern,
young one.
I am merely getting used
to life as a...
Mortal.
I will be fine.
I promise.
Now... Off to sleep.
Something I do not
think I have done in...
Well... Ever.
It should be
quite the experience!
You killed my brother!
I did. And... I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't bring him back.
Your clan,
they killed my people...
My son, my wife...
The man that led that raid
used magic to appear
as your brother.
Lies!
Listen to me.
They will destroy us both
if we don't work together.
Help me... or we die.
Listen, there is no
time for this.
That's the Kamidogu.
If they get that,
all the realms are doomed.
Your thirst for vengeance will
disappear along with all of reality.
You are lying.
I'm not.
- I don't care!
- Yes, you do.
That's what
makes you different.
That's what makes you better.
I know
the desire for revenge.
It's a sickness
that eats at your soul
until you become a monster
of regret and pain.
I deserve to die.
And it would be fitting
if you did it.
So kill me, if you must.
But promise me
you'll take that Kamidogu
and keep it
from those monstrosities.
Do it.
I will never forgive you.
Neither will I.
Brother. Don't.
We've been lied to.
Whoever hired the Lin Kuei
wants this for an evil purpose.
You can't give it to them.
It is our objective.
Is it me, or does Sonya look
really pissed?
Yeah. I figured
that would happen.
What would happen?
Well, bug lady there made the
mistake of hitting Sonya's man...
Moi. She's defending my honor.
He's not my boyfriend.
What... the hell?
I don't know what you are.
But it's time to go back
to the hell you came from!
Ah!
No. Stop!
Stryker!
Finish him!
You're next.
We failed.
No, not yet.
Come. It's time
to find redemption.
- He can't.
- Liu Kang.
Mortal Kombat
has been declared.
This is Kung Lao's fight.
Are you ready
to die, young one?
I'm Kung Lao,
descendant of
the Great Kung Lao.
It is you, who should be ready
to die, Shao Kahn.
No.
No!
Fatality.
I know he was
like a brother to you.
But he died as he lived.
A warrior.
His sacrifice
will not be in vain.
Kitana... No mercy.
Yes, your highness.
It is never too late, Kitana.
Fight.
Finish him.
Traitor!
No. Queen of Outworld.
As rightful heir, I hereby
surrender to Earthrealm,
so they may unmerge Edenia
and the other realms
from the grasp of tyranny!
You wretched child.
Did you think I would be
so easily defeated?
Finish it.
Kill you? No!
You'll stay alive.
Watching as I merge the realms.
Then...
when you've seen
all that you love destroyed,
then I'll kill you.
Take her away!
Who's next?
No!
Come on, baby.
You'll be all right.
I've been waiting a long time
for this, boy.
So have I.
Fight.
I expected better.
Liu Kang.
Surrender now,
and I might let you live.
Your arrogance,
knows no bounds, Shang Tsung.
I do not need my arm
to beat the likes of you.
Finish him.
Huh?
No. Live with knowing
I defeated you,
and it wasn't even close.
What did he do to me?
Some sort of... curse.
If I were still a god,
I could...
But you aren't.
Oh, great! Our second greatest
fighter is sidelined.
- What now?
- We fight.
We win at all costs.
Soon...
Soon you will rise,
and take the realms
for your own.
No more pain.
No more suffering.
No more... anything!
You have it?
The Lin Kuei never fail.
At last.
The final piece
of the Kamidogu!
The Kamidogu...
What? You thought
I had you chasing some bauble?
But... if it is put together...
The One Being will come back
and destroy all of existence?
Yes! It is said the mad
god Shinnok has searched...
You're Shinnok!
Ah. Now you realize the
pitfalls of being a mercenary.
But don't worry...
I have your payment...
in full.
Children.
Huh.
Kratakoth!
Malentakoth!
Responde!
No.
- Lord Raiden, don't... I can...
- Do not fear for me.
This is what I am meant to do.
To protect Earthrealm.
To protect you.
Ah. At last.
As it should be.
You and I...
to the death.
You talk too much.
Lord Raiden!
Any last words?
Your parents loved you, Liu Kang.
And...
No!
Your destiny was never
to defeat Goro, Liu Kang.
It was to defeat Shao Kahn.
It is over.
- I have won!
- No.
What the hell is he doing?
Protecting Earthrealm.
Yes, come to me.
Come to die!
Yeah! Kick his ass!
That's nothing compared
to what I'm about to do.
He did it!
He fuckin' did it!
It's over.
- You did it.
- We did it.
Liu Kang...
You have won
the final Mortal Kombat.
For that,
you are awarded great power.
But we fear,
it may not be enough.
Enough? For what?
The One Being.
Come here!
Your spirit lives!
Mmm!
Yes, the One Being!
The end...
begins!
What... What is happening?
The end of the realms!
The realms are merging.
Hurry.
Lord Raiden told us of a child.
The chosen one.
A soul so pure
that he could hold our power
and save the realms.
You... are that child,
Liu Kang.
And this is your final battle.
Whoa.
Scorpion? I thought
you were dead.
- I was.
- What are you doing here?
Trying to stop that.
Let the unmaking... begin!
Find cover.
This is my fight now.
Lord Raiden...
Why am I the chosen one?
Because I chose you.
And I chose you
because of what is in here.
You have lost much
in this life.
And yet, blame no one.
Never stop fighting, Liu Kang.
As long as you stand,
goodness and light
will stand also.
I am the chosen one.
What the fuck?
Look at that.
What now?
Now, we open my luggage.
I'd kiss you, but your
boyfriend might get jealous.
Not my boyfriend.
Listen,
with the realms merging,
there's a lot of
innocent people in harm's way.
Spread out and help them.
Get to shelter. Quickly.
Major Jackson Briggs,
reporting for duty.
Everyone get behind me.
Well, what are you waiting for?
An invitation?
Get some, get some,
get some.
Uh!
- I'm out.
- Me too.
Sonya!
Sonya... Sonya, stay with me.
I'm sorry for being an idiot.
You deserve so much more.
This fight, all the death...
it was worth it, to meet you.
You really mean it, don't you?
Then... I guess we should
get out of here,
and... talk.
- I love you.
- No shit.
You never
could have won.
The destiny of the realms...
is oblivion.
Get over here!
Aw... shit.
No...
I am eternal.
I am everything.
Impossible!
You don't deserve this.
Liu? Liu? Are you there?
Yes, and no.
It is difficult to explain.
Is it over?
No, not yet.
Now, is it over?
Yes, the realms
have been separated.
Edenia is free once more.
No more tournaments.
No more gods.
Just peace.
As it should be.
Yeah? I've heard that before.
Shao Kahn's body is gone.
What happens when he
or someone else
gets the itch to take over
Earthrealm again?
Then we'll be there
to stop them... together.
Whoa! Hey, I don't remember giving you perm...
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull