Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Ah...
Oh...
I need a raise.
Go and bait
the next hunting site.
Yeah!
Not now.
We're movin'. Now.
- But I'm not finished yet.
- Right now!
Let's go!
Come on, we gotta go now.
Up that hill, now!
Pick him up and put him down,
I'm not gonna to ask twice.
Raptor One,
prepare for site one LZ arrival.
Copy that, Blazer One.
Got 12 on board for the hunt. Over.
Roger that, Raptor 1.
Dinner's hot and ready.
Lindon inbound to tag. Over.
I can't breathe in this thing.
- How much further is it?
- We're close.
Copy you,
Blazer 1. Raptor 1 inbound.
Tasers limited to five max.
Alright, looks good.
Let's do it.
All guards report immediately.
- Over there!
- You over there, feet there.
All guards report immediately.
- 4] Now assist the boys.
- Bags off.
This place is a dump!
Welcome to Jurassic Hunt.
Are we ready to have some fun?
Alright, fantastic.
Thank you guys so much
for adhering to my
somewhat lengthy list
of safety precautions.
I know they can be
a bit of a pain, but uh,
we can't be too careful
these days, can we?
While inside the reserve,
security and privacy are essential,
speaking of which,
one final check for prohibited items.
I would say I trust you, but...
Hey, what are you doin'?
Hey, that's my
personal property.
Why would you
bring that here
and cheat the trust
that you and I...?
Listen, guys, the hunting
and non-disclosure agreements
you signed prior to entry,
specifically state,
"No outside cellphones,
communications or recording devices
are allowed inside the reserve.
Period.
Failure to adhere to said agreements
is forfeiture of your payment
and will result in
your immediate expulsion."
Mr. Corrigan, I am truly sorry to disappoint
you and your many, many Twitter followers
the way you have disappointed
me, and us, with this.
Hey! Hey, no, let...
Oh! Oh, my nose!
You broke my nose!
Oh, you're gonna pay for this!
I'm gonna sue you so hard,
you'll be sorry for this.
We're all here
to have a good time,
but it is best
to follow my rules.
Alright, who's ready to hunt?
Pick your poison.
We've got anything
you could possibly want
from Rambo First Blood
to Last Blood.
You crazy kids, go ahead and have at it.
You bought it all.
We had an explosives box
around here somewhere.
I need a tranquilizer gun.
You sure about that?
Guy on the last trip wanted one of those
and, uh, he used it to skin 'em alive.
That's some pretty gnarly stuff.
Is that your brand
of entertainment?
Parker, right?
You have fun.
Alright. Now, if you guys
could please give Mr. Marko
your undivided attention.
Right now, we're standing
at the dead center
of the reserve.
Tomorrow, we'll head south
and hunt various grounds
until we reach camp site two.
We'll stay the night,
hunt the following day
until we reach the exit
and you leave.
We've flown in
the most exciting specimens
from the big park
for your hunting enjoyment.
You are allowed to shoot anything
that was allowed 65 million years ago.
You only keep
what you can carry.
Yeah, and one last thing.
Uh, tracking chip.
I don't remember nothin'
about no tracking chip.
Uh, or you can join
Mr. Corrigan and your hunt ends now.
No refunds.
Listen, guys,
it's just one final precaution,
just in case we have to dig you out
of the forest or the belly of a T-Rex.
Okay.
There you go. Now, I'll know
where to find you.
Ah, it's already up.
You see that? That's you guys.
Neat, right?
Rest assured,
everything is under my control.
Everything is a lot to control.
And that's why
I'm the one controlling it.
I have seen you before.
What is your name?
Valentine.
And you're Blackhawk;
pirate, warlord,
head of a poaching empire.
Wanted by the FBI, CIA, Interpol.
You're famous.
You mean infamous.
Alright, guys.
It is time to eat.
You're gonna love this.
Roasted raptor.
Alright, they're all yours,
Mr. Marko.
Reserve rangers, move out!
If you cannot do it...
I will dig it out for you.
Go play with your little knife
in your tent.
You want to watch me?
I handle it real good, mami.
You lay a hand on me,
and you're gonna regret it.
That's right.
I can spot a killer
a mile away and you...
Maybe you are not one.
Everybody wants to be
the alpha, huh?
Get over yourselves.
The only thing we're
killin' out here is dinosaurs.
I'm sorry. I won't tell anybody.
I swear, I swear.
You hear that, Riggs?
He swears.
It's all good. Stop the car.
The corporation trusted me
with the reserve's privacy,
because it is the single most
essential element in its success.
Tell me you understand that.
Well, yeah, but the thing is...
Good!
Back to the hunt you go!
Hey, wait, what are you doin'?
You get the VIP experience.
No, wait! Hey!
Happy huntin'.
Hey! Come back!
Hey! Hey, you red bastards!
Don't you leave me!
Oh, come on, Corrigan, think.
Marko, come here, please.
Rabbit, where are you?
Rabbit. Rabbit, where are you?
Let's run away.
There are too many of them.
They're too fast. Marko!
If I have to come find your ass,
I'm killin' it.
I thought you boys hunt that...
Get ready.
Rocket launcher.
Get up, Parker!
Well...
That's five down, gentlemen.
Six to go.
I don't plan on dying.
I also do not plan on dying.
Any sign of Marko?
I found this.
Alright, it's your kill.
Finish it.
- It's time to choose.
- Do it.
It's waking up.
Kill it already.
I'll do it.
Back off.
Damn it, Valentine!
What?
Somebody had to put it
out of its misery, right?
Now, it's done.
Alright, what's next?
Hello, is anyone there?
Can anyone hear me?
Over.
Well, fellas,
looks like we're on our own.
Now, see,
this is the opposite of good.
Sir.
Come on, breed already.
Listen, my clock is ticking.
If these two don't start spilling
baby batter in next two hours,
put them in the blender
for next week's guests.
Comprende? Fantastic.
Sir, should I extract
the hunters?
Extraction. Not yet.
Get me everything you can
on this Parker woman.
Sir.
I don't care for you very much.
I always wanted
one of these AKs, man.
- Hey.
- Where'd you get that?
Mother Russia.
What do you
think you are doing?
It's been hours.
Nobody's coming for us,
and I'm not staying here.
And I paid to hunt.
You sure you know
where you're going?
Marko said if we trek south,
we'd reach the exit.
Oh, wait, wait.
You can be reasonable, boys.
It is a big mistake, but we stay
here, they know where to find us.
I-I just think maybe not...
I don't care what you
or anyone else thinks.
Stay if you want.
You've seen what
those dinosaurs can do.
Hey... they hunted us,
so we'll hunt them on our way out.
Yes.
Better to stick together.
I didn't catch where you
said you were from, again.
- I didn't say.
- Take this.
Hey, kid, you're gonna need
more than a tranquilizer gun
and a knife
if you intend to survive
in a Jurassic game hunt.
I have exactly what I need and
I'm gettin' out of here fast.
Well, Valentino,
let's go hunting, man.
Let's go.
You ain't used to
this sort of thing, are you?
I have hunt duck.
Duck? What the hell
are you doin' out here, man?
Honestly, I'm not too sure.
Yeah, well, I'll let you
in on a little secret.
These guys? I've been on more
hunts than any of them combined.
Trust me on this.
If you wanna kill some
dinosaurs, you stick with me.
What is this?
- What the hell is that, man?
- What is that?
It burns!
Do not touch it!
Help me. Get it off!
Get it off me!
No, no. Help me, help me!
Hold still!
Help me.
Get down!
Are you alright?
What the hell was that?
A grenade, of course.
You could have killed us all!
You whine like a mule,
yet you are still alive.
- Don't you ever...
- This is my hunt.
You are not in charge.
You do not give me orders.
If you think you
have the power here,
you came to
the wrong place, woman.
Still hurt?
No, no, screw it, man.
I don't need it.
Yes, this is my forest now!
Let's move.
Well, welcome to campsite one.
Well, boys,
we're eatin' better tonight.
The roasted raptor yesterday
tasted 200 million years old.
The world could always
use another vegan.
Sweet Jesus.
Are you a vegetarian, too?
How does a vegetarian survive
in a dog-eat-dog world?
It is now a
dinosaur-eat-dinosaur world, huh?
Yeah, no, that does not
have the same ring to it.
Ah, yes.
This is what
I am talking about. This.
Permiso, senorita.
Hey, Parker, are you going to do
some actual hunting here?
I think I've seen enough carnage
for one day.
- Hey, Sergei.
- Hm?
- Ask you a question, man?
- Yeah.
When you're out there
on the plains,
and you see
one of them dinosaurs,
you ever feel like doin' somethin',
you know, other than killin' them?
Like a little more, you know?
You ever...
when you see 'em you know, get...
Get those like urges to...
Like a crocodile hunter.
Wrestle.
Yeah.
Yeah, kind of like that, man.
- You know what I'm sayin'?
- Nyet.
Yeah, no. No, me either, man.
That's weird.
Let's go hunt 'em.
Yeah, let's go hunt 'em.
Yeah, keep laughin'.
Assholes.
I want a brontosaurus.
Massive!
Then I've killed
the biggest thing on Earth.
Well, the second
biggest thing on Earth.
Bullock, what trophy
are you here for?
I will drink to that.
Those are US dog tags.
Yes.
The communist
has a taste of it now.
It's a thrill to kill.
That's how it starts.
Only once
you have killed something...
...can you find out what you are.
Only then can you
fully appreciate life.
This guy's insane, man.
He's got the touch.
Work as hard
and maybe, just maybe,
you will be as good as I am.
Does being good include
throwing grenades at your prey?
If it works, it works.
Do you know
how I got my name, hmm?
Shall I tell them, hmm?
I took down
a Blackhawk helicopter
filled with US soldiers
with one grenade.
And that make you proud?
Those soldiers come to my home
to stop my people
from hunting animals
on our lands.
Endangered animals
whose parts you sold
to fund a civil war that killed tens
of thousands of innocent people!
You may think you know me,
but you know nothing of my people!
Now, I did not start the fight
with your soldiers, but I ended it.
They died a warrior's death.
That's the most a soldier
can hope for.
You cannot be serious.
Throwing grenades
does not make you a badass.
It make you a coward.
Warrior, solider,
poacher, bastard.
Names do not matter.
You know what matters most, hmm?
I am the one
that is still alive!
that is still standing!
Who needs to prove themselves
when you have this?
Ah, yes. That is power.
I have the power!
Blackhawk comes out on top.
Blackhawk never...
Take it off!
Everyone down!
Blackhawk down, motherfucker!
You think we're
stickin' around after that?
Hell with the group, man.
Too many people,
too many targets.
That's why we're creepin' out of here.
Right, Sergei?
It's nothing personal.
See y'all at the exit.
If you make it. Good luck.
Every man for themselves. Right?
You're gonna wanna read this.
Now.
Now, see, that is
the shit I don't like.
Shall I handle it?
While I do appreciate
your fervor,
uh, let's not risk any valuable
personnel by going out there.
Lindon, please.
Rabbit, buddy.
I need an extraction.
I'm so tired of running.
It's gonna be alright, buddy,
we're comin' to get you.
But, hey, listen,
there's something
I need you to do first.
There's a hunter named "Parker."
She cannot leave
this reserve alive.
Can I ask you to take an active
role in the imposition...
No! I can't do it.
Please, just come and get me.
I will triple your salary.
How much we talking about?
We made the right decision, man.
Them fools are gonna get
their asses killed.
But like I said, man, stick with me...
Stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
And we'll be out just...
What, man?
Yeah. Shoot it.
- What?
- Yeah, man, come on.
That's what we're here for.
Shoot it.
It's-it's peaceful creature.
Kind of. Hey, I'll do it.
AK, man.
What's up? What's up?
Here we go. Headshot.
Oh, damn, he moved.
Oh, yeah. Alright, alright.
I got this, alright, go.
Damn, man.
Whoa, man! You hit that thing
with a shotgun.
- Hmm.
- That's badass.
Do-do you hear that?
Nah, man, I ain't hear nothin'.
Get it off!
No, please, no!
I gotta get out of here.
Jesus.
Ooh. Hi.
Too much for you, mi amor?
Huh, this little adventure
not going the way you expected?
It's going exactly
as I expected!
Fine.
Oops.
You don't wanna do this.
Yes, I do.
Drop the knives.
Valentino, just let us have
a little bit of fun here, eh?
We all paid to kill dinosaurs,
not people.
That's pretty stupid logic if
you're going to, uh, shoot us.
No... just you.
Okay.
I had it handled.
That's a funny way
of saying "thank you."
Once again,
I don't need your help.
You need to take a hint, Parker.
It is time for you
to hold a real weapon.
- I don't...
- Shut up.
Parker, people are dying.
Our numbers are dwindling.
Did you see Torres?
He's gonna scalp me alive
the second he has a chance.
I need you to have my back.
Hold it!
- What the hell?
- Please! I heard voices.
Oh, my God.
I am so glad I found people.
I've been out there
for so long.
Who are you?
I'm with the hunting group.
I'm the only one left.
Those things, man,
they're everywhere.
Are you with the reserve?
Do we look like
we're with the reserve?
How long have you
been out there?
I don't know.
I'm Rabbit, by the way.
You guys have names?
I'm Valentine.
That's Parker, Bullock.
This is Torres.
- Parker...
- Hey!
You don't look like no hunter.
I'm not.
I'm actually an accountant.
Yeah.
I thought I could handle this,
but I was so wrong.
What's in the bag?
The bag?
I found somethin'
really strange out there.
You wanna see it?
What the hell is this?
I think it's some
type of synthetic compound.
That's a mighty big assumption
for an accountant.
May I?
I think it's...
What... Get...
What the hell just happened?
- Are you okay?
- Do you smell that?
Let's go, let's go!
Run, go!
It has begun.
They're dropping
like flies, sir.
I said take...
- Oh.
- What are you, a woman? Huh?
- Jesus freak.
- I'm lactose intolerant, man.
Perfection.
Lactose intolerant!
You think...
Dumbass!
Oh. Okay.
What's that smell?
Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop.
You gotta get rid of the jacket.
Ditch it now, go.
- Go. Now!
- What is it?
Dino hormones. Has to be.
Hunters use that sometimes
to attract prey.
Look, anything
that got spray on it,
you gotta get rid of it,
alright?
So who was that
yo puta guy, hey?
He has to work for Lindon.
Wait, so Lindon's
trying to kill us?
The Jurassic hunters
have become the Jurassic hunted.
This place is insane.
Lindon is crazy.
He's out of control.
This doesn't end
until we're all dead
or until he thinks
we're all dead.
We have to get off the grid.
For once,
we're on the same page.
Who's first?
I'll do it.
- No.
- It'll work.
Do you know what you're doing?
Let me see. Alright.
All the, uh,
chip signals are dead.
Rabbit must have done his job.
What are you lookin' for?
Riggsy, do you know
why I'm in charge?
Nepotism?
It's because I am thorough,
and I leave nothing to chance.
My tasks are completed to a level of
perfection rarely achieved by others,
with no loose ends
and no collusion.
Something to remember
if you ever want to be a big dog
in the corporate machine.
Ah.
Shit.
Do you want me
to send the team in?
No collusion.
We are not murderers, Riggs,
we are moderators at best.
We allow nature
to sort herself out naturally.
That said, we can make their
chances of survival difficult.
How many more
provision drops are there?
- Three, sir.
- Yeah, let's make sure those are canceled
and all loose caches
are removed.
No food, plus no weapons,
equals no hunters.
- Easy.
- Yes, sir. I'm on it.
My little piggies.
My man, Rambo.
We need to be silent, no?
This silent.
There's something about hunting
dinosaur with bow and arrow.
It just seem right, you know?
Does it?
So campsite two?
Yeah, we'll have
more supplies there.
That's just where Lindon
wants us to go.
So? We kill him.
And anything else
that try to stop us.
He'll be waiting for us there.
We have to use
the element of surprise.
So what then?
You're a hunter, right?
Let's hunt.
You mean for that little guy
that sprayed you?
Wherever he's goin',
probably be safe.
Ooh, I am going to love gutting
that little pendejo.
We gotta keep him alive
to get to Lindon.
Without him we have no leverage,
no nothing.
Don't jeopardize our only lead.
Wait. You hear that?
Yeah.
Good, good, good.
But let's try this, alright?
Let's slide this down
nice and easy like this.
And there we should be able
to watch all our little friends.
Alright, let's get it over here
and take a little peek.
You like to watch, don't you?
Yeah, you do.
And we should see one, two...
Three should be right over...
Rambo, baby.
Yeah, not too bad.
Now, do you think
you can find Rabbit?
Does a dinosaur
shit in the woods?
He went that way.
Ooh!
Hey, you even know
where you're goin'?
He's fast, but messy.
Stay here.
Can we trust him?
I don't know.
I hope so.
I told you
he would skin me alive
if it meant his own survival.
That's probably still the case.
Been trackin' us for a while.
You used us as bait?
Torres, teamwork.
Hey, I just saved
your lives, okay?!
You can have
the next one if you like.
Can I borrow your knife
a second?
Gracias.
You want one?
Alright, hurry up,
we're wasting time.
Alright,
he's getting further away.
Come on. Get what you need,
and let's go.
Gracias.
You're so nice.
He's here.
Down there.
Let me go, let me go!
If I do that, Torres here
is gonna open your throat.
What-what do you
want me to do?
Make a call.
We don't have two days.
I need a new drone now.
So get Jeff on the phone
and tell him to use that
fancy prototype delivery drone
to bring us a new drone now.
Rabbit, for you.
Go.
You're gonna wanna take this.
Talk to me.
It's done.
Elaborate.
They are...
Dead. They're dead, all of 'em.
Are you sure?
After they shot down the
drone, I scented them
and then the raptors got 'em.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
Congratulations.
You've become a very,
very rich man.
Campsite two, high noon.
I'll bring my checkbook.
We don't need him anymore.
He's dead weight.
- He's still useful to us.
- It's a mistake!
We made a deal with him.
We're keepin' him alive.
Look, the map says campsite two
isn't far from here.
I say we
camp here for the night.
Yeah, it's safe enough for him,
it'll be safe enough for us.
At least, let me check my traps.
Obviously,
we didn't trip any coming in.
They need to be checked.
Look, I don't wanna
die here either,
and you don't know
where they all are.
Show me.
Uh... I got bad news.
We're gonna have to put this out
otherwise they might see it.
Well, then I think you ought to
give me your scarf, pretty boy.
Good, it's done.
That's the last one.
Okay, vamonos.
Come on, pendejo!
Alright.
Come on!
Try that again.
Por favor,
try to escape one more time,
so I can accidentally bash your skull
nine times on one of these rocks, hey?
Your time will come.
Now, get your ass up.
You going to show the world
this part of your hunting video?
Where you tie up a man
and hold him against his will?
The world needs to see
what's goin' on here.
I haven't killed anybody.
Not yet.
Just make sure
that gets to its proper home.
It does not deserve
to stay here.
Strangely nice of you.
I always kept a souvenir
from every person I kill.
But maybe it's time
for a change.
Just out of curiosity,
how many people
have you murdered?
There was a-a sniper
in Afghanistan...
and he was pickin' off
US troops, like for weeks.
So they brought me in
to hunt the monster.
Sniper.
So I'm laying on
my belly for days,
and I'm scouting every nook and
cranny, every shadow.
I cannot see him.
But I know he's there
and I know...
I know that he's
doin' the same thing.
He's hunting me.
Five-hundred yards in the unforgiving
terrain and crosswinds everywhere.
Got him.
The reflection... in the scope.
Right in his eye.
There is nothing like
killing another human being.
But when they die...
you know,
a little piece of you dies, too.
Well, thank you
for your service.
Okay. But what about you, eh?
Yeah, I can tell you served.
Yep.
Maria, mira puesso.
So development group.
SEAL Team Six.
Soldier for life!
You know...
which was always
assumed to be a short life.
All I ever wanted
was to die a warrior's death.
You both place
such a low value on life.
If you had to
blow Lindon's brains out
to escape this place...
could you do it?
You're a real psycho,
you know that?
Maybe I am.
Where's the...? Where's the...?
Watch, Valentino.
Where are you going?
Hunting.
Adios, mi amor.
You're dead!
You hear me? Dead!
Hey, hey, come on.
Hey, listen,
I still need you okay?
There's still a mission for you
to complete, soldier, understand?
Where's the bottle?
Give me the bottle.
Shit.
Thank you for saving me
back there.
Oh, feeling's mutual.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
Oh, you want to play, hey?
Okay, come on,
let's do this. Eh?
Ahh!
Hey, come on.
Hey. Hey.
Come on, baby.
I have to tell you something.
Lindon isn't trying to kill us,
he's trying to kill me.
These glasses are recording
everything in here.
So you are a spy.
I'm with an agency that's trying to
expose this place and its cruelty.
I've got to get this footage
out of here.
What if Rabbit's alive?
If he is alive,
I seriously doubt he would
contact Lindon after he got free
and tell him that he lied,
and that we're still alive.
Hey, Valentine, campsite two!
We're here. Hey, buddy. Hey.
Keep movin'.
Enjoying the hunt, Miss Parker?
You son of a...
Ouch! That looked painful
and completely unnecessary.
Riggs, you bad boy.
Didn't your father ever teach
you never to strike a woman,
but if you do, you beat her to the
body, so the bruises won't show?
Oh, Rabbit, buddy!
How nice of you to join us.
- I can explain.
- Mm-hmm.
They were gonna set
a trap on you.
Clearly, we figured
that out, but thank you.
- Where's the other one?
- Dead.
You'll forgive me
if I don't trust you anymore,
so we'll double check
that when we're done here.
We're lucky
we were tracking you,
but we'll circle back to that
betrayal thing in just a moment.
Now, I'm not gonna hurt you
or kill you,
but whilst you are in my beautiful nature sanctuary...
...you will not enjoy
any unnatural advantages either.
Nerd.
- Someone...
- Someone will what?
Replace you? Leak the secrets?
Nobody cares.
I've had US senators here,
- the general of one of those Asian armies...
- Lujo.
Lujo. Hollywood directors,
rap superstars,
all come here
for the same reason.
The thrill of the hunt.
They don't care.
Even that one guy
in your group...
What was his name?
Uh, Pecker? Poultry?
- Sergei.
- Sergei, close enough. Even him.
He's some Russian tech genius
with direct ties
to the President
of the United States,
who I am this close
to convincing
to come out here
for a weekend.
We're all good.
Eh-ah.
You can't keep your secrets
contained here forever.
It's not just dinosaurs
you're killing, it's people.
- People will care!
- Easy there.
And if that happens,
we'll be insured.
Or on a beach somewhere.
I hear Tahiti is nice
this time of year.
- Do you like Tahiti, Riggs?
- I can dig it.
How about you, Miss Parker?
Do you like Tahiti?
Tahiti is awesome.
Visit the big Fuck You Island.
I hear it's beautiful.
Whoa!
Hey, you. Hey, buddy,
wake up, come on! Hey!
Jesus Christ!
What'd I miss?
Bad guy won.
Your glasses.
Lindon got exactly
what he wanted.
I even killed more dinosaurs
to save myself.
At least there's no
video evidence of that.
This isn't funny!
This isn't a joke!
This place...
It can't be stopped!
If Lindon dies, the corporation
will just send another Lindon.
If I die, Lindon was right,
no one will care.
Then don't die.
Get out of this place.
At least, you have your voice.
Lindon can't control that.
Give me the gun.
Where are you going?
To the truck.
Hello?
Hello, is anybody out there?
Somebody answer this now
or you're all fired!
Lindon, is that you?
Of course, it's me!
I need an immediate extraction.
You send the whole team,
you send everyone!
Copy, we can do that.
What's your location?
Somewhere near campsite...
Somewhere near campsite two.
But where near campsite two?
How in the hell should I know!
That's your job!
You come and get me.
Move your asses.
Do you have a tracking chip
or something?
No, I don't have
a fucking tracking chip!
On a side note,
kill anyone and everything
that isn't me.
You understand what I'm saying?
Clear this park.
I'm talking dinosaurs, women,
babies, anyone who isn't me.
Your boss,
the guy who signs your checks.
Try to make
your way back to the gate, sir.
- We'll find you.
- You clear this park, you understand?
Well, bad luck, Parker.
Keys are probably in the belly
of a pterodactyl somewhere.
Can't you hotwire this thing?
I mean, didn't they teach you
how to do that in Desert Storm?
No, they did not teach me how to hot
wire 2010 Tacoma in Desert Storm.
I wasn't even in Desert Storm.
Whoa! Oh, thank God,
I'm so glad you found me.
I really need your help.
I think they're right behind me.
No.
Fire.
Hello? Hello?
Does anyone copy?
- I copy.
- Oh, good.
In case, you haven't noticed,
I'm still out here,
somewhere south
of campsite two.
I've been walking for hours.
Hours?
We would have seen him by now.
Hello, can you hear me?
Sir, are you sure it's south?
Yes, south! From campsite two,
toward the exit.
- I'm not a total idiot.
- Okay, sir.
We're close. We should be
seein' you any minute.
Okay, hop to, chop, chop.
I keep hearing shit
in the bushes.
Alright, it's clear.
- Lindon could be wrong.
- It's possible.
But if they get to the
exit before we do...
We have to fight our way out.
We don't stand a chance.
We have to find a way
around them and beat them out.
Alright, hear me out.
Maybe he's dino-food by now.
One can only hope.
Should we call him?
Go ahead.
What the hell was that?
Sir? Mr. Lindon?
Maybe it was a dinosaur.
There's no way this works.
It's a bag hanging from a tree.
What's not to be curious about?
Well, they're just about
to walk...
Don't!
God, it smells.
Good. It shouldn't be long now.
Let's move.
Whoa, hey.
Just me. Finally.
Now, how hard was that, guys?
Where's transport?
Oh, my God, what is that smell?
Oh, God. No, no.
Get away from me. Stay!
- What?
- You stay there.
I gotta get out of here.
You guys, you go that way,
I'm gonna go this way.
Get 'em! Kill them!
Huh?
Wait.
What?
We got another problem.
- We are not alone either.
- How many?
Uh, two, three, maybe more.
I don't...
Alright,
we'll make a stand here.
No, not this time.
You need to keep movin'.
It's the only way.
- Take this.
- You'll die.
Alright, I'll cover you
and you get out of here, okay?
Happy hunting, Valentine.
That's what I came to do.
Don't look back.
Really? Not one of you
could have followed her, huh?
Okay. Let's go!
Oh, uh, Miss Parker.
Are you forgetting something?
Give it to me.
You know, it's never too late
to earn back my trust.
Shut up and give me that key!
Or what?
Or what, you'll shoot me?
I don't think so.
Last chance!
You know what? Then you do it.
You shoot me right here,
and you take it from me!
Oh, my God.
For a moment there
I wasn't 100% sure
which way it was gonna go.
I mean, it could have went either way.
Whoo!
Oh, my God, that was intense.
What do you want, Lindon?
At this point,
I don't even know anymore.
I just... I just want you
out of my reserve.
Go tell your story,
tell whoever will listen.
I already told you
it's not going to matter.
We? We'll be back up in a week.
Back up and running.
And you? You could be on
television with Sally Struthers
doing your
feed-the-dinosaur thing.
You know, for the price
of a cup of coffee a day,
you could feed a stegosaurus
for a month, right?
All you have to do is just...
Just put down the gun and go.
See? I'm a reasonable guy.
Be sure to leave that
on your Yelp review.
I can't believe
you're that stupid.
Come on over here
and get on your knees.
You really thought I'd let you
walk out of here alive
after all the shit
you've pulled?
No, Miss Parker.
I truly hope you are as flexible
as you are tenacious,
because it's time to bend over
and kiss your ass goodbye.
Please, not the face.
Not the face! Not the face!
Give me the real key, fast!
Listen, I think if we just...
Just kill me, get it over with.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Remember?
No collusion.
- Okay, okay.
- Welcome to Jurassic Hunt, you son of a bitch.
No!
Get back!
Did you miss me?
You're alive.
I told you not to look back.
Now, let's get out of here.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull