Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[STONE]:
Hey!
[SHE WHIMPERS]
John.
The town of Westberg
had 5,000 people.
3,000 die from the virus.
1,500 of the infected
was taken care of.
So you do the math, yeah?
That's 500 missing.
500 potential
contagious bearers.
The town was clean.
I don't care
about your opinion
but I do care about facts
and I'm gonna give you
the chance to share some with me.
Tell me where
the townfolks went.
- [SHE WHIMPERS]
- John?
I'm gonna count to 10.
One.
I don't know where they are.
[STONE]:
Two.
Three.
Four.
[JOHN]:
Let her go.
[STONE]:
Five.
Six.
[JOHN]:
I don't know.
I don't know!
They all left by the time
my squad got there.
Seven.
She's got nothing to do with this.
You're really gonna
sacrifice your wife
for a bunch of strangers?
Eight.
Nine.
Kill me instead.
[SHE WHIMPERS]
I beg you.
Kill you?
[HE CHUCKLES]
Please stop this.
The time
for heroes is over, John.
[GUN COCKS]
Remember.
Look at me.
Look at me!
I love you, I love you!
You chose this.
You chose this!
I don't know where they are!
- [GUNSHOT]
- No!
[HE BREATHES HEAVILY]
[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
[HE GRUNTS]
[ADAM]:
Get down.
[PEOPLE WHIMPER]
[THEY SOB]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [PEOPLE GASP]
Stop!
Leave them alone!
[GUNSHOT]
[PEOPLE SCREAM]
Stop!
They're innocent.
[GUNSHOT]
[STONE]:
Traitor!
[STONE'S VOICE ECHOES]:
Remember.
[JOHN'S VOICE ECHOES]:
Please stop this.
[STONE'S SNIGGER ECHOES]
[STONE]: You're really gonna
sacrifice your wife?
[JOHN]:
Let her go.
[STONE]:
You chose this.
[JOHN'S SCREAM ECHOES]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRS]
Your wife was infected, John.
She had to die.
And you know the rule
we cannot let one person
be responsible
for a million dead people.
She was not infected.
She wasn't?
You could've tested her.
Oh, we did, John. We did.
But I always found those
things highly unreliable.
I'd rather trust my gut,
or as they say
stay on the safe side.
How many innocents
are you gonna kill
for the common good?
Innocent?
[HE CHUCKLES]
Don't change the subject.
Are you at least not
a bit interested
in what's in store for you?
No.
[STONE]:
No?
You're immune, John,
and we want to find out how.
So maybe you'll get
the chance to save
some more lives after all.
Cheer up, little boy.
If this was Lapland,
you'd be boiled in a sauna
and thrown into a frozen lake
until the skin came off
your bones.
Now you're only getting
pin pricks.
The only prick around here
is you.
Fuck you.
Save your jokes, comedian.
You might be needing them later.
[MAN GRUNTS]
[NECK CRACKS]
Seal the ship.
Seal the ship! Seal the ship!
[ALARM BLARES]
[MAN ON LOUDSPEAKER]:
Contagion subject 5788
is loose on the vessel,
apprehend on sight.
Contagion subject 5788
is loose on the vessel...
[SOLDIER]:
Buckle up, boys. Take him alive.
[JOHN GRUNTS]
My name is John Wood.
[SOLDIER YELLS]
[SOLDIER 2]:
So you've made it this far?
[SOLDIER 3]:
Hey, asshole!
[SOLDIER 4]: Get over here,
you little fucker.
[JOHN]:
Goodnight!
[TWIG CRACKS]
Please.
Help me.
Hide me.
[HE GRUNTS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [SHE GASPS]
It's OK.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Your wound is infected.
We have to remove the bullet.
It's for your own good.
Drink it.
That's why it's gonna hurt.
Wait.
What's your name?
John.
Are you a doctor, John?
No.
Aren't you gonna ask my name?
Maria.
[SHE WHIMPERS]
Porca Puttana cazzo Madonna.
Che cazzo!
[SHE YELPS]
[SHE SOBS]
[BULLET BEEPS]
Military grade.
[BULLET FIZZES]
Who's after you?
And how did you get here?
[HE GRUNTS]
[AXE CHOPS]
You can stay here for a few days
then you have to leave.
I don't want to have
any problems.
I want to live in peace.
[DISTANT HELICOPTER WHIRRS]
[JETS ROAR]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[HE COUGHS]
[AXE CHOPS]
- [SHE GRUNTS]
- Give me the axe.
You need to rest.
Nice clothes.
Keep them.
I will!
[HE GRUNTS]
[AXE CHOPS]
[PAUL]:
Hey, timber man.
We're looking for a girl.
You have anyone pass through?
Oi!
I'm talking to you.
Have you seen a girl?
She's a threat.
Infected.
With the virus, you know.
You're the first fucks
I've seen in ages.
Since the virus, you know.
Search the place.
[MAN YELLS]
[SHOTGUN BLASTS]
I found it under the mattress.
I know.
That's some guns.
You're not just a random
timber man...
are you?
I like to prepare for war...
and pray for peace.
A riddle?
You're the only mystery
around here.
So, what's next?
You tell me.
You're the one they're after.
I can help.
Start with this.
You made a bloody mess.
Ow!
Hmm.
[MEN GRUNT IN DISTANCE]
The mercenaries should
have been back by now.
Yes, they're dead.
Oh, what makes you so sure?
Well, they're not at a Sunday
school reunion, are they?
I'd be surprised if these... guys
even finished kindergarten.
They're only ever good
for two things
affordability and disposability.
So we send another squad?
Yes.
And wait with reporting
to Commander Stone
until we know what's going on.
[GRANITE]:
Break it up!
Attack me, come on.
[MAN GRUNTS AND YELPS]
Your best move, now.
Come on!
[BONE CRACKS]
[MAN GRUNTS]
[MAN YELLS]
Stop!
[MAN GROANS]
What the hell are you doing?
Your job.
I'm supposed to train them,
not kill them.
[GRANITE]:
Then step your fucking game up.
Huh?
[HE GRUNTS]
I want to know how you got here.
I can try.
- [DOGS BARK]
- [SIRENS BLARE]
[DISTANT VOICES YELL]
The next thing I remember
is waking up here
at your cabin.
I fear there are more coming.
They shot you
with a tracking device.
Not a real bullet.
Do you want me to leave?
Not anymore.
Thank you.
They said you were infected.
But you have no symptoms.
It's a long story.
They won't give up, they're just...
They...
These people, the ones
that's after you
they killed my wife.
John.
You chose this.
I'm sorry.
You'll be safe here.
[SHE KNOCKS]
Come in.
Come out.
Hey, how did you become so tall?
Your favourite cake.
Easy on the sugar, babe.
It's supposed to be sweet.
The only sugar I need is you.
The romantic mechanic.
[THEY GIGGLE]
How's the yard?
Why do you think I came here?
I told you you have
to build the fence yourself.
I'm done, silly.
Fence, too?
Materials arrive tomorrow.
Don't worry, I'm not letting you
anywhere near it.
I've seen your carpentry.
[SACK RUSTLES]
Praying for peace?
More will come,
and hell with them.
You don't seem too worried.
Fear is an illusion.
This is very real.
Pain is real, death is real.
So is love, John.
And life.
Love ends, life ends.
But death is forever.
[HE GRUNTS]
They found the cure.
He wants to have it.
It will change
the whole world, John.
The one controlling the
vaccine controls the virus
and the one
controlling virus controls life.
The vaccine belongs to
the people, not one man.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I am the vaccine.
It's in my blood.
I don't want to give it to them.
I want to give it to the people.
It's my redemption.
You just brought a lot
of problems to my cabin.
There's going to be
a bloody mess.
I need you to help me.
You have to.
I don't want this.
Damn it.
Do it for your wife!
Do it for good.
Help me to get my blood
to the people.
It needs cleaning.
[GUN COCKS]
What?
The wound is fine.
The gun.
What's your story?
I told you, I am the vaccine.
Not that.
How you handle weapons.
Orphaned as a teenager
after my parents died
turned juvenile
went from jacking ATMs...
to an armed robbery.
Got pretty good with that.
Well, before I got caught.
Sentenced 10 years in
a women's penitentiary.
Survived the virus
as it swept through the pen.
Then I was sent to the lab
for testing.
All the rest you know already.
A jailbird, huh?
I figured as much.
Is it that obvious?
Barcode tattoos tend to
tell their own stories.
[GUNSHOT]
You know the saying
you shoot like a bank robber?
I was trained not to kill.
Can't kill a can.
I can.
Go ahead.
But what if it's a hostage?
[GUNSHOTS]
No one is innocent.
[GUNSHOT]
[BIRDS CAW]
Legend has it a mighty
timber man lives in these woods.
He kills the enemies of nature
and he himself cannot be killed.
He was born from
the ashes of a forest fire
where 100 people died.
And he eats babies
for breakfast.
[HE LAUGHS]
I can smell the shit in
your pants from here, boys.
The look in your eyes,
priceless.
[DENNIS]:
That's not funny.
[ADAM]:
Target in sight.
[DENNIS]:
Call for backup?
Negative.
We split the bounty three ways.
Since when are we
fucking bounty hunters?
Since there was
a prize put on the girl's arse.
Focus, guys.
Kill the logger
and bring the girl.
Easy.
Nature calls.
Stay alert.
Time to say goodnight,
Boogeyman.
Goodnight.
[SHOTGUN BLASTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MUTED GUNFIRE]
Easy.
Easy!
I'll kill the girl
if you don't let me leave
with her.
[THEY GRUNT]
- [HE GRUNTS]
- [GUNFIRE]
I don't negotiate.
There's only one road
leading to this cabin.
We got 30 minutes before
the dogs arrive, bloodthirsty.
[MAN]: Get your weapons
and your gear.
[MEN YELL]:
Sir, yes, sir!
Up and out! Look alive!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
Do we have a plan
how to stop them?
I think we can hold
'em off until winter.
But after that,
a little bit harder, but doable.
Time is ticking.
I used to play with
these when I was a kid.
This won't be no play time.
Good.
Cos I ain't no kid no more.
Hey, John?
You're one bad motherfucker.
Sure I am.
Grab some water, things
are going to burn tonight.
[HE GRUNTS]
[GUNS COCK]
[SCANNER BEEPS]
[MERCENARY]:
Yep, it's her.
[FELTSPAT ON RADIO]:
Commander Stone, the target
is finally in our hands.
[SHOTGUN BLASTS]
[SHE YELLS]
- [SHOTGUN BLASTS]
- [MAN YELLS]
I told you to bring water,
not mercenaries.
[GUNSHOTS]
Hm!
[HE GROANS]
We are under attack.
The girl has escaped,
send backup.
It can't be that hard,
you morons.
He lives by a lake in
a small fucking cabin
and chops wood.
Find that timber man, now!
[FELTSPAT]: The fellow living here
is helping her.
Listen, Timberlake is
going down, not the girl.
I repeat, not the girl.
You harm one hair
on her precious skull
and you're as dead as him.
Got that?
[GUNFIRE]
I have orders not to kill you
but I can and will hurt you.
Bad.
[MARIA GRUNTS]
- Ciao, bella.
- [GUNFIRE]
Kill the timber man
whatever the cost
and me bring back
my golden cargo.
I want a coordinated
siege of the cabin.
Block all roads,
seal all entrances
and attack in small units
from all angles.
The girl can under
no circumstances get away.
There shall
be no escape routes.
[SOLDIER]:
We're half a click from target location.
Approaching from the south.
- [SHE YELLS]
- [GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIERS YELL]
[THEY GRUNT]
Is it really just one man?
Seems like
a special forces soldier to me.
The efficiency,
the way he kills.
Then why the axe?
Fuck knows.
Probably wants
to make it personal.
- [JOHN GRUNTS]
- [SOLDIER YELPS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [SOLDIERS YELP]
[FRANK]:
OK, hold.
[HE SNIFFS]
[HE SCREAMS]
[MUTED GUNFIRE]
- [SHOTGUN COCKS]
- [SHOTGUN BLASTS]
[SOLDIER YELLS]
[SHOTGUN BLASTS]
- Fuck.
- [SHOTGUN CLICKS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNFIRE]
We need to clean up
all this mess before supper.
Huh?
What's the point?
Not finding your dead comrades
is worse than finding them dead.
How many have we lost?
Awaiting confirmation.
Awaiting confirmation?
My empire is crumbling!
Find out now!
[SOLDIER ON RADIO]:
We've lost comms with Delta Team.
Find out what happened to them,
and stay alert.
Granite.
Come in, over.
Listening.
There's a tunnel,
an underpass under the cabin.
What do you mean?
They're all dead?
Where does it lead?
Straight to hell.
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
Good job.
[MARIA]:
Thanks.
Hey! Where are you going?
Hunting.
[SOLDIER SCREAMS]
[STATIC HISSES]
Come in.
Over.
Fuck.
It's an old mineshaft.
A tunnel system.
Do we know where it leads?
We do now.
Prepare for all scenarios.
Tunnel extraction on the cargo.
And should
that timber man slip inside
you take a small group
and you flush him out.
And I will make sure
he gets a very special
warm welcome
on the other end.
[SOLDIER]:
Target approaching.
[GUNSHOTS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOT]
– [SOLDIER YELLS]
[BRANCHES SNAP]
[FELTSPAT ROARS]
Well, well, well.
So, this is where you've been
hiding all these years, huh?
Huh?
C'mon!
[SOLDIER]:
Stop!
Drop it.
Get your hands in the air.
[SHE YELLS]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[FELTSPAT GRUNTS]
[SOLDIER ON RADIO]:
I have eyes on the package.
West side of the cabin,
by the waterfront.
Freeze!
- [GUNFIRE]
- [SHE YELPS]
[SHE WHIMPERS]
[SHE GROANS]
[HE GASPS]
[GROUND RUMBLES]
[BIRD CAWS]
Target acquired.
Going underground.
Rendezvous coordinates, 057.
[SOLDIER]:
Copy that, Feltspat.
We're en route
to that location.
Keep the cargo safe.
And you guys will never
believe who our timber man is.
[SOLDIER]:
Come in, Feltspat.
Our timber man...
[SOLDIER]:
Repeat?
- [RADIO CUTS OUT]
- Is John Wood.
[STATIC HISSES]
John.
Come in.
[SOLDIER ON RADIO]: The good doctor
is out of radio reach
but has acquired the target.
Rendezvous at the coordinated
pickup site for surface extraction.
[STONE]:
Gentlemen.
Yesterday,
you were all lost sheep
and today
we rejoice towards
the future as shepherds.
They say one man
cannot rule the world
but with an army of leaders
this desolate landscape
we now call the world
shall be rebuilt again
in an image
of impenetrable rule of furious...
Sir.
Sir, sir.
Feltspat wasn't there.
And neither was the cargo.
[GUNSHOT]
Three, five.
I should be here.
I am here...
Oh, shit.
Shit.
[RATTLING]
[JOHN]:
Good to see you again, Doctor.
You.
You really need to learn
how to die.
[THEY GRUNT]
Reinforcements.
Send 'em in.
Get him, flush him out, kill him
and get the fucking girl.
Now! Let's go.
How many?
All of them!
[JOHN GROANS]
[FELTSPAT YELLS]
[JOHN YELLS]
- [JOHN YELLS]
- [NECK CRACKS]
You need to learn how to kill.
John.
[SOLDIER]:
Fan out!
- Go around the ladder.
- Go, go, go, watch his back!
Two minutes.
That will be the two
last minutes of your life.
They're catching up.
It's like an infinite supply.
They're like cockroaches.
That's why the world
made exterminators.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[SOLDIER]:
Shots fired, shots fired.
- They're heading for the...
- Got the target!
[SOLDIER 2]:
Put 'em down!
- [SOLDIER]: Secure the exits!
- Move out of the way!
[GUNFIRE]
Move, move, move!
Get down!
Take cover!
[GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[SOLDIER]:
Down! Back up, back up!
[GUNFIRE]
- [GUNFIRE]
- [SOLDIER GRUNTS]
- [SHE YELLS]
- [RAPID GUNFIRE]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
I'm out, reloading.
Get ready.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
Behind you!
Take the shield.
We've got to get out of here.
[SMOKE GRENADE POPS]
Go, go, go, go, go.
Stay close, stay close.
Move. Go, go, go, go!
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [JOHN YELLS]
- John?
Go, go.
Keep moving.
Go, go, go!
[SHE PANTS]
[GUNFIRE]
[JOHN PANTS]
Stop.
Get in here.
[JOHN GROANS]
[SOLDIER]:
Boys, come on. Move!
- [SOLDIER 2]: Go, go, go!
- [SOLDIER 3]: This way!
Stay here.
[MUFFLED VOICES]
No.
You need to trust me.
There's no time.
No, I don't want to lose you.
Life is nothing but lies.
All we can do is live.
I don't want to live
without you.
You will.
[HE GRUNTS]
[DOOR LOCK CLUNKS]
[MUTED GUNFIRE]
- [JOHN YELLS]
- [MUTED GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[MUTED GUNFIRE]
[HE SPLUTTERS]
[HE BREATHES HEAVILY]
[HE GROANS]
John Wood, what a surprise.
Our dear timber man
is John Wood.
The defector
who escaped his sentence.
Now I know why this woodpecker
was such a pain in the ass.
It was John Wood.
Welcome home.
Nuh-uh-uh-uh, don't kill him.
Not just yet.
He's an old friend.
Friend?
Is that what you call family
these days?
Ah, yes.
Friend.
That's as close
as you will ever get again
my dear... brother.
And you should be honoured
by that notion.
You can change your name
but you can never change
your blood.
Wood.
[HE LAUGHS]
I always thought
that sounded too soft.
My name's Stone.
Commander Stone.
Besides, Father always
favoured you.
His favourite woodsman.
But he's not here now, is he?
To save your ass from
another beating this time.
And actually,
you can change your blood.
That's the whole reason
why we're here.
The girl!
Where is she?
The girl, John. Hand her over.
I killed her.
There were two things
you were never really good at.
Killing innocents and lying.
Where is she?
[GUNS COCK]
I killed her.
We can't find her, she's gone.
[STONE]:
Then she's missing, not dead.
And I'm pretty sure
she's around here somewhere.
So, please,
with some conviction here
my dear brother
will tell us exactly where she is.
Guys, beatdown time.
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
This can be easy, John.
It doesn't have to be
high school all over again.
Enough!
Had enough, tough guy?
Are you ready to speak now?
Huh?
You ready to talk to me, John?
John?
She's dead.
Gone.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[JOHN GROANS]
[BONES CRUNCH]
For fuck's sake!
This is pointless.
Kill him.
[JOHN]:
Coward!
Are you afraid of
a half-dead man?
Last man down,
you and me!
[HE GROANS]
[HE CHUCKLES]
Oh boy, we're really back in
high school again, aren't we?
You really want to do this?
You and me.
[STONE YELLS]
Come on!
You never knew
when to quit, little brother.
Did you?
Always wanting to impress,
always struggling to catch up.
But guess what?
Today, you did catch up.
Catch up to your own death.
But you've been dead to me
for many years.
But it's about time
that you join your wife in hell.
[THEY YELL]
Give me a gun.
Give me the fucking gun!
John, turn around.
Turn around!
Turn around.
You chose this.
[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
[GUNSHOT]
[HE PANTS]
I was planning
to do that myself.
Thank you for saving me
the trouble.
Go fuck yourself.
You're the only one
getting fucked around here.
Stop!
[GUNS COCK]
Back away from him,
you assholes.
Or you will be wearing my bloody
antidote to your own funerals!
No.
I'll come with you...
but you let him live.
Don't.
Good girl.
Take her to the chopper.
[MERCENARY]:
Yes, ma'am.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRS]
I'll find you.
The new blood of the future
has arrived.
Hello.
Sovereignty is never given.
It is claimed. Taken.
We must let go of the old
and embrace the new.
The children of yesterday will
adapt to the revised constitution.
These laws will be
governed by the select few.
Mainly us.
Spring has a way of
welcoming all of us
but only the fittest
survive the winter.
To the north.
The new dawn.
The beginning of a new era...
that is ready to greet you.
[MARIA, VO]:
Dear John
if anything happens to me
you will find three vials of my blood
in your fridge.
Promise to give my blood,
the antidote, to the people.
That is my last and only wish.
Yours, Maria.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull