Retail + transcript by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
She looks very tired.
Go ahead. Let them in.
Ready to make
another video to send to your husband?
- I think it's time...
- No, no, no, no!
...to cut off one
of your pretty little fingers.
No.
No!
Hey!
Come on, Sasha.
Come on.
Please.
Be careful with that one.
It's worth more than the GDP
of most countries.
What is this?
It's a proprietary satellite
designed to track some...
Expensive government stuff.
What?
We have to stay focused.
We're already behind schedule.
Copy that.
Morning, Sasha.
Hi, guys.
How are you feeling?
I don't know.
The past few days
have been such a blur,
I'm just trying to get
used to freedom again.
I can't even imagine.
From what I heard
happened here last month,
I... I think
you probably can.
How are your accommodations?
I know it's not fancy, but...
It's great.
I'm very comfortable.
Good.
Let me know
if you need anything.
Obviously, we're short on supplies
'cause we've been decommissioned,
but we have
to get essentials.
Where is your dad?
Still in the infirmary,
but the doctors expect him
to make a full recovery.
It must be hard for her.
She finally gets her freedom
only to find out
her husband is dead.
It was Balzary's fault
she was being held prisoner.
Which only
complicates it further,
it doesn't help anything.
Not to mention the fact
that the man who saved her
is also the man
who killed her husband.
If that's not complicated,
I don't know what is.
It's crazy how life
changes so fast.
A month ago,
I had never met you.
Now I can't imagine
my life without you.
We're supposed to be focused.
No distractions.
We've earned
a little distraction.
Don't you think?
I guess so.
Whoa.
Check this out.
Jesus, do you think
these things still work?
Holy shit.
Let's not find out.
Those stay here.
I already have enough going on.
I don't need an exploding truck.
Hi.
How is Robert doing?
He's, uh, he's stabilizing.
And his latest EKG is normal.
Oh. That's...
that's a relief.
Yeah. We were worried,
given how deep
the bullet penetrated.
It looked awful.
But he's proving to be
very tough, as usual.
Yeah.
I know a little bit about
what happened in Russia.
How?
Our doctors,
they get field reports,
and we need them
for any possible surgery
that this facility
needs to perform.
I see. Okay.
You know,
it's in Robert's nature,
and like him to confront danger
almost instinctively.
He saved my life.
Yeah. He protects
the innocent, always.
I just can't help
but think, what if I...
No, Sasha. None of what
happened was your fault.
Look, you can go in
and see him now.
He's been asking about you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Good to see you.
How are you?
I'll be fine.
I heard the bullet ripped
through your shoulder.
Doesn't sound fine.
It'll heal.
I might die of boredom.
Oh. They don't give you
a TV or something?
They packed it up.
I wanted to thank you.
If it wasn't for you,
I would still be in Russia.
They would have
killed me eventually.
Don't mention it.
You didn't have to do it,
and I'll never forget that.
I gave Frederic my word.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Killing my husband
in self-defense?
Ah.
Ulysses, tell me
you still have Paul.
Ulysses?
Ulysses!
Shit.
Ah!
Ah.
They say life...
could be
understood backwards.
But it must be lived forward.
That's right.
Do me a favor.
Try and save my wife.
She's suffered enough
for my sins.
Please, Robert.
Done.
You had no choice, right?
I had no choice.
Well, Frederic
was a complicated man.
That's an understatement.
You still having nightmares?
Those aren't going away
anytime soon, I guess.
Just take one day at a time.
Give yourself
a chance to heal.
Time heals all.
Yeah. Sounds like a man
speaking from experience.
I can tell you and your son
have done some healing together.
Too many mistakes
in the past.
But I always did it for good.
Time heals all.
I guess it's good advice
for both of us.
Mmm, feel better.
- Bye, dear.
- Bye.
So, there's something
I haven't told you.
Oh, my god.
You're pregnant.
What is it?
My mom's coming to visit.
Really?
She freaked out when she heard
about what happened last month
and wanted me to come home,
and when I told her I wasn't,
she insisted on coming here.
- I can't wait to meet her.
- You won't have to wait long.
Ken is headed to the airport
right now to pick her up.
She's coming today?
She's gonna love Ken.
It's all part of my plan.
- Your plan?
- Mm.
I figure Ken will
soften her up a little
before she gets here.
Ah, very smart.
A little manipulative,
but smart.
- Hey.
- Hi, I'm Carole.
Oh! Wait a second,
hold on a sec.
I thought I was supposed to be
picking up Kate's mother,
but no, wait,
you must be her sister.
Ah, no, I am her mother.
Um, but what the hell,
I'll take the compliment.
Ah, smart lady.
This is Kate's
little sister, Zoe.
She's come along
for the ride.
You're kidding.
Does Kate know she's here?
No, it's a surprise.
Well, that's great!
Oh, my goodness.
How about that?
Carole, Zoe, I'm Ken.
- I'm a really good friend of Kate's.
- Hi, Ken.
She couldn't be bothered
to pick us up herself?
Honestly, I couldn't wait
to meet you guys' mom,
so I sort of volunteered.
But getting to
meet her little sister, now,
that's a glorified bonus.
- Please, allow me to help you with your...
- Oh, thank you.
All right. Hold on a s...
So... could you just
hang on to that for me one second?
- This should be fine. Well, you know.
- Got it.
Well.
- Wow.
- Had a good flight?
Um, it was... it was a little bumpy.
- Bumpy? Wow.
- Yeah. A little.
It's hot out.
You're in for some good weather now.
This is us here.
So how did you end up
working with Kate?
Well, let's see.
When I finally finished
my deployment and came home,
let's just say things
got a bit rocky.
Hmm.
Ended up struggling
back to having
any sort
of normal life, right?
You see, I had two bad knees
and a shoulder full of shrapnel.
That was some
real serious pain.
The VA's solution was
a little physical therapy
and a whole lot
of pain meds.
Yeah, well, no,
my days got pretty dark,
and those
antidepressants only made things
a hell of a lot worse.
That sucks.
Oh, it did suck, Zoe.
But thankfully, just as
I was hitting rock bottom
that's when I got a call
from my old friend Robert
that changed my life,
thank God.
Yeah, it was an offer
to come work at a retreat
on a beautiful island.
While I was there
he introduced me to Kate,
and she welcomed me
with open arms.
That's quite a story.
I know. I'm sorry.
Once I get going,
I can be a bit of an open book.
Then you won't mind telling me
what happened here last month.
Yeah, well...
It's certainly
a very direct question, Carole.
Yeah, she does that.
Charms you
just to set you up for the kill.
The press doesn't
seem to have any answers.
An alarming number of
people were killed here
and my daughter could've
been one of them.
I'd like to know why.
Honestly...
Greed.
Greed?
Look, it's kind of a long story,
but I guess the short version is
that a very bad man
tried to use our facility's resources
to get his hands on
a whole lot of seized government money.
Did he succeed?
No.
And your daughter is
a very big part of the reason why not.
Kate is a fighter.
She always has been.
Oh, I know.
Here you go, sir.
As requested.
Thank you.
Just want you to know, sir,
it's been an honor for all
of us to help you recuperate.
Thank you.
Six-two-nine-nine-two.
Ashcroft. Neptune.
One moment please.
Robert, my friend.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Just missed
the sound of your voice.
Huh, I find that
hard to believe.
An unexpected call
on an encrypted line?
I hear you got
a little banged up in Russia.
Hm, well, no big deal.
I'll be fine.
How's our business
transaction? Concluded?
Yes, it has.
Good.
Everything okay, Robert?
I think so.
What is it?
One of your famous hunches?
Maybe.
Was there
anything I should know?
No, Robert.
We have no new security flags
anywhere on the island.
Thanks.
Hmm.
Ah, there's Dave.
Here we are.
Ah, one second.
- Hey, Marcia!
- Hey.
- You're leaving us today?
- I am.
Ken, this is my niece, Janice.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
Well, sad to see
your aunt leavin' us for good.
She is too. We all are.
But after what happened...
with all the years we came to
visit, I've never heard
of anything like what
occured here last month.
An armed assault?
And any information has been
virtually non-existent.
Even the local police
have said nothing.
It just seems like
there should have been
a more thorough investigation.
Look, I respect
the concern for your aunt,
but rest assured
it was dealt with thoroughly,
even if not reported that way,
but I am sorry.
Seriously.
I'll miss you.
You as well. Safe travel.
It's kind of a shame
you have to see it this way.
It used to be something special,
a really impressive place.
Hello, hello.
- There she is. Kate! Oh, baby.
- Mom.
It's so good to see you.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you for coming.
What?
Surprise.
How are you
even more gorgeous?
There is Wi-Fi here, right?
Ah, not exactly, Zoe.
I guess I should have given
you the heads-up about that.
Hey, everybody.
Mom, this is the man
I told you about.
- Paul.
- So nice to meet you, Carole.
I... I heard you saved
my daughter's life.
I... I think I have
to give you a hug.
Well, to be fair,
um, she saved mine first.
Paul, this is my sister, Zoe.
Hi, Zoe.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Like what?
- Like that you're, uh, one tough cookie.
"One tough cookie"?
Isn't she adorable?
Okay, stop.
Not a kid, thank you.
Should I take their luggage
to one of the cabins?
Yes, that would
be great. Thank you.
And do you guys wanna
go straight to your room
- or do you wanna look around first?
- Thanks, Blain.
I'd love to see the rest of the property.
Assuming it's safe to do that?
It's safe.
Ken was nice enough
to tell us a little bit
about what happened
here last month.
It's over now.
Well, I still have
a lot of questions.
Can they wait 'til later?
I suppose so.
Hey, how are you feeling?
Like some asshole
shot me in the shoulder.
Excuse me.
I think if somebody shot me
in the shoulder,
I'd say something
much worse than that.
I'm Kate's mom, Carole.
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
- No, no, please, please. Don't get up.
- She's right.
Take it easy.
Thank you.
You've raised a very
special young lady.
Thank you.
You, um, you wanna leave us
alone for a bit and we'll get acquainted?
Go see what sort of trouble
Zoe's gotten herself into.
Okay.
Paul is a lucky man.
Our children seem to be
quite fond of one another.
I'm sure you're worried
about Kate,
especially after what happened.
Help!
Oh, for fuck's sake, get up.
- Help me!
- I said get up.
Yeah.
I am.
But meeting all of you
wonderful people
is beginning
to put my mind at ease.
Don't tell Kate I said that.
So, how did you guys meet?
- Well...
- It's kind of a...
It's very cozy.
Hey, did you manage
to get a signal?
No, I just have
some movies downloaded.
Don't worry. I won't tell.
You know, Blain, you,
ah, you really outdid yourself
with the, ah,
with the spaghetti.
- You're being serious.
- Oh, absolutely.
- Paul.
- Only the third time this week.
Thank you
for including me, guys.
Um, I had a fun night.
Thank you.
Of course. You're not gonna
stay for dessert?
Um, I'm a little tired.
Well, goodnight.
- Good night.
- Good night, Sasha.
- Have a good sleep.
- Thank you. You, too.
So, what's for dessert?
More pasta?
So, what's Sasha's
connection to this place?
I guess you could say
she's a friend of my dad's.
Is she okay?
I-I don't mean to be rude,
she's...
She just seems almost haunted.
I mean, to put it simply,
she's had some very significant struggles
the last couple of years, and...
She's kind of just
trying to rebuild her life.
I guess all of us
have to do that at some point.
I suppose.
Very true. Very true.
Now I see where Kate
gets her wisdom from.
Oh, he's good.
But seriously, it is. It is true.
You know, a month ago,
all I ever thought about
was my company.
But now...
my priorities have certainly changed.
Oh, pl... You know what?
You guys need to get your own table
with a couple of place cards.
This is...
So cute.
Zoe helping to clear the dishes.
Well, wonders never cease.
I told you this place was magic.
I can see why you like it.
It must be a little different
when people are shooting at you though.
There is that.
But all in all, yeah, it's a good spot.
I have to admit,
I have kind of been holding out.
Hope you might think about
coming back to Michigan for a little while.
I miss you guys. I really do.
You really like him.
I know we just met, but...
it's like nothing
I've ever experienced before.
How long can he stay here?
Doesn't he have to get back to his company?
Well, technically,
we don't even know
we'll have a company
when the dust settles, so...
And he can, technically,
work from anywhere, so
we figured
we'll stay here for a little bit.
She really misses you, Kate.
She's really struggled
over the last couple of years.
I'm really worried
about her.
Why? Did something happen?
Ah, you know what?
This has been so nice. Let's...
let's not talk about this.
- Mom.
- Let's make time to talk tomorrow.
- Okay.
- I'm tired. Maybe...
maybe Ken can take us
back to the cabin.
Hello.
Hey.
I thought you were sleeping.
Nah, I...
couldn't. Couldn't sleep.
Really?
Me neither.
What-What are you reading?
Um...
A book.
- Yeah.
It's not important. Um...
Thanks for dinner.
- Oh.
- I really enjoyed your pasta.
I mean, it wasn't, like,
an Italian pasta, of course, but uh...
You know, since I was really hungry,
I ate it all.
I'm kidding.
- It was good.
- I appreciate your honesty though.
Any time.
- What's up?
- Look, uh, I was just doing some thinking.
- And, um...
- Yeah?
Yeah, I mean...
This has been home for
as far back as I can remember.
And I'm just...
scared of, you know...
what happens now with us.
Where do we go?
I know that f-feeling very well.
My dad and I,
we traveled the world together.
Never actually had a home
because of his work, so...
- I know.
- Moving on
is something
I'm very familiar with.
Well, that was sort of
the other thing I wanted to ask you.
- All right.
- Um, yeah.
Um...
Yeah, I was doing some thinking, and...
wondering if you were...
considering moving on again,
and if you were...
would you consider
moving on with me?
Are you serious?
- Oh, yeah, I'm serious as a heart attack.
- I'm just kidding.
Oh, oh.
- You do this... And I can't tell if you...
- I'd...
I'd love to. I'd love to. Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Of course.
Wow, that... that was easy.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You know, of all the places in the world,
I don't know where to go.
The world is big,
I'm sure we'll find a place.
How about...
mmm... Paris, France?
I-I would say yes.
I've never been to Paris, but...
- absolutely. Uh... Why? Why Paris though?
- Yeah?
Out of everywhere in the world,
just what about Paris?
Well, when... When I was 9 years old,
my dad took me to Paris.
Um...
We were gonna go see my aunt,
she was a ballerina
at the Opéra de Paris.
And, um, I remember
passing by this amazing market,
and I got this ice cream. Oh, my God,
the best ice cream in the world.
And, um, we never made it.
Turns out my aunt was very sick,
that's why we were there, and...
she passed away, so...
I never got to see Swan Lake
- I'm sorry.
- or the Opéra de Paris.
And... yeah.
And because I wanted
to be a ballerina, by the way.
- I didn't know that.
- I know.
I'm actually really flexible, look.
Whee!
Yeah, so...
You're full of surprises.
Well, w...
would you, uh...
feel good about
going to Paris with me?
- We would go.
- You're gonna take me to Paris?
Yes.
- It's not a proposal, I'm just kidding.
- No.
- Could be though, you never kn... I...
- Uh...
- I... I would...
- I'd love to go to Paris with you.
- really... I...
- Promise? Y-You have to promise.
- Pinky.
- Cross my heart...
- Pinky swear.
- ...and hope to die.
But it's a guarantee.
- I like that.
- Yeah?
- We're going to Paris?
- We're going to Paris.
We're going to Paris!
Hey, Dad.
They serve better food
in Russian prisons.
I wouldn't know.
How you feeling today?
A little better now,
thank you.
How's Kate's mom?
Ah, seems to be
growing on her.
We're all going for a hike
up to the waterfall.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could join you.
It's okay.
I know that look.
Well, the work crews are
almost done packing things up.
They should be done
by next week.
What's on your mind?
Kate and I were talking
last night.
Now she's thinking she wants to
go back to Michigan for a while
and spend some time
with her family.
I was thinking
I'd like to go with her.
You should.
Really?
A woman like Kate...
doesn't come along often.
I just don't like the idea
of leaving you here all alone.
I won't be alone.
Ken Blain is always around.
No, he's not.
You and Kate
are good together.
Don't be a fool, son.
See where it goes.
Thanks, Dad.
I see the look in your eyes.
Reminds me
of your mother and me.
Don't let her go, Paul.
Keep her close.
I will.
Hey, Ricky. Ricky?
Ricky, where you at?
Don't tell me you slept through
a graveyard shift again.
Oh, shit!
How's he feeling?
Bored and complaining
about the food.
Getting back
to his old self, I see.
Exactly. I told him
I was thinking
of coming to Michigan
with you.
What'd he say?
He thought it was great.
I like it.
- Get a room.
- Oh! Hoo!
Oh, it's such a beautiful
morning.
- I am so excited to see the waterfall.
- Morning.
Oh, Carole.
You're gonna absolutely love it.
Everybody ready?
Let's do this.
Hot diggity dog!
Yee-haw!
All right, baby.
You guys, you'll get used
to it, don't worry.
Um, I need to
go to the bathroom.
Oh, uh, it's through those
doors, down the hall on the left.
Thanks.
She's cute.
A little mean, but cute.
Hey, Sasha. You coming
on the hike with us?
Guess not.
I think I have
enough for everyone.
What's wrong?
Ah, I thought
I heard something.
Do you hear that?
Yeah, I do, actually.
Kate, what's going on?
- We're unarmed.
- Hands in the fucking air!
- We're unarmed!
- Now, motherfuckers!
They're up!
Why don't you show me
your hands, huh?
- Hey!
- Hey, easy!
Hands off!
Don't turn this
into a tragedy.
We've already disposed of what
was left of your security team.
Put it down.
Sandra! Sandra, no!
No! Sandra! Sandra!
On your feet!
Déjà vu, Robert?
Here we are,
together again, old friend.
Reunited at the Fortress.
It's a little depressing to see
this place like this, though.
No government
security personnel.
It already seems like
a dying husk of its former self.
I think the same about you.
Are you surprised
to see me?
Kevlar.
- Mm-mm.
- You never can be too careful.
- Speaking of...
- Mm-hm.
- Feeling good?
- Yeah. You look good.
- Mm-hm.
You look good.
You never can be
too careful.
I suggest you should
get one of these.
Where's Paul?
Do not worry about him.
It is time
to get you out of bed.
Rise and shine, Robert.
Madris, would you please
give our friend here a hand.
All clear, boss!
Sad.
It's not possible.
Why? Because
your father shot me,
left me to die
like a dog?
Now, you must be Ms. Taylor.
Yes, I can see the resemblance.
You know, there is so
very much you don't know
about Robert Michaels and Paul,
your daughter's new squeeze.
Who knows, maybe
I'll be doing you a favor
by nipping this relationship
in the bud.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay. We are together now.
I'm sorry.
No. No, no.
Do not pity them, Sasha.
It may have been Robert
who freed you from that prison,
but it was also he
who put you in there
- in the first place.
- Bullshit.
You said
you wouldn't hurt anyone.
Yes, it is unfortunate.
However, she really
shouldn't have run.
Isn't that right,
Master Sergeant Blain?
What do you want, Balzary?
What do I want?
That's a good question, Paul.
Have you heard the saying,
"A man's greatest weakness
is tied to his strongest want"?
Alas, I have no doubt that
my greatest weakness is revenge.
But fortunately for me,
revenge and riches
are bundled together now.
Ah. Ulysses,
care to join us?
- Didn't any of you assholes die?
- It's good to see you again.
I should have hit you harder.
- Time to go, Kate.
- Get your fucking hands off her!
Enough!
Ms. Taylor,
everything will be fine
as long as Paul
and his old man cooperate.
This isn't what we talked about.
Nobody gets hurt. That's what you said.
Shh. You're right,
you're right,
you're right, you're right,
you're right, you're right.
Okay, the girl
should not have been killed
and I am sorry
about that, truly.
But the rest, the rest is...
this is all an act.
It's all part of the act.
I need you
to trust me on that, okay?
And then you and I will get the
'happily ever after' we deserve.
Take him out to pasture.
But do it away from here.
I don't want the wife to know.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here's your
15 minutes of fame.
Do you believe
in karma, Paul?
Where did you take Kate?
You see, when you end up in the
same place that you started,
it's time to take
a hard look in the mirror
and ask yourself,
what is it that I'm doing?
Why does the same thing
keep happening to me?
Where'd you take her,
you son of a bitch?
Where?
Watch it, pretty boy.
Perhaps because it's exactly
what you deserve.
All right, boss. We're in.
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
God bless technology.
Now, I'm gonna simplify
things this time.
You see, I pride myself
on learning from my mistakes.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
using this system
to buy shiny silver bars
that just happen to be on sale.
Go for it. Do your worst.
Today's game
is 1.1 billion in silver,
for a familiar sum of
600 million in cold, hard cash.
This again? Look, you know I don't have
access to that money now. It's gone.
I told you
he would say that.
Investbia is about to be dissolved
by federal prosecutors and FinCEN.
Your transaction violated
about 15 federal laws.
Everything has been seized.
That money is gone.
You see, we had a bet
as to whether you could
access the money or not.
Denton here thinks...
he agrees with you.
I, however, do not.
My account is still intact,
just sitting there in
an encrypted evidence file
at the U.S. Treasury, awaiting
international litigation.
Like I said, gone.
No, Paul! Not gone!
Just locked.
And last week, when
the encryption was updated
for security protocol...
my hackers found it,
there at the back door.
Then have them
get it for you.
They tried.
They failed. Some died.
Maybe you can.
How?
Oh, Jesus, no.
No, please.
Don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Don't do this, please!
Let's see
what's possible now, Paul.
Fuck this shit.
So, you guys serve?
Marines.
That's good.
See any action?
Two tours in Afghanistan.
How 'bout you, my friend?
My friends
don't point guns at me.
But yeah, 15 years
on the other side of the fence.
Oh, you were Delta?
Yep, and Green Beret
after that.
Impressive. Hope you
don't take offense.
Look, uh,
at least do it
up there, okay?
Just let me enjoy
the view one last time.
Move. Keep walking.
Who are these people?
It's a long story.
They're just after money.
Kate will be okay.
Hey, you.
Untie her hands.
She's not goin' anywhere.
Oh, I bet your mother's
proud of you.
Shut your mouth,
or I'm gonna shut it for you.
Oh, he talks.
I'm impressed.
It appears to be the original
access mark to your account,
but all local credentials
have been wiped,
I guess,
for evidentiary purposes.
The only chance is to go through
FinCEN administrative SSL portal.
And it looks like all the
administrator privileges are...
still operational,
for some reason.
There.
You're back in.
What is this?
It's your account.
There's only 300 million there.
Where's the rest of it?
I guess whoever has access to it must have
figured out how to somehow...
- What are you up to?
- I'm not up to anything.
You asked me to get you
into the account. You're in.
Where's the rest
of my money?
How the fuck should I know?
Like last time, you said
you can't trust the government.
I mean, there's maybe what,
30 Treasury employees
that have access to the account,
maybe someone got greedy.
God.
If you're lying,
when I leave this island,
I'm taking Kate's
pretty little head with me.
I'm not lying.
You can walk away right now
with 300 million dollars.
That's a whole
hell of a lot of money.
Enter the authorization code
before any more
of my money disappears.
- The code!
- Okay, okay.
All right.
There.
Now, can I please use the
bathroom before I piss my pants?
Madris, go with him.
Thank you.
You mind?
What, do you wanna hold it?
What the fuck is this?
You never seen
a zipline before?
I have.
You should take a ride.
You run a quarter mile.
I'll just wait here.
No need to worry about me.
On your knees.
I didn't spend half my life fighting
for this country to die on my knees.
Kill him.
All right. Fine.
You win.
Shit.
This is for Sandra.
Nice try.
You son of a bitch.
- Oh, Zoe! Zoe!
- What happened?
They took Kate to some... some cabin.
Graffiti on the walls.
Paul, what are
you talking about?
You got...
you gotta tell someone.
Tell who, Paul?
Just go... go...
go tell someone.
Paul!
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Easy, chief.
Boss needs to see you
down at the Fortress.
What?
Why?
I don't ask questions.
I just follow orders.
Just like you taught me.
You really
are a disgusting piece
of fucking shit, aren't you?
We never should've hired you.
Go ahead. Call the boss.
Check it out.
Call Balzary.
Sleep tight, big boy.
No needle.
It shoots the drug so fast
it breaks the skin.
It's an amazing little toy.
Now...
I think it's time
that you and I
get to know each other.
Oh, it's time to buy
a whole lot of silver bullion.
Not as much as I had hoped,
but no one would call me a greedy man
now, would they, Denton?
Not even close.
Why is
Kate's video feed off?
Check in with Ulysses.
Ulysses.
Why the hell is
Balzary so mad at you all?
Ulysses?
What did you do?
Is it drugs? Or money?
Murder?
You might like it rough,
but I don't think you're the violent type.
Okay, it's done.
Transaction has been processed.
A third party
will hold the funds
until the bullion is
authenticated and certified.
This all will be tracked back
to this facility, correct?
Should put Robert
in a tight spot with the feds.
Are you saying
I'm driven by revenge?
Not at all.
Oh. Well, I am.
Where are they?
I'm trying to figure out.
Go see what's going on.
All right.
And you come to Papa.
Madris?
Hey.
What happened?
Fucking clocked me with
the fucking fire extinguisher.
- Jesus.
- He got away.
You're the one
who's telling the boss.
Fuck you.
Paul is gone.
What?
There is a secret passageway
in the bathroom.
Of course there is.
Why wouldn't there be?
Find him.
Or I kill you.
Go check on Ulysses.
Oh.
And where the hell
is my wife?
No!
I think
it's time to cut off
one of your pretty
little fingers.
No!
Stop!
No! Stop!
No!
Now look,
I promise you
you're not gonna get hurt
unless you put up a fight.
I have no intention
of hurting you.
God, you got great legs.
How about a dance?
I ain't asking.
All right, let's do this
the hard way, huh?
Zoe. Zoe! You okay?
Yeah, but somebody shot Paul with a dart gun,
and he said that they took Kate somewhere.
- Where?
- I don't know. Something about a cabin with graffiti.
- Port Arthur, near Cascade Falls.
- So, you know where it is?
Yeah. It's gonna take us
a while, though.
We need a vehicle
of some kind. Uh...
Wait, what about those?
What?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'll work.
All right,
I like the way you think.
Stay close.
Easy. Easy.
In 3 seconds.
Zoe, down!
Shit!
Time to go, come on! Fuck!
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
- There's a rope on here.
- Yeah, so what?
Stop.
Drop it!
Going to shoot me
with my own gun, malishka?
Don't come any closer.
Or what?
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, you're okay.
You had no choice.
You just saved
both of our lives, Zoe.
Do you understand me?
You're a hero.
All right?
Listen, I need you
to keep it together, please.
All right?
We gotta go.
All right, you're okay.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Frederic said he just
wanted to get his money.
He promised me
no one would get hurt.
I never should have
believed him.
It's okay. I understand.
If you can't trust your own
husband, who can you trust?
When I saw the video
of you tied up like that,
it was exactly
what they did to me in Russia.
No one deserves
to be treated like that.
Let's get out of here
before he wakes up.
What are you doing?
Looking for keys.
Keep smirking.
Gonna get yourself killed.
Have you seen Sasha?
No, sir.
She decided
to stay away from you.
- I'm sorry. Were you saying something about my wife?
- Stop. Stop it!
Why? Why, Robert?
Why should I?
She doesn't have anything
to do with this.
You really haven't figured
this out yet, have you, Robert?
I really just wanna
make you suffer.
Then point the gun at me.
Too easy.
Hm-hmm.
Where's Paul?
Oh, he slipped away
like the little
sewer rat he is.
Hm. Good.
Oh, I'll find him.
Oh, I will.
I got my money.
Maybe not all of it, hm,
but enough.
I could leave right now and
live a very comfortable life.
But you know,
I'm not ready to do that.
Not 'til I kill
Paul and Kate.
No!
Shh!
But you, Robert.
Oh, Robert. No, no, no, no.
I won't kill you.
I used to want nothing more
than to take your life.
But I've realized
the best way to hurt you
is to destroy
every little thing you love.
Keep an eye on them.
Zoe!
Denton. I'm going to go
bid our friend adieu.
When I'm gone, would you please
take care of that loose end for me?
Good man.
Hm.
Farewell, Robert.
I wanted you to know...
I truly enjoyed the time
we spent together
years ago as colleagues.
You, my mentor,
meant the world to me.
I considered you
a true friend.
And this is why
your betrayal
hurt so much.
And why
I must make you...
suffer.
Get up!
Don't get too comfortable.
What the fuck?
What, are you gonna
cut me now?
- That's entirely up to you.
- Ha.
Where are the keys?
Ah, come closer
and I'll tell you.
- Here's how this works. Are you watching?
- Yeah.
Always keep the blade
at a 45-degree angle,
one quick motion
from the neck to the belt.
But not today.
Ah.
You are a crazy
fucking bitch.
Where are the keys?
You're not gonna kill me.
Oh, here.
Under the fucking
floorboard.
Don't move.
Freeze!
Get out of the car.
What the hell
are you doing here, Sasha?
Come on, get these bitches!
Now, tell me,
what the fuck
is going on here?
Ulysses, come in.
Ulysses,
do you fucking copy?
Go for Ulysses.
There you are.
I was beginning
to worry about you.
Tell me you still
have Kate.
I've got Kate right here
in front of me.
What's your ETA
to extraction?
- About ten minutes.
- Good.
Swing by the Fortress
and pick me up on your way.
Copy.
But there's something else.
Sasha's here.
Why?
I... I don't know, boss.
Bristow got here before me,
and he drugged me.
Fuck!
Bring her and Kate,
and we'll go
to the extraction point.
Roger that.
Hurry.
You're driving.
Mother and daughter...
back together again.
Time to head
to your rendezvous point.
You know Balzary.
He doesn't like...
Kate!
Finally!
- Where have you been?
- Let them go.
You know I can't do that.
Then I have
nothing to say to you.
Are you okay?
Have you seen Zoe?
What about Paul?
There. Kate's inside.
You need to wait here.
Stay alert.
Don't move.
Come on.
- Place is empty.
- What are those?
Useful toys for later.
Let's get back.
All right, we're all going
to the extraction point,
one big happy family.
- Frederic.
- The matter's not up for discussion.
Drop it, hero.
Drop it.
Now walk. Easy.
Walk.
Look what I got.
Well, well.
Good to see you.
We were just about to leave.
You can join us.
Balzary.
Check his quarters.
Well, Robert. Why am I not
surprised to hear your voice?
Let everyone go.
We can work something out.
We tried that.
The first time, you stole
600 million dollars from me.
The second time, you shot me
and left me for dead.
I'm beginning to think
I can't trust you, Robert.
It's empty.
And Denton's out cold.
Where are you, Robert?
You won, Balzary.
Nothing is worth
what you're doing.
It's over.
Well, maybe I will.
But first your son dies.
No, please, no!
No, please!
Please, no!
Paul's blood
is on your hands, Robert.
Just stop this!
Let them go!
- What is wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you?
You lied to me.
You said no one would get hurt.
You said you'd get your money
back and we would leave.
These people betrayed us.
These people took me in.
Gave me a place to stay.
Because Robert felt guilty.
He's the one
responsible for everything
- that happened to you in Russia.
- Really?
Don't you get that?
Robert is the one
who got me out of there!
And we both know
the only reason I was there
is because
you couldn't pay your debts.
- Because of Robert!
- Listen to yourself, Frederic!
You stole their money
in the first place!
He was just doing his job!
Everything I've done
was for us.
Bullshit.
This has all
been about you.
None of this
is about us.
The helicopter
will be here any moment.
Just the two of us,
we'll get out of here.
No, it won't.
I called it off.
You what?
That's right.
After I saw what you were
doing, I called it off.
I think it's time
to stop running, Frederic.
It's time
to take responsibility.
So now you betray me.
Just like everybody else.
I should have
seen that coming.
Betrayal.
Go ahead.
You've already destroyed me.
Finish the job.
- Hey!
- Duck!
Zoe, go hide with your mom.
You know where.
Kate...
I'm going back in.
I gotta finish this.
Paul!
Go!
Drop it, big boy.
Nice and slow.
Oh, never disappoint.
Where's my money, Robert?
Where's my money?
I made a deal with Tomlinson.
The government
accepted my down payment
on the Fortress property.
It belongs to a new private
cyber-security firm.
Run by yours truly.
I'm gonna
fucking kill you, Robert.
I'm gonna fucking kill...
I'm sorry.
Robert, I didn't mean...
I didn't mean that, Robert?
I just wanna talk.
Show your face
so I can fucking shoot it!
Fuck! I just wanna talk.
Where are you?
Where are you, Robert?
Come on.
Show your face.
Where the fuck
are you, Robert?
Hey.
Kevlar.
Shit! Fuck!
Nope.
Babe.
You're gonna be all right.
Thank you, sweetie.
I need this.
You doing okay, Zo?
Yeah.
So glad I came.
Scooch over.
Look at what
you went through today.
That was pretty
extraordinary, what you did.
Thanks, Mom.
Okay, no, but for real...
you were amazing.
And I'm really proud of you.
And...
Paul and I are excited about
coming home for a little bit.
I think the change
of scenery will be good.
And I think, you know,
you can put him to work
in the backyard or something.
He doesn't really strike me
as a mowing-the-lawn kind of guy.
Is he a shrub-trimming kind of guy?
'Cause I... I really need one of those.
I'm thinking... I'm thinking...
That's so cute!
Retail + transcript by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull