I had fun tonight.
Yeah, it was a beautiful night.
Yeah.
Uh, the stars really bring out your eyes.
You're so sweet.
Look! A shooting star!
You have to make a wish.
Uh... I wish...
this moment could last forever.
- Geez!
-What was that?
I don't know.
Let's check it out.
What is that?
I don't know.
Come on! Let's go!
Open!
My keys!
Jutta, when you get this, call me back.
Suena, I just heard that...
Don't!
My brother's family's up
north about a hundred miles.
They were hit first
and I've been trying to get
in touch with them for hours.
Is Lukale safe at home at least?
No.
They're keeping them at school
since we're here on the base.
At least I know he's safe.
Unless that toxic smoke comes down here
or more of those things fall from the sky.
At least we're here doing something.
I'd rather be doing something than nothing.
We're doing something.
Besides, he's safe.
How's your brother?
The hospital lines are down.
Nothing on his cell.
Be safe.
At ease.
Sir, our allies in the Eastern Hemisphere
have declared emergency
across the continent
as most satellite networks around the globe
have been knocked offline.
Now it would be advisable
to follow their lead
or lead by example to raise alarm, sir.
Deploy troops to investigate
and maintain order.
Any word from the Commander?
All personnel are on complete lockdown
until further instructions, sir.
Sir?
I've been fielding calls from
specialist agencies all morning.
Climate scientists and the space agency
are telling us that the
carbon monoxide levels
from these asteroids are unprecedented.
It's like an extinction level event,
but something isn't adding
up in these reports.
Such as?
Well, first off, our
radars didn't detect them
when they entered our atmosphere.
And I've noticed that all of the asteroids,
or at least their blast zones,
are roughly the same size.
I mean, in some cases, they're identical.
That can't be normal, sir.
Who is this?
This is Lieutenant Wellesh from Cyber Ops.
Ashlaya Wellesh, sir, Cyber Ops Specialist.
Wellesh, unless there's some
sort of breach in our network
that I'm not aware of, I don't understand
what this has to do with
you or your department,
so if you don't mind...
Sir, we're painfully under-staffed
because of the stay-at-home order.
Now we need to act fast
and this information
may be pertinent to the next...
Sir, if I may?
Wellesh! Read the room.
As you can tell, I've
assembled a crack team.
And from what we already
know about the situation,
this is far, far beyond your clearance.
Now for the record, I agree with you.
We must identify the
source of the toxic clouds
in order to minimize fatalities, okay?
Sir, we need to treat this as
a matter of national security.
It's only a matter of time before things
take a violent turn out there.
We need boots on the ground.
No! What we need is to help
the people who've been affected
the worst and evacuate
the areas in proximity
to these asteroids until we
know more about their origin.
We need to identify the
source of the toxic clouds.
Deploy a recon squad asap.
Right away, sir!
With all due respect, sir,
you are making a wrong call.
We are up against something
that we have never seen before!
All non-essential personnel are dismissed.
I appreciate your concerns, Wellesh.
Now if you'll let us do our jobs, please.
That means you, Wellesh.
- Thanks, Shanel.
-Yeah.
Help me seal up this window.
Sorry. Just a little anxious.
You and me both!
I don't know which one's
worse, Stawvak or Skuller.
Jutta!
Ash! Finally!
The phones are all messed up up here.
I was getting worried.
Me, too. Where are you?
Just about to head out
with the squad on patrol,
orders courtesy of your pal, Skuller.
Oh, God!
I hate the idea of you going out there
when we have no idea what's going on.
I know, but look at it this way.
You said the same thing right
before my desert tours, right?
Okay, yeah, I just...
Look, I just have a really
bad feeling about this.
No, no, no, no, don't say that. Come on.
No. I just...
Just be careful.
My number one priority is getting back
to my incredible wife and son.
Any word from his school?
Yeah. They're keeping them there
until we know what's going on.
Look, I know you're worried. I get it.
It's scary out there.
I'm gonna make two promises.
Promises?
Okay, I'm listening.
First, I'm gonna be extra
careful to make sure
I get back in one piece.
Then when things go back
to normal, which they will,
me and you and Luka are gonna go camping,
someplace beautiful, get
away from all the people
and the noise.
Well, that does sound like something great
to look forward to at least...
Ash, I gotta get going on now. I love...
What? Jutta, I can't...
Love you, Ash! Love you!
Jutta?
This is Patlin. I can't get to the phone.
Please leave a message.
This is your sister. I'm
sure the hospital is crazy.
Call me as soon as you can.
All right. Someone will be with
you guys momentarily, all right.
Be patient, everyone.
Please, please.
Miss, you still with me?
That smoke... everyone was running.
My brother, he...
I know.
Can you tell me your name?
It's Tomeka.
Very good, Tomeka, very good.
Okay, right now all I need
you to do is breathe, okay?
- All right.
-Breathe.
Perfect.
Good, good. You got this.
You got this.
Okay, listen up, team!
Alpha team have been deployed.
They'll report back with intel
from the Northern Quadrant.
Be prepared for hostile activity.
We're going in locked and fully loaded.
Sir, yes, sir!
Sir, it was our understanding
that this was supposed to
be a strictly recon mission.
Has there been word of civil unrest?
We don't what to expect in here.
But from Skuller's orders,
I can gather that something's not right.
Proceed with extreme caution.
Be prepared.
Take down anyone or anything
you find in that smoke.
At anything, sir?
I knew it. Didn't I tell you, Samad?
There's some dirty bomb
terrorists crap out there.
Sanchino, again with the conspiracy stuff?
Nah, this?
I reckon this is just
the tip of the iceberg.
It's time for our kind to say "bye-bye".
Open the case.
All right, everyone grab a mask.
We do not leave this truck until
your masks are completely secured.
You hear me?
- Yes, sir.
-Yes, sir.
Wellesh, you good?
Yeah.
I just gotta grab something.
Quick as you can, soldier!
Luka, my man!
I tried calling you like I always do.
Listen. They're sending me out and...
Jutta, now!
Look, I gotta go.
Love you, bud.
Come on.
Major! Update!
Sir, the squad has just been deployed.
Status?
General Skuller?
Wellesh, what are you doing here?
You need to see this.
I've just received updated reports
that the asteroids are
causing seismic activity.
Asteroids will cause seismic
activity upon impact.
No, sir. I mean after impact.
They're moving underground.
We've never seen anything like this.
It could be that the smoke
is just the beginning of
something that's much worse.
Sir, I need your eyes on this squad asap.
What are you suggesting?
Sir, my husband is in that squad
along with a lot of other great officers.
We don't know what we're sending them into.
It could be a suicide mission.
I think you need to
pull them out right now.
Cabbon's squad is entirely capable
of handling this situation.
And this is precisely what
your husband was trained to do.
But, sir, we have never seen anything...
Wellesh.
Enough.
Clear.
Squad, fan out.
Clear? How can you tell?
Can't see anything in this.
Sir?
We're picking up some unusual
frequencies on our network.
It could be radioactive
energy from the asteroid or...
something else.
Something else, Major?
Sir, our soldiers, they're
not alone out there.
Fall back!
I didn't... I didn't see anything.
Sir, what's your status? Over.
Thought I saw something.
Just keep breathing.
It's your biology trying to protect you.
Anyone have eyes on that?
Do you have any activity?
Alpha, do you have any
activity on your end? Over.
Hey, what's going on?
Alpha team, what's your status, come in!
- Okay, guys! -We're on high alert!
Home base, this is Bravo team.
We are in contact!
We need immediate assistance!
Do you copy? Over!
Bravo team, this is home base.
Copy troops contact.
Sending additional troops to your AO. Over.
We are handling this situation!
That is my husband.
Quiet!
Wait. Is that our comms?
Can you ask him if he can hear that?
No, ask him if he can hear...
can we get a live feed on one of...
Lost eyes on Campbell. A-team is down.
Teams all inactive. Hostiles present.
We have eyes!
It's just white.
Wait! I see something.
You got eyes on?
Home base! I need backup!
Now! Over!
Sir, it looks like the smoke is clearing.
Oh, sweet God, it's over.
Sir, the fog is lifting,
but we've lost contact
with all but one soldier.
Come on, Jutta. Please.
Jutta, please, please, please.
What the hell was that?
Sir, we're detecting
several heat signatures.
It's as though the asteroid smoke
was shielding them from detection earlier.
I'm calling in an air strike
before this escalates any further.
No! Jutta's still out there!
Hey, hey! What do you think you're doing?
Jutta, if you can hear me,
I need you to get out of there right now.
- Wellesh! -Run! Get out of there!
Home base, hostiles confirmed!
Send backup! Over.
Jutta?
Home base! Jutta! Lost contact!
Please send backup! Repeat, Hostiles...
present! Over!
- Ashlaya...
-Jutta!
Save our son.
This is General Skuller calling
for an immediate air strike.
Enemy grid zero-niner-seven-six-four.
Repeat, zero-niner-seven-six-four.
Affirmative.
All right, listen up!
We don't know who they are,
where they're from, what they want.
We do know that they attacked first.
They don't like our people, our politics,
what we think, the way we live.
We do know that they have
more advanced weaponry
than anything we've ever encountered.
I warned you before you sent them in.
Effective immediately,
this entire building will
go on emergency lockdown.
All personnel, to your combat
positions until further orders.
Dismissed.
Hug your child one last time.
Hey!
You're defying a direct order!
Ah!
Sis, pick up!
Damn it! Come on! Where's my reception?
Oh, wait!
Pat? Patlin?
Patlin? I can't hear you! Is that you?
Damn it!
Okay, guys! Don't panic!
I'm sure the backup generator
will kick on any second now!
Please evacuate the building
in an orderly manner!
in an orderly fashion!
Please evacuate the building
Luka, come on!
Luke, hurry! The coast is clear...
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Please, please.
Oh, my... No!
No!
Luke? Luke!
Oh, my God!
Baby!
They killed Shanel.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Mom's here, okay, okay?
But we gotta go, we gotta go, okay?
Yeah.
You ready? We're gonna go right now!
Okay, come on! Come on!
Okay, essentials only.
If you can live without it, just leave it.
Five minutes, five minutes!
Mom, when's Dad getting home?
Won't Dad know what to do?
Where is he?
He's not out there, is he?
Mom? Mom!
Luke, baby, um, sit down.
So, sweetie, um...
you know your dad's job
sometimes it can be really,
really dangerous and, um...
Sometimes, uh...
Where is he?
Sometimes...
Mom, where is he?
Dad's not coming home.
Luke, baby, listen to me.
Dad would...
Your dad wants us to be safe, okay?
So we've gotta leave.
Luke, honey?
Look, I get you. I do, baby, I do.
This is hard, I know, I know.
Baby, I know it's been hard
for all of us today, okay?
But it's just you and me
now, it's just you and me.
We gotta keep it together and
we gotta get moving, okay?
We've gotta get outta here
before they come this way.
Come on, okay?
What are they after?
Baby, I don't know.
Was Dad fighting them?
Yes.
- He was trying to save us?
-Yes.
Baby, that is all he ever wanted to do.
Oh, my God.
Luke, baby, we gotta go.
We gotta go right now.
Come on. Come on, baby.
Come on, we gotta go.
Maybe it's all right if it kills us all.
Hey! Hey! You listen to me, Lukale!
Your father sacrificed his life for you,
for me, for all of us, okay?
And we are gonna honor
him by staying alive!
Do you understand me?
Yes.
All right then. Grab
your stuff and let's go!
Come on!
Come on, baby!
Ah!
Go, go, go! Come on!
Come on.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Damn it!
Hey, fella.
I was just leaving.
You on your own? What's in the bag?
You got meds?
Look, I'm a doctor. This is for patients.
- I can't give them to you.
-Good for you.
Let me see what sort of
stuff you got in there, doc.
It's been a rough day, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm doing the best I
can just like you, man.
Don't make me ask again, doc.
Let me see what's in the bag.
Look, I don't want any problems.
Me neither.
Then I'm sure you can find whatever
you're looking for in here.
People took everything. They're desperate.
Turned 'em in to animals.
Now I don't even care what's in the bag.
Just give it to me.
Don't move!
I don't want to have to use
this thing, but it's loaded.
And I'll shoot if I have to!
Don't be stupid, doc.
I just wanted to get a water or something!
God, why did you make me do this?
The world goes to hell and the next day
you're coming after your own people?
There not enough pain out there for you?
This is them.
It doesn't have to be us.
Damn it.
Lukale?
- Lukale?
-Mom!
You okay?
- Yeah, no, I'm fine.
-I was just peeing.
You need to tell me if you're gonna leave.
You were asleep.
Wake me up next time. We
got to stay together, okay?
- Okay.
-All right.
It's close.
Yeah, it was.
No, no, hey, grab your bags!
- We're leaving the car? -Yeah.
We're gonna walk.
Run! Just run! Come on, baby! Come on!
Where are we going?
Come on, baby. Come on!
- Mom, wait!
-Come on!
Wait! I don't hear anything.
- I don't hear anything.
-Shh!
Okay. Okay, you're right.
We should keep moving, though.
We can just slow down a bit.
Come on.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Look!
Do you think anybody's home?
Let's find out, come on.
Hello? Hello?
It's okay. Come on, babe.
So, sweetie, why don't you...
Why don't you get some rest?
Sweetheart?
Okay.
All right.
We're gonna be okay.
Lukale!
Think it will just pass by.
Now that don't look right.
- Get back!
-Okay, okay, wait!
What the hell you guys doin' in my RV, huh?
We lost our car! We were walking all night.
We found this. We thought it was empty.
We needed a place to rest!
You see how it is out there!
Okay, the door was broken.
Could you please stop
pointing that at my kid?
Shut up!
You can point at me instead, please?
Stay calm, Luke.
Get your little skinny ass over here, man.
Now!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Anybody else up in here?
Nope, nope, nope, it's just us.
It's just me and my kid.
I'm putting it down.
Nobody's gonna jump out from behind?
- Nope, nope.
-Huh?
It's just us! It's just me and the kid.
Now what about you, little man?
You wanna try something?
No, sir.
Good.
All right, all right.
Everybody just take a minute.
All right.
I ain't gonna lie.
It's kinda good to have company.
Great. Yeah, yeah, we're
great company, right babe?
You guys hungry?
You really didn't have to do all of this,
so thank you... what's your name?
They call me Tiago, but you
can call me T if you want.
Okay. Well, thank you, T.
I'm Ashlaya and my boy's name
is Lukale, but we call him Luke.
Well, tell him to come over here, ma'am.
The food's ready.
Luke, baby?
Food's ready.
What about you? You gonna eat?
Um, I'll wait 'til he eats, yeah.
Get all you want, kid.
Get it while it's hot.
Baby, chew, chew.
Don't want you to choke after
everything we've been through.
I'll tell you what. Today's your lucky day.
I'm gonna give you guys the RV here.
You guys can take it.
I don't need it no more.
No, no.
We were just crashing 'til we
could figure out the next move.
It's cool.
Luke, you wanna give us a minute?
Listen, I didn't wanna say it
when the kid was around, right?
But there's been a lot of talk on the box.
You got people hiding in ditches, sewers.
There's people hiding out like us, man.
It's a damn shithole, right?
Hiding in a sewer?
I mean, that's no kind of
long-term strategy for survival.
Ain't nothin' long-term no more, lady.
All that's over.
Don't you see what's happening there?
It's everyone for themselves, right?
So what I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna hook you guys up
with some food.
I'm gonna send you on your way.
You guys do you and I'll do me.
Okay. Well, it's not me for myself.
It's me for my kid.
And we're the only thing
that we have left, so...
I'm not looking for friends, all right?
Especially some mom and a kid
dragging their feet
around, slowing me down!
I can't have it!
But there's safety in numbers.
I mean, we got this far.
And what do you wanna do, huh?
You wanna try to fight a whole alien army?
That's your plan?
If I have to to keep my kid safe, I would.
All right, well, good
luck with that, all right?
I mean, come on.
You got a family, right?
Right?
Of course, lady, we all got family.
Okay, then you understand.
I mean, you wouldn't want your family,
you wouldn't want your wife,
your kids out here alone!
You know what it's like! Don't bail on us!
Please?
Listen, lady, lady,
we all got our own problems
right now, all right?
I already told you, you do what
you do, I'm gonna do what I do.
Mom, just forget about it!
Look, look.
I know you're a better man than that.
You are not gonna leave us alone!
We have no place to go.
And I've got to get him
someplace safe, please!
Please!
All right.
I got a spot that's secure.
You guys can tag along, but
don't slow me down, all right?
No, no. We'll keep up, yeah!
Luke, we keep up. We're tough. We're tough.
All right.
Well, if you keep up
and you guys carry your
own shit, all right.
Grab those supplies and let's go. Come on.
Okay. Grab our stuff, Luke.
So, where are you from?
We're not doing that today, all right?
Okay...
Hey, hey, hey!
Need to stop going ahead of us, all right?
Yeah, baby, just chill.
Just stay behind me, okay?
Preferably on this side. Thank you.
Keep an eye on him, okay?
I will, I will.
- Hear that?
-What? What? I...
I can hear you!
Are you friend or foe?
Do you come in peace or pieces?
'Cause I don't care anymore.
I don't.
We deserve to die, right?
We're pretty messed up.
So, Judgment Day. That's what today is.
It's the day everything
comes crashing down.
Are you hiding?
It is not gonna work.
They'll find you eventually.
Shit, they'll find all of us.
We're dead men walking.
You know what the irony is?
I'm still alive.
You know who's dead?
Nice people.
Priests, dead.
Children, gone.
Moms and Dads... and we're left?
The miserable, the scared...
Agh!
Go, go, go!
Oh, God!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
All right.
We gotta get you seated, man.
Sorry. It's a bit of a
free-for-all at the moment.
Just find a spot.
It's better than being outside.
Was wondering if you could use some help?
I'm a doctor.
Oh, my God, yes!
Yes, please!
Just set yourself with
anyone who needs help, okay?
All right, my man. Let me
take a look at you, okay?
No point.
We're like sitting ducks in this place.
Why don't you try and relax and I'll...
Why don't you just run while
your legs will still carry you?
I can't. I have to help these people.
You know they're coming back
for us to finish the job.
We're not getting off that easy.
We can stay in here for
the time being, all right?
All right.
Is this the secure place?
It's as safe as we're gonna get right now.
But is it safe?
It's safe enough, man.
You and your mom wanna go
back to the RV or what?
- Makes no difference to me.
-No!
No, no, no, no.
Luke, this is good,
this is good, all right?
Look, the walls, they're fortified, okay?
So the aliens aren't
gonna be able to see us
moving around in here.
I think this is the safest
we're gonna get for right now.
If you say so.
I knew I had a good feeling about you, T.
Hey, look. It's four walls.
Nobody's gonna be able to try to get us.
There's a couple of prisoners inside.
But as long as you guys are with me,
they ain't gonna mess with you, all right?
Wait. There's still prisoners inside?
Let's go. You coming or what?
Yeah, yeah.
So, um, how long have you worked here?
About four to five years.
I was getting ready to be a
sheriff, but all this went down.
Just for the record, I think you
would have made a great sheriff.
Just follow me, all right?
Everything been good here?
Yeah? All right.
Here. Put these bags over there.
Give me your bag, lady.
- All right.
-All right.
Go on.
- All right, follow me down here.
- All right.
I always walk ahead of you, all right?
So where are the other guards?
You're looking at him.
Just you?
Yeah. This place became a shelter, man,
ever since this happened.
Got prisoners here. We
even got some citizens.
What happens if the
prisoners tried to break out?
More food for us. Let's go. Come on.
You could take this one here.
Best I could do for now.
You should be safe.
Okay.
I know it's not a suite or anything,
but it's better than the RV, right?
Yeah. The RV's probably
burned to a crisp by now.
All right. What about you, little man?
Wanna get in your room?
Wait, Lukale. Why don't
you stay here with me?
In this tiny cell? Together?
Yeah, I don't want us to split up.
He'll be all right.
I'm just gonna put him next door.
Kid's probably hungry anyway, yeah.
- Okay.
-Want some more food?
Sure.
Let's go. Right this way.
I'm watching.
We'll be back to check on you, all right?
Okay.
Hey, Luke?
Lukale? Luke?
Lukale?
Has anyone seen my son?
Any... oh, God.
What do you know about shooting so far?
Anything?
Let's see what you got.
Uh, well, uh...
I know I'm supposed to bend my knees...
slightly.
Uh-huh.
And visualize the bullet making impact
and squeeze the trigger and inhale...
or like so?
First off, you're holding
the gun wrong, all right?
When you hold the gun and you aim,
you always want to support this
hand with this hand, understand?
Right.
Gives you that extra
strength when you shoot.
- Got it?
-Got it.
And let me tell you something, bro.
You're trying to tell
me if all these aliens
come attacking you, right?
The best thing you're gonna
do is bend some knees,
pray and meditate?
You think that's gonna handle it?
- Come on, dawg. -I mean, I just thought...
Yeah, you think too much, man.
That's your problem, all right?
Calm down. Relax.
Check this out.
You're loaded. Take the gun.
Keep your finger off the trigger
'til you're ready to shoot.
Hit these bottles right here.
All right, give it your best shot.
You think I was gonna give
you a loaded gun, huh?
- Is that what you thought?
- You're crazy, man.
- Come on, man.
-You're crazy.
Look, the world's gone
crazy, but not Tiago, right?
Let me show you how to do it, all right?
- Look, check this out.
- Mom, were you watching?
Oh, just a little bit.
I am one with the gun.
You guys suck. You both suck!
Ah, kids, right?
Yeah.
What you gonna do?
Can't love 'em, can't hate 'em.
Good to see him smile, though.
Thank you again for taking us in, Tiago.
I really appreciate it.
And thank you for...
for just being there for Luke.
He's having a hard time, you know...
since his father...
You know.
Nah, nah, I get it.
I like the kid, you know.
He's got a good heart.
He does.
I can only imagine what
you're going through.
I can't even.
I haven't really...
I haven't had any time to process it
with everything going on.
I just...
No time to think about it.
Well, if we survive this,
you're gonna have a lot
of time to think about it.
If... yeah.
I just... I just can't help but think
it should have been me, you know.
It should have been me out there
'cause then Jutta would be alive.
And Jutta could protect Lukale
'cause I am...
barely holding on here.
Don't... don't say that.
I mean, maybe there's a
bigger purpose here, you know.
Maybe you're just not seeing it.
I don't know, but...
Yeah, maybe.
You know, when you asked me earlier,
I didn't wanna tell you
earlier, 'cause I just...
I didn't know you yet like that,
but what does it matter anymore?
I'm from the west side
and when all this went down, you know,
the day that it happened, I was supposed
to take my daughter shopping that day.
And then, uh... Well...
Tiago, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, we're all going through it.
Bad stuff happens, you know.
Yeah, yeah, stuff happens.
Wait. Tiago, hear that?
That's not good.
All right, take cover. Take cover!
Everybody take cover!
Now! Get outta here!
What's goin' on?
Damn it!
We gotta get everybody outta here now.
Right. Everyone grab someone.
We're gonna head up the
stairs, okay, come on!
Everyone help each other! Let's go!
Faster.
Nobody panic!
Oh, God... Okay.
Run!
Okay...
Wait! Wait!
Where are you going?
Come on. Go, go, go!
No!
Oh, God.
All right, come on! Come on!
Everybody load up! Load up!
Load up! Load up! Let's go! Let's go!
One at a time! Come on, one at a time!
Shoot to kill! Shoot to kill!
Shoot to kill! Shoot to
kill, you understand?
Let's get these bastards, man!
Come on! Make 'em pay! Make 'em pay!
Come on, everybody! Take what we got!
That's all we got! Let's go!
Let's keep it moving! Let's keep it moving!
Come on, take what we got!
Come on, come on!
I got you!
All right, we're good.
Listen, everybody fights now, all right?
Everybody! You understand? You get it?
Come on! You know what to do, all right?
Oh, geez!
Take cover!
Run, baby, run! Run!
Get the hell out of here!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get back. Hold on, baby.
Mom?
Mom, what are we gonna do?
We're gonna fight.
Okay, I'm gonna cover you!
You run through there,
were going to find T.
Go! Go!
Get the hell outta here!
What the hell you guys doin' here?
We're fighting and I'm not gonna leave you!
I said get the hell outta here!
And I said we're fighting and staying!
Wait! What are you doing?
Stupid mother...
It's gonna be okay, baby.
We're gonna get out of this.
Here!
- Pull the pin.
-Okay.
Hold up! On my cue!
One, two...
Now!
Ah!
- You got 'em!
-We got 'em!
Yes!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
Is it clear?
All right.
I can't believe we got him.
We actually took these bastards down.
Hold up, hold up. Move in slow.
You don't know if there's more of 'em.
It's still moving.
Look at that thing.
That thing's still moving, man.
It's like twitching.
Shoot it!
Oh, I'm gonna get its gun, man,
or whatever the hell that thing is.
Here, cover me, cover me.
Go!
- You touch that thing! -I
ain't touching that thing!
Cover my ass, man. Shut up!
Thing's heavy.
How the hell you shoot this thing?
Ha-ha!
This thing got power, man!
You wanna mess with me now, huh?
Do it again! Do it again!
It ain't working.
There's more of 'em!
Let's get out here! There's more of 'em!
Hold on, hold on! Let me check!
Come on, come on, come on!
- Hold on, hold on!
-What?
What the hell you doin', lady?
Okay, let's go!
Go, go!
Be careful!
Whoa, whoa!
I can't believe we got past them!
You and me both, man.
You guys understand what this means, right?
Right? I mean, we can fight back!
They're vulnerable!
We can send these monsters
back to where they came from!
And we can make 'em pay
for what they took from us!
I mean, they can't push us around anymore!
That's passion, girl, that's passion.
Did you see the way that the
mothership was leading them?
I mean, that must be where
they acquire their directives.
I don't know.
Sounds kind of military
to me, don't you think?
It is, and without a comms department
as your base of support,
then all your teams are disconnected
and they become even more vulnerable.
I mean, these machines,
they aren't self-powered.
They're being controlled
from somewhere else.
And that means someone is controlling them.
Now we find that controller,
we take out that
controller, no more tripods.
Right, right, right, exactly.
But then who's controlling them?
That's my question.
T, look up!
If we could take out the mothership,
we can take out their entire army!
Hello?
Anybody?
Oh, God. Oh, God!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's gonna be okay! I got you.
Oh, God.
What...
What is this?
I don't know if you can
hear me or understand me,
but why are you doing this?
Can you understand me?
Are you gonna kill me, huh?
Are you hurt?
Are you gonna kill me?
What...
You speak?
Oh... No, no.
No.
Help me.
Okay, easy. Easy.
Okay, I got you.
Okay.
Can you help me?
Yeah, yeah.
You're gonna be okay, all right?
We gotta get outta here.
Okay, come on. I got you.
Let's try to find a spot and post up.
Sounds good.
Rest a little bit.
But you're, uh...
you're trying to say that
the mothership is alone?
- That's what you're saying?
-Yeah.
The mothership's the only
one that can travel alone.
Uh-huh.
That's why we've never seen
just one soldier or one tripod.
'Cause they're taking their
directives from the top.
Standard military practice.
Okay, but how does that help us?
I mean, we're lucky if we survive
another attack like before.
And I don't know how
effective these guns would be
on one of those giant tripods.
I don't know, okay?
But this is good. This is good!
We know that we can hurt them.
We know that they're vulnerable.
And we're gonna beat their asses so bad
that they are gonna wish
that they never met with us!
Don't you want that?
Hell, yeah, that's what we all want.
Kick ass and chew bubblegum, man.
Kill every last one of 'em, but
I think you missed his point.
How we gonna take down the mothership?
That's my question.
I don't know, but look,
if the three of us have gotten this far,
if we're figuring things
out and we're surviving,
then the military has got
to have made more progress.
It's just a matter of time, okay?
I'll buy that.
Nobody move!
Where'd you get that weapon?
What the hell is this?
Stand down! We're not looking for a fight!
That's real funny coming
from a bunch of folks
who just snuck up on us
with their guns drawn.
I invite all of you to lower your weapons
if you just wanna talk.
Identify yourselves! What division are you?
818th.
Mom, wasn't dad 818th?
Yeah, baby, he was.
Your father served in
the Marines, young man?
Yes, sir. Jutta Wellesh.
Your father was Jutta Wellesh?
Gun, lower.
Thank you for your father's
service and his sacrifice.
He was a great man.
I'm truly sorry, ma'am.
You can't be too careful out here.
So what do you want?
We need fighters.
You guys look like you've
been through the mill.
But if you're holding that alien blaster,
I'm assuming someone else isn't.
You're right about that. You
guys haven't upgraded yet?
Some of our squad has.
Our stockpile's growing.
So are our numbers.
We're training, strategizing.
We've even taken some
of those tripods down.
Right on.
Come with us to our bunker and
our General will show you more.
You're gonna wanna meet him.
Just a second.
Okay, you got it, you got it. Okay.
All right, there you... there you go.
Oh, Jesus.
Water's still running.
Looks like you're in luck.
No! Don't touch it! Don't touch it!
It's toxic!
You have it boil it first!
Get it away from me!
Whoa, look, look! It's safe. Look.
Try.
Oh, my God, it's not burning!
It's not burning!
- Why would it burn?
-It's not burning.
I'm Patlin.
Patlin, my name?
It's what people call me.
What do they call you?
Off... Officially, 042-100-Omega-Zeta.
It's not my birth name, though.
That's Gwen.
You have two names?
One is Government issued,
so I could travel.
And kill people? Kill a planet?
I don't expect you to
understand or take pity on me.
What we've done is unforgivable.
- Then why...
-Don't.
What answer would satisfy you?
We are soldiers.
We were told to fight.
We were told that this was the Great War.
War on an innocent planet?
Oh, my God, so much death!
What have we done?
Whoa.
Oh, wow. Stay awake.
Stay with me, Gwen!
I see how you help people.
I see your heart.
Our species have much to learn from you.
Hey, just... just save your
energy for now, all right?
Gwen? Gwen?
We gotta get you to a
hospital or a triage center.
You're gonna lose that
leg if we don't act fast.
No, no, they'll kill me.
You can't. You can't.
Take your armor off.
Excuse me?
Take it off. I have an idea.
On your wrist, is that a military thing?
Be a good idea to hide it.
You have made it this far because...
Where we going?
Hey, where we going?
Quick. Sounds like Skuller
is giving his briefing.
Wait! Did you say Skuller?
Who the hell's this guy? Seriously?
Now we have pinpointed
the source of the attack
to a planet outside the solar system.
Oh, got visitors.
Skuller?
Wellesh!
How come I'm not surprised
you're still around, huh?
All right, back up, man.
You guys know each other or what?
Well, well, well, Wellesh.
Kid, your father died a hero.
Let's make sure it wasn't for nothing.
Hey, the kid's good, all right?
Who are you?
Oh, let's just say I'm
down here for the ride.
So whatever speech you got,
you save it for your soldiers.
But if you need someone to kick
some monster ass, I'm your guy.
That your specialty, aliens?
Yeah.
O'Brivee, what did you find?
Our patrol has delivered intel that shows
our backup facility
survived the initial attack.
What's the inventory?
Two nukes, 10 Straight Feather missiles
and 325 armed drones.
Okay.
So our objective is to draw as many enemy
into the building, detonate it to blow,
take out as many bad guys as possible.
Back up, man. That's not gonna work.
Just getting there alone,
that's a suicide mission, you understand?
Well, it may not win us the war, but...
I have a better idea.
Tell me, Wellesh.
I mean, as dangerous as they are,
we're wasting our time
on these worker bees.
The worker bees are protecting
the queen, the mothership.
That's what we need to attack.
We have to unload a wars worth of ammo
and resources just to take
one of these things down.
But I believe that the
queen, the mothership,
is vulnerable like any queen
would be without her sentries.
We take down the mothership
and all the rest of them
are gonna scatter
because they'll have no
central base of command.
Our military is decimated.
We're it. We're the last stand.
Well, then let's go big.
Let's use all of that stuff
to attack the mothership.
Do you think we will have the capacity
to launch these missiles remotely?
Everything is down.
There's some manual overrides,
but we need to get to the facility.
At the facility. So where's that at?
It's not far. It's on the base.
I know this facility.
I was stationed there.
Okay. Well, then what we
standing around for? Let's go.
The building may not be far,
but what stands between us and
that building is a world war.
Wellesh, I need you in the game.
You know the access.
Okay.
But I'm going too.
Just like the old man.
Well, if he's in, I'm in. That makes three.
I need every one of my fighters
to be willing to put their lives
on the line, every last one of you.
Understand?
This is no longer about war!
It's about annihilation.
Let's do this.
Just... I need a minute. I need a minute.
How's your leg holding up?
Oh, God, it's not great.
I definitely wouldn't have made
it this far without you, though.
We gotta get you to a hospital.
You're losing a lot of blood.
Patlin, it's okay. It's okay.
What? No, no, we can do this.
No. You've already done so much for me.
I don't deserve this. Thank you.
No! Gwen?
Gwen?
Quick, before they see us!
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, God.
You guys okay? She doesn't look too good.
No, sir. I'm a doctor. She's
really been struggling.
Where you guys from?
Oh, just back east.
This your wife?
My wife? Oh, yeah, my fiancé.
We just barely escaped an attack.
Hop in.
Okay, great.
Let's do it. Thank you.
Let's get moving!
All right, let's go!
Everybody grab a weapon!
Let's go, let's go!
Do you think I'd be going
if there was any other way to do this?
Come on! You gotta understand
where I'm coming from!
Look, I need you to...
I got you, calm down. I got you, I got you.
I understand. Go ahead.
Thank you.
- Hey.
-Hey.
Theses alien blasters are just so bad ass.
I know, right?
You know, your father
would be so proud of you.
I'm gonna kill those alien
bastards that killed him.
I know, but I have another mission for you.
What?
I need you to stay here.
What? That's not fair!
No. I need you to stay here.
Mom, no, no! I wanna fight!
And I want you to live!
Mom, you said a good soldier
follows his commanding orders.
And if not, he's the weakest link.
But alive!
Mom! I don't want to be the weakest link!
No, baby, you are just the opposite!
You are the strongest link!
- But...
-No!
I need you to stay here because
they need me on this mission.
They cannot do it without me.
And the only way, the only way
that I am getting through this
is if I'm fighting for you and your future.
That makes you the strongest link.
We've all gotta fight.
T, ain't that what you told me?
Yeah, it sounds like
something stupid I'd say.
T, you said you wanted to go out and...
I know what I said, man.
Sometimes things change, all right?
Your mom wants us here, we stay here.
Besides, I gotta teach you
some of my signature moves.
You know what I mean?
You're look out for my boy, right?
I think he's gonna watch over me.
And, Lukale, you listen to Tiago
'cause he's wiser than he looks.
I'll just pretend I didn't hear that.
Well...
It's Dad's.
In case you need it.
Okay, everyone! We're moving out.
Hey, hey, hey, Lukale.
I love you, I love you.
I love you too, Mom.
MVP.
Hey. You all right?
Yeah.
She's a strong lady, man. She'll be fine.
I know.
All right, come on, man.
I got some things to show you.
Listen...
Hey. She's lost a lot of blood.
She needs a transfusion and antibiotics
for the infection in her leg.
She's gonna be on our last blood pack.
We've got a universal donor.
And she'll be able to keep leg
if she takes these
antibiotics for the infection.
Gwen, are you okay?
Patlin...
So how are you feeling now?
Hey, hey, she's been through a lot.
Can we do this another time?
Right wrist, Captain.
Hey, it's nothing!
Hey, whoa! Whoa! Hey!
So we've heard reports
that fallen enemy soldiers
appearing to look like our people.
So I am going to ask you one more time.
Who is she and who are you?
- This is crazy!
-Wrong answer!
Stop! Stop! Patlin was just trying to help.
So you're an alien?
No! She's not like them!
She's different! She's...
Just shut your mouth!
You're aiding and abetting the
enemy, punishable by death!
Look, it's not like that, man!
I'm just trying to help!
You need to keep your mouth quiet!
But you...
yeah, you can talk.
You understand me.
You and I are gonna have a
little conversation right now.
Who are your people?
Where did they come from?
How do we stop them?
Please! She just needs some help, man!
You can see her injuries! She needs rest!
Talk!
I said talk!
Our planet is just like
yours and it's dying.
Everything on our planet is dying.
And instead of fixing it,
we looked out into the
universe for our new home.
We built ships and our armies grew.
And we found this planet,
a near replica of our own.
So we set our sights on it.
Colonization!
So you just thought
that you would come here
and take our planet?
Our entire lives, we've been told
that you are the aggressors!
We were told that, to survive,
we had to annihilate you!
Why?
I guess to prepare for this day,
to justify the slaughter.
Our people are sick. They are dying.
And the air here, the
environment, is so pure,
you have no idea how lucky
you are to be on this planet!
And the tripods? Their tubes?
What's their purpose in all of this?
The tripods are harvesting
clean blood from your civilians.
They're exterminating all hostiles.
Dear God.
So you were just gonna keep going
until you wipe us out?
Is that it?
How long does it take
to get from your planet?
How long does it take to
get from your planet!?
We can jump in worm holes
and be here within weeks.
Are there more coming?
We were the first team.
If it's successful, then yes.
What is your planet called?
It's in the Orion Arm of the solar system.
It's called Earth.
Alpha Team, go!
Alpha Team, forward!
Alpha Team, move!
Bet you didn't think you'd be doing this
when you woke up yesterday morning.
Understate much? How far?
Couple blocks. Ready? Move in!
O'Brivee! Over here!
Time to take your sorry
ass back to Planet Hell!
Oh, my God!
A walk in the park, man.
Check it out, all right?
Look.
Cartridge loaded, right?
Loaded, ready to shoot. Got it?
Hey, hey, hey! Where you goin', kid?
My mom's out there.
Hey, come back here, man. Hey!
You wanna see your mom again, man,
you listen to what Tiago's
telling you, all right?
Now come here!
Go! Get to cover. Get to cover.
Give me the gun. Come
on, give it to me, kid.
Shh, shh.
We need that gun.
We need that gun!
I'll get it. Just shoot low, all right?
I got this!
Okay.
No, no, no. We gotta
get the hell outta here!
All right, Luke, I need
you to live, all right?
- But...
-Just shut up!
- You listen to me, all right?
-Yes!
You go, go! Get the hell outta here!
You have to go, now! Now!
T!
Luka, go!
Tiago!
Are those our missiles?
What's left of them.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
Lukale! Luke!
Ashlaya, wait!
What are you doing here?
I gave you orders.
What the hell happened here?
What do you think happened?
This is war. We were attacked.
Where is my son?
I've no idea.
The facility is destroyed, General.
There are no missiles left.
Let's go.
Sir? Sounds like our
allies in the East Quadrant
have been compromised.
We're all alone now.
Has that been confirmed?
Hard to say, sir.
Radio interference is
muddling the frequencies.
Wellesh?
Wellesh.
Listen to me.
Nobody expects you to
be okay, you understand?
But if we're gonna get out of here alive,
I need my best intel right by my side.
You can grieve another time.
Everybody here as lost somebody.
You're not the only one.
I'm sorry, but we need to strategize.
I need you to focus.
Interference.
You said something about
interference? Yeah?
Affirmative. I reckon the hostiles
are causing the interference
with their own...
Internal network likely
powered by the mothership.
Exactly.
Our grid is down, so it has
to have its own power source.
Sir?
What if we could use their network
to run remote commands
for our defense system?
What defense system?
Everything's been wiped out.
O'Brivee, when we were at the facility,
did you see any of the drones?
No, just the missiles.
Okay, me neither.
That means that the drones
must still be protected.
And if they are, they're
probably operational.
I mean, it's a long shot, but if
we could get them turned on...
What are you saying?
That if we cut through their interference,
we can have them
communicate with our drones?
Exactly.
How confident are you that
you can bring our satellites
back online to communicate with our drones?
It's a big if, but if we can
make the connection, sure.
How do we make the connection?
We hack in, disrupt their signal.
And the only way to do that
is with an alien soldier.
Exactly. Worker bee talks to the queen.
Exactly.
Now you're talking.
Show time.
Under the rubble.
Over here! Outside!
Cover us! Go, go, go!
I'm gonna stop them!
What are we looking for?
Any kind of opening.
Looks like someone's
already got the good stuff.
What do you mean?
Gun's gone.
It is?
Seems pretty tight.
I'm not seeing anything.
Me neither.
I got an edge here!
Okay. Let me know when you got it open.
Looks like we've got incoming! Binoculars!
Damn it! I found the back
panel, but I need tools!
Okay, uh...
Even a knife or something!
Try this.
Fancy alien technology, meet your match!
Okay! Tell me when you're in!
Almost there!
Oh, my God.
Here comes the cavalry!
Two minutes!
Go, go, go!
What happened?
Shh! You're okay. You're okay.
Did you save me?
How do you feel? Better.
What happens now?
I don't know.
Hey!
What'd she do...
Shut up!
Solomon, are you with me?
Yeah.
Good! Help me take her to Skuller!
- I'm in!
-Okay, okay.
What are you looking for?
I am looking for any kind of connection.
There we go. Okay.
How do you know if this'll work?
Well, even alien technology
has to obey the laws
of science and physics.
Just have to figure out
which process they are using.
- This one. -How do we know that?
Right now, we're gonna guess
and we're gonna hope that we are right.
Yes!
Okay, it's gonna take a
minute for our satellites
to come back online.
But we're in, okay.
Come on. Come on!
No, no, no! Go, go!
Come on. We're almost there.
Wellesh?
Almost there!
Wellesh, let's go! There's no time!
Come on! Please hurry.
One minute!
Okay! I'm connected to our satellites!
Now all we have to do
is reprogram the drones
to attack the mothership
before they catch me using their network.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Hurry up.
I'm hurrying as fast as I can!
- Hold on!
-We need to go.
I'm almost there. You go. I've gotta stay!
Let's go!
I've gotta stay! I'm almost done!
Wellesh! Move!
Almost there!
Come on.
Hold on, hold on! There!
Ha-ha!
Yes!
We got those bastards.
Ha!
Oh, my God...
- Patlin?
-Sis!
Oh, my God!
General Skuller?
Brennan? Just in time
for the fireworks show.
Wait! What are you doing holding
a gun on him? Let him go!
General, he was harboring one
of them, one of those things!
No! This is my brother!
Brennan, he's cool. Trust me on this, okay?
We'll figure this out later.
Jutta?
Luke?
I'm so sorry.
Brennan? Creature still alive?
This is her.
They can morph into humans?
We're the same.
We are not the same.
When we first discovered your planet,
we were able to determine
that we had the same foundational DNA.
You've been here before?
Yes, recon and intelligence gathering.
That's how we knew that this planet
would be the key to our survival.
And you helped her, Patlin? You helped her?
You tell me right now
why I shouldn't kill you!
Ash, this isn't gonna help anything!
She can help! She can make this...
How the hell is she gonna help?
How is she gonna help?
How could she make anything right?
Do you have any idea what
she has taken from me?
I do.
Ma'am, I murdered in the
name of my own survival.
I killed indiscriminately
and I stand before you
for your judgment to forgive or condemn me.
I'm at your mercy.
Yeah, you are. Yes you are.
General... we have more incoming.
More ships, smaller ones.
Ferry ships?
The mothership is opening up.
No, no! They're not soldiers!
Those are... They're not soldiers!
What are they?
Please, they're refugees!
And the ferry ships, they're...
They're filled with families!
Please! We only came her because
our planet is dying! Please!
They have nothing to do with this war!
Please!
Ash...
Shut up! Shut up!
Mom?
- Oh my God!
-Mom?
- Mom... -Oh, my baby! Oh, my baby!
- You're alive!
-Mom?
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
-Are you okay?
Baby, it's okay.
Mom, I'm fine, really. I'm fine.
Oh!
Give me your phone.
My husband was Corporal Jutta Wellesh
and he was a good man.
You and your people killed him.
Look at it!
Just wanted to let you know that I love you
and that I'm always thinking
about you and your mom.
And that's what I do.
I don't just fight for our family,
but for all families.
And that's why it's so important
for you to fight every day.
Fight for those who
can't protect themselves,
who can't defend themselves.
I'm getting all mushy, man.
I love you, my man.
See you soon, all right? Be good.
Do you have a family?
Yes, yes.
I have two kids, they're five and three.
They're on that ship.
Please.
Please, please...
General, call off the strike!
Not your call, Wellesh.
But they're innocents!
Nobody's innocent in war.
You gotta pick a side.
Whose side are you on, Wellesh?
I'm on the side that...
doesn't pick death, okay?
I'm on the side that wants to figure out
how we can help each
other get through this.
I am on the side that is
gonna give my son a future!
And if you don't understand
that, what side are you on?
Prepare to engage, General.
Fire on my command.
Look! Look! Look! She's telling the truth!
They're refugees!
They're just... they're families!
They are families!
Fire.
I said fire already!
Don't do it. Don't!
Fire and that's an order!
Now!
I said fire.
How dare you?
Brennan?
I'm sorry, General.
You are all traitors, every one of you!
The blood of this planet...
it's on all your hands, all of you.
Mom...
Baby, I'm so proud of you.
Your dad would be so proud of you, baby.
Thank you.
I was wondering what was
happening with my sister.
It's been hell. I'm sorry.
No, no. I get it.
Baby.
Hey, come here.
Uh, by the way, this is Gwen.
She's not from around here.
What now?
Let's go meet our new neighbors.
Let's welcome them peacefully.
Let's try trust this time.
We have incoming.
I'll put them up on the screen.
Are these our ships returning home?
I don't think so.
Then who is it?
Let's see how they
handle their own weapons.
Prepare to fire at my command.
This war's only just begun.
Fire!