Shane!
Son of a bitch.
Where is he?
Relax.
Bet that's him.
Late on his first day.
The balls on this fuckin' guy.
Hi, there.
Special Agent Justin Rosa.
Here for wire room duty.
Got an ID, Special Agent?
Yes, I do.
Let's take a look at that.
Well, you're definitely not new.
How can you tell?
Your photo.
I'm guessing that's what,
20 years ago?
Good eye, 18.
But thanks for noticing.
Well, I can tell there's
a good story here,
but, uh, considering you're about
ten minutes late for your shift,
guess you'll have to fill me in
some other time.
- Yeah. Will do, will do.
- Know where you're goin'?
- Fourth floor, right?
- Got it.
Friday night's slow around here.
Let us know
if you need something.
- I will. Thank you.
- All right.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I couldn't find any...
I didn't ask.
Shut the door.
That's rule number one.
Okay. Okay.
Hi, there.
I'm Agent Justin Rosa.
How you doin'?
Don't talk to her.
She's busy.
You must be Special Agent
Mueller. I'm your new transfer.
It's Senior Special Agent.
I know who you are,
and I know what you are.
Eh, look, I'm sorry I'm late.
I don't have access
to the garage yet.
I had to park
like six blocks away.
Who knew downtown
could get so busy on a Friday?
Yeah, no shit.
No excuses.
You're not allowed.
Understood.
Yeah, you look a
little old... for a rookie.
Yeah. I started out
in Secret Service.
But to be honest with you,
it was a little boring.
I wanted a little more action,
so I figured I'd try this.
Action? Yeah,
there is no action.
Well, I've never been
in a wire room before,
but if this is
what one looks like,
then, uh, you guys must have
a pretty good case. Huh?
It's a shit case.
- You know what a wire room is?
- Yeah, yeah.
You want
the textbook definition?
- Sure.
- Yeah, a wire is a lawful interception
of telephonic and internet
based conversations
of subjects
under criminal investigation.
You memorized this whole thing?
Yeah, I did, yeah.
From that little pamphlet.
Your knowledge doesn't matter.
You want to know why?
Uh, let me guess,
one of your rules?
Nope.
Why doesn't matter?
Tell him.
Because you are nothing more
than a warm body here
to make sure the place
doesn't burn down.
Exactly.
Don't fuck anything up.
What, so that's it?
You're not gonna
brief me on the case?
It's a gun-smuggling case
with the cartel.
- Which one?
- Does that matter?
Well, yeah, 'cause if we're
talking about the Baja cartel,
they control all the smuggling
routes in and out of California.
So if that's the one you're
talking about, then we're good.
Yeah, well, maybe
you're not a complete idiot.
The Baja cartel.
This is our guy.
That's Eddie Flynn.
That's Eddie Flynn, huh?
That's him.
- Huh, this guy right here?
- Yep.
So this is what a shit
case looks like, huh?
If you ask me,
it looks like someone put a lot
of hard work and money into this.
And that is just unbelievable.
That's your entertainment.
She's the expert.
I'm the expert on all of it.
So, these screens are
tied into two sets of CCTVs...
One for the federal building and
these are from Eddie's compound.
We have most of the inside
and all of the outside monitored.
So he can't take a shit
without us knowing the color.
It's brown.
Each camera is recorded
to a hard drive,
that way you can rewind, pause.
You ever see anything
good on there?
Nope.
Just like the wire.
Nada.
Who knows?
Yeah, maybe you'll get lucky.
Yeah, get some actual activity.
However, we never turn the
channels off of Eddie's CCTVs.
They are triggered
by facial recognition tech.
Impressive.
Don't get too excited.
It's worthless.
And that's about it for the TVs.
Now, if you don't mind, I'd really
like to get back to my actual job.
Can I go, or do you have
more questions for me?
Um, what if I want to leave? If I
gotta, you know, go pee or something?
You don't.
That's rule number two.
Well, what are the other rules?
You're a real
special agent now, huh?
Yeah, you'll figure it out.
Uh, the rest
are in the blue binder.
- Okay. All right.
- Read 'em.
Nour Holborow, the analyst
assigned to the case.
Hi, Nour.
Well, that went well, huh?
Don't let him get to you.
He's three months
from retirement.
He's not always that friendly?
Shane? He used to be one
of the coolest agents around.
- Oh, yeah?
- Fun-loving, laid back, charming.
One of the best.
Fucking rock star.
What happened?
Well, it started
as a swan song, you know.
One last case
to hang his hat on,
but didn't quite
turn out that way.
And now he's just trying to
make it these last few months,
so he can collect his
pension, call it a career.
So is this case that bad?
I mean, it had legs early on.
Shane had a CI
in the organization
who was feeding us great intel,
but he went dark
several months ago.
Is that normal?
Mm, there's nothing normal
about CIs.
Anyhoo, Eddie Flynn
is an infamous
Irish arms dealer.
Smuggled Russian-made weapons
into shipments bound
for the South American rebels.
Ended up on the run
after a bloody gang war.
Made his way to the US.
And now is biding his time as
a middleman for the Baja cartel.
- Ah.
- Still using his arms and dope connections to survive.
And that is his number two,
who we've yet to identify
other than a nickname of Junior.
Junior.
We tracked
a few of their shipments,
but once the CI disappeared
so did the guns,
and it's been quiet
here ever since.
Nothing but a bunch
of coded talk
and calls to numbers that drop
the moment they hang up.
Eleven wasted months.
All right, let me show you how
everything works so I can get out of here.
So, program is always on.
And you'll know someone is
either making or receiving a call
- when you hear three beeps...
- Yeah. Three beeps.
...and a dial tone.
Once the call connects,
it will play in real time.
And here is the audio waveform
visualizer, or AWV.
It's basically a computer-generated
image of the audio recording.
Okay.
But for today, you won't need
to worry about any of that.
Eddie doesn't make calls
before midnight.
A criminal with a
schedule. I like it.
Ah. And if a call
does come in,
the program automatically
records and stores it
for review
and evidentiary purposes.
So nothing to do but count
the minutes until shift change.
Completely agent-proof.
All right.
Speaking of shift change...
- Think you got it?
- Yeah, it's completely agent-proof.
What could go wrong?
Good luck, Special Agent Rosa.
Thank you, Nour.
- Good night.
- Have a good night.
Senior Special Agent
Shane Mueller.
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
All right.
Let's look at those
fucking rules, huh?
Keep the door closed.
Don't leave the room unattended.
No one other than HSI
personnel are allowed in.
Don't destroy wire room.
Never contact the target.
Keep the target alive.
Don't fuck anything up.
If you have any issues,
questions or emergency,
the only number
you should call is Shane."
All right.
Let's get into it.
Oh!
Hey, it's me.
Yeah. Can you get me
the same again?
The chicken dumpling.
And the special sauce.
Don't be late.
Eh, call before midnight.
All right.
Here.
Can't be good
if you're calling this late, boss.
We had to terminate
one of the babysitters.
How quickly can you
find me another one?
- The White girl?
- Nah, the Chinese girl.
- How quickly do you need one?
- Quickly.
Talk to Marsh,
he'll fill you in on it.
Why are you dressed like that?
What's that, boss?
Not you, hold on.
What, we don't look sexy enough?
- Where do you think you're even going dressed like that?
- Out. And you're taking us.
Oh, no.
No chance, darling.
Please? Just today.
I won't ask again.
Right.
Until the next time.
You need to take better care
of my girl.
You already know me answer.
- Such a prick.
- Paranoid prick.
I'm getting really tired
of having to explain myself
every fucking time
you talk back.
Nor do I appreciate being
called prick in me own home.
Well, then don't act like one.
You always do this. All because
you think someone wants to kill you.
You're not that important.
Seriously.
You know what I do.
And who I am.
This is the only place I'm safe.
So take your sweet little asses
back upstairs,
put your pajamas on,
we're staying in.
I'm not.
- You want me to call back?
- Did I say I wanted you to?
'Cause if I did, I'd
say so. Hold the line.
Upstairs.
- Upstairs!
- Fuck that!
Cindy...
do I need to raise
my voice again?
Go change.
Go upstairs.
You know, you're right.
Someone does want to kill you.
It's me!
I'll add you to the damn
list, you fucking floozy!
Call Ma.
Find me a babysitter.
What's the story?
This guy's life's
a fucking soap opera.
All right. Uh-huh.
Right. Okay.
Okay, yeah.
What do I pay you for?
Fucking useless.
Hey.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Shit.
Didn't mean to scare
the piss outta you.
Just doing my rounds.
- Officer...
- Axum.
Call me Mike.
- Hey, Mike. How you doin'?
- Good. Pleasure.
Yeah, pleasure's mine.
You know, how is it you've
been around here for 18 years,
but I've never seen you before?
Well, there's not much
to tell, really.
You know, I started out
with Secret Service
and... yeah, I just thought
I'd mix it up a little bit.
Yeah, no, I get that.
I was a deputy with the
sheriff's department for 20 years.
- No shit.
- Yeah.
Yeah, just retired
a few months ago.
- Hey, congrats.
- Thank you.
Took this gig here
purely out of boredom.
What, this isn't boring?
Well, to be perfectly honest,
keeps me out of the house
a little bit
between the wife and the boys.
Yeah.
How about you?
You married, kids?
No. Divorced.
No kids.
Eh, you know this line of work.
It ain't easy.
No, no, it's not.
What kind of case
you guys working on in here?
It's nothing too exciting.
Guns, drugs, as far as I know.
I'm the new guy.
- Same old shit, huh?
- Yeah.
Well, looks like you're busy.
Let me let you get back to work.
- All right, Mike.
- I'm gonna take care of my rounds.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Hey, Mike, uh...
- Yeah.
Hang on one second.
What is it?
Where's the bathrooms
around here?
Can you show me where they are?
Yeah, let me show you.
Gets a little confusing.
Prostate's gigantic nowadays.
- Holy shit.
- I should a wore my Depends.
I didn't know I was gonna be
stuck in an office all day.
Come on, man,
I'll take you there.
Thanks, man.
I don't know why
you put up with him.
I can do better, I know.
Let me guess... he loves you.
Does he say that when
he's drunk or sober?
That's what I thought.
No! No!
Junior, come on.
One time I need you.
You useless Yank.
Where are you?
At the tone,
please record your message.
Come down here, Junior.
Someone's come for me,
where are you?
Fuck!
Come down here, Junior.
Someone's come for me.
Where are you?
Fuck!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Cin, is that you?
- I don't wanna die.
Tell me where you are.
They have me
downstairs on the couch.
Okay, okay, okay. Listen...
They're here for me, not you.
You do whatever they say,
and I'm gonna come find you.
I promise,
it's gonna be all right.
They're gonna kill me,
I know it. Please...
Cindy! Cindy!
Fuck!
Fuck. You fuckers.
What the fuck?
- Hello.
- Shane, it's Justin.
- Who?
- Justin. Justin Rosa.
- From the wire room.
- Oh, shit.
- What do you want?
- Hey, look, Eddie already made some phone calls.
- And there's...
- Who did he call?
Well, the first one
I don't know.
Some guy about firing
the babysitter
and hiring some Chinese girl.
Those are code words for drugs.
Fentanyl, stash house.
The other two calls
went to Junior,
but they went
right to voice mail.
Did he leave messages?
Yeah, he said get some guys
and come to the house.
Did you read the folder?
The ones the binder?
Yeah, yeah, I read the rules.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, they're pretty much self-explanatory.
Obviously not.
You damn broke the last one.
Fucked up my day.
Hey, there's a bunch of guys
over there right now.
There's some kind of a seat...
Hello?
Fucking prick.
- Looks like one of those days, huh, Shane?
- Yeah.
You need to train
hose recruits better.
Tell me about it.
- Well, next round of drinks is on me.
- If you can afford it.
Hefeweizen, not any
of the American slop.
Deal.
All right.
Okay. All right,
think, Justin, think.
- Hello?
- Special Agent Rosa, this is Nour.
Oh, Nour, thank God.
Hey, look, there's...
I think I forgot my PIF
there in the room.
Could you check around for it?
Okay, uh...
what's a PIF?
It's our access card for the
building, parking, the wire room.
And if we lose them...
Okay. Yeah, yeah,
I got your PIF.
Hey, look, Eddie already
made a bunch of calls.
- Who did he call?
- Look, that's not important right now.
There's a bunch of guys
in there,
and they got his wife,
or his girlfriend
or wherever she is,
and they're looking
for him right now.
I mean, these guys are like military
or they're SWAT or something.
It's hard to tell.
Shit, Rosa, why didn't you
lead with that?
Give me a sec, I can log in
remotely from my laptop.
If they are SWAT,
I'm gonna be pissed.
I cleared that address.
If any other law enforcement
agency runs it,
I should have been
notified immediately.
Unless they didn't clear it,
and in that case,
I bet it's the DEA,
because those assholes
never clear shit.
Okay, I'm logged in.
Let me zoom in.
They don't look like
law enforcement.
Have you notified Shane?
Well, I tried to.
I called him, but he hung up on
me before I could explain. Dick.
All right, I'm on my way
back to the wire room.
Call Shane back, let him know
what's going on.
Hey, Nour.
Just real quick, uh...
Shane's rules, that one about
keeping the target alive?
What's that about?
It's driving me crazy.
Remember that CI
I mentioned earlier?
He told Shane that Eddie has a list
of dirty cops who work for the cartel.
They export loads, run checks
on databases, stuff like that.
Eddie keeps it as his
get out of jail free card.
And Shane hopes
if he can arrest him,
he can be used to go out on top.
You know, take down the
shit bag and the dirty cops.
The problem is,
the list is in Eddie's head.
Okay, so Shane needs him alive.
Exactly.
Well, how the hell do we
keep him alive from in here?
We can't. Call Shane.
Shit. All right.
It's Shane, you know what to do.
Hey, it's Justin. I just
wanted to let you know
that there is a group
of armed men at Eddie's house.
I just spoke to Nour,
and she's on her way back in,
and she thought you
might want to do the same.
Uh...
That's it. Okay. Bye.
Fuck you!
Tell your fucking friends.
He just killed him.
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice message system.
999-555-2183 is not available.
At the tone,
please record your message.
When you're finished recording,
you may hang up or press one
for more options.
Goddamn it, Junior, someone's
come for me. Where are you?
Shit! It's my fucking men.
It's my men coming after me.
If I find out he sent them,
I'll chop him up
into dog treats.
Come on, Eddie. Come on.
Turn around, you dumb fuck.
Fuck...
Fuck it.
Answer it, goddamn it.
Answer it.
About time you called back.
Hello, you there?
There's one right outside your
door. He's coming your way.
Quit playing,
I don't time for this.
Hey, listen to me, asshole!
He's coming from your left!
- There's no one there, you lyin' piece...
- Your other left!
Okay.
Let's talk.
Who the fuck are you?
You still there?
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my...
Sheriff's
office. Is this an emergency?
Yes, it is, uh...
I need to speak
to the on-duty supervisor.
May I ask who's calling?
Special Agent Justin Rosa
of Homeland Security.
Hold, please.
This is Sergeant Roberts.
Yes, look, uh...
This is gonna sound
little strange,
but we're on a T-3 right now,
and the target of our
investigation is under attack.
Under attack?
What do you mean?
Well, some men
broke into his house,
and it's-it's a complete
war zone out there.
Okay, and what would you
like for me to do about that?
- Well, if you could send the cavalry.
- Right.
And may I ask, how come you
guys aren't doing that right now?
Well, that's my next call, but if you
could please just send a unit out there.
- What's the address?
- It's, uh...
903 Lake Point.
That's I as in Lima,
A as in alpha...
Nine-0-3 Lake Point.
Got it.
All right,
I'll send some guys up.
Thanks. Hey, um,
any chance you can give me
a follow up call?
Well, if you're on a wire,
- wouldn't you find that out?
- Maybe, maybe.
You're new, aren't you?
- Yeah, is it that obvious?
- Yes.
But I know a few of the HSI guys
and your name
didn't ring a bell, so...
Yeah, it's my first day.
Wow. Wire room duty
on your first day?
Lucky me.
Well, I look forward to seeing
you face-to-face at some point.
Same here, Sergeant.
Thank you.
Shit.
You've reached Homeland Security
Investigation Special Agent Justin Rosa.
Please leave a message.
Special Agent.
Aren't I lucky?
Well, Mr. Rosa,
I don't know why you called me,
but your number
is now in my cell.
And I can hide
from these goons easy.
But if I die tonight,
someone is gonna wonder
why a Special Agent from
Homeland Security be callin' me.
And that's not gonna look
good on your resume, is it?
So we need to chat,
sooner the better.
Call me.
You are one annoying fuck,
you know that?
I know. Uh, look,
did you get my message
about the people at Eddie's?
People?
- What people?
- I don't know who they are, but, uh,
I-I called Nour,
and she's on her way back in.
- She is?
- Yeah. Uh, look...
Eddie got into a fight
with a guy and he killed him.
- Eddie's dead?
- No, no, Eddie...
Eddie killed the guy.
He blew his brains out.
- What the fuck?
- But don't worry.
- Don't worry. I got it under control.
- How?
- I talked to the sheriff's department...
- Why would you do that?
Christ. Dirty cops
are everywhere.
Don't worry,
I talked to the supervisor
- and he sent a unit out there.
- Don't you call anyone else.
- You hear me? No one.
- Yeah, um...
About that,
- I, uh...
- You called him, didn't you?
- You called Eddie.
- Hey, your fucking rule
said to keep him alive.
What was I supposed to do?
I was wrong.
You are an idiot.
A complete idiot.
I did what I thought
was right for the case.
- I couldn't just let him die, right?
- You listen to me.
You plant your ass on the couch.
Don't you dare move.
Not till I get there.
You got that?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- This can't get any worse.
- Uh...
Jesus fucking Christ.
You're gonna tell me how,
aren't you?
Well, when I called Eddie,
I used my cell phone,
so now he's got my number,
and he has since called me back.
Of course he has.
- Did you answer?
- No, no, I didn't answer.
Call the sheriff's office.
You tell him you're wrong.
- Okay.
- Make something up.
Hey, Special Agent Rosa.
It's Mike.
Oh, hey, Mike.
- This fuckin'...
- Just checking in on you, man.
- Doin' okay up here?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just trying to keep the place
from burning down. You know?
- Not much else you can do on wire room duty, huh?
- Yeah.
Especially considering
you're not the, uh, case agent.
These guys, they get pretty
territorial about that kind of...
Mike, I hate to be rude, but, uh, I
got a really important phone call...
Yeah. No,
my-my apologies.
I've been known
to drone on and on.
Wife and kids always get
on me about it, you know.
Hey, look, maybe could
shoot the shit later, okay?
- I gotta...
- Hey, deal.
- All right, bye. All right.
- Listen, man,
if you need any help or
anything like that, I'm here.
- I'm good. Thank you, Mike, I appreciate it.
- Good? All right.
- Sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, good.
- Hello?
- Special Agent Rosa.
Yeah, hey, Sergeant Roberts,
I was just about to call you.
Uh, apparently,
I made a mistake.
There is no attack
on our target.
Well, actually, that's why
I was giving you a call.
Your target...
that's Eddie Flynn, right?
Yeah. How'd you know that?
Well, the address
seemed familiar.
So we ran it
through our database here
and come to find out
a few of our detectives
are investigating him also.
Well, if you could have
your men stand down for now,
I'd-I'd appreciate that.
Well, knowing my guys,
they'll probably do a
welfare check regardless.
Actually, seems like they're
on the scene right now.
Hey, uh, hold on for a second.
Let me put you on hold.
Yeah, no problem.
We got this covered.
Hey, it's good to
see you, man. How you doing?
Special Agent Rosa?
You there?
Yeah, yeah, I'm still here.
All right, well, I'm glad
my guys cleared the scene.
Everything's code four.
They did a standard
routine check around the house.
No one's home.
So, looks like you were right.
Nothing's going on.
All right, well,
I appreciate it, Sergeant.
Hey, anytime.
And if you need anything else,
you just give me a call.
Will do.
You've reached Homeland Security
Investigation Special Agent Justin Rosa.
Please leave a message.
Special Agent Rosa?
We both know these gobshites
aren't leaving 'til I'm dead.
Which may not be much longer.
It's gonna be very bad for you
when someone finds
your number in my call log.
Basically, your career's fucked.
So pick up.
How many of you fuckers are cops?
Mr. Rosa.
You gotta stop calling me.
Why would I do that?
You saved my life.
Plus, I really wanna know
why a Fed called to warn me.
And more importantly,
how you knew.
Are you watching me?
Are you one of these gobshites
out here trying to kill me?
- No. Those were sheriffs.
- Sheriffs?
Was it Roberts?
How the fuck
do you know Roberts?!
I don't, I sent a unit out there
because I thought I saw...
Saw? Are there fuckin'
cameras here? Huh?
Have you got a spy
satellite over my base?
Can you see this, can ya?
Huh?
Fuckin' have some!
Or maybe you're watching me
through my phone.
Is that it?
You listenin' to me?
If you are, you're wasting
your fucking time.
I don't use my phone
for anything business-related.
Nobody's listening to you.
Nobody's watching you.
You're not
that fucking important.
Clearly I am.
Otherwise, why'd you
call and warn me?
I told you, it was a mistake.
Doesn't change the fact
that you did.
And I have no idea how you
knew, but I will figure it out.
You're fucking crazy.
You know that?
Yeah? Let's see how
fuckin' crazy I really am!
Sheriff's office.
Is this an emergency?
Peter Roberts, please.
May I ask who's calling?
- No.
- Is this an emergency, sir?
It isn't yet, but the clock's
ticking, darling.
- Put me through.
- Hold, please.
- Roberts.
- You piece of shit.
Eddie?
Surprised I'm still
alive, are we?
What? No.
You're not calling me
from your cell, are you?
- No.
- Good. That's good.
Okay, so why are you
calling me at work?
I've called you around
a dozen times tonight,
but you never answered.
I don't answer that cell
at work. You know that.
No, you don't answer
when someone else calls,
but if it's me,
you fucking answer.
Look, I can't talk
right now, okay?
I'm not alone.
Funny, neither am I.
Get alone. I'll wait.
So, what's so urgent
that you couldn't wait
until after I got off work?
Let's start with the army
of men you sent to kill me.
Army of men? I have no idea
what you're talking about, man.
Don't, Junior.
Junior.
I know it was you who
orchestrated all of this.
What I want to know is why.
Why?
Why, why, why?
Because you put
our organization at risk.
That's why.
Allowed a snitch to
infiltrate your little enclave.
Do you know how much intel
he probably got?
None of it important.
You don't know that.
I had to deal with it, not you.
Now I have to clean up
the other messes.
One of which is you.
And you'll be dead by morning.
Is this little plan of yours
approved down south?
Didn't think so.
And if you think I'm
a problem... just wait.
You're out of your league.
Or do I have to remind you
the last time you got kicked
out of town, like a little rat?
You lost your empire,
tucked tail
and ran like a little bitch.
Now you're just
a paranoid lackey.
A middleman.
A reject.
I'm the king.
I'll own this town.
You don't got shit on me.
Without me, this entire ship
goes down like the Titanic.
You hear me?
I'll cook you
like the chickenshit you are,
you fuckin' weasel!
I could see it in your eyes all
along you were gonna fuck me!
You think your bitch boys
can succeed in their mission?
- Huh?
- Oh, absolutely. Without a doubt.
Is that a promise, sweetheart?
Then please tell me
why two of them are dead,
and I'm still breathing!
Oh, and Sergeant Roberts...
I am using my cell, which is
being monitored by the Feds!
But I think you already
knew that, didn't you?
Shit. Peggy!
Let's fucking go.
How's that for crazy,
Special Agent Rosa?
You have my number.
We have a lot to discuss.
Thanks for confirming
you're listening to my calls.
And that probably means
there are cameras in here.
Which would explain
how you saw something.
There's nothing there.
You're just being paranoid.
Is that right?
We'll see about that, won't we?
Come on.
Come to Eddie. Yeah.
You crafty little bastard.
Fuckin'...
How many more
of these are there? Eh?
You really want to know?
I hope you've enjoyed
everything you've seen so far,
because mostly like
your wire room,
these are nothing
but a waste of your time.
I'm hanging up. Erase my
number, forget we ever spoke.
And what's that gonna fix?
If it's your job you're
worried about, don't.
I gave you Junior.
He's a high-ranking, well-respected
member of law enforcement.
Probably be awarded
some sort of medal.
But we'll have to survive
the night first.
So, are you ready
to go to war, Mr. Rosa?
What does that mean?
If I know Junior, which I do,
he'll be coming after you
and your evidence.
Yeah, he's really gonna
attack a federal building?
It's too risky, and for all he
knows, we have nothing on him.
No, for all he knows,
you have everything.
Which threatens that perfect
little life of his.
So he'll be coming after you.
He'll be coming fuckin' hard.
Yeah, well,
he can't get up here.
Too well protected.
Who're you trying to convince?
We got guards here,
armed guards.
Six, right?
They're Junior's guys.
The only difference
between you and me,
is they don't know where I am.
No.
These are our guys.
After everything today,
are you still that naive?
What the fu...
Mikey, what the hell?
Fuck, man, I told you
to get out of here.
What's going on?
Well...
looks like there's been
a, uh, small...
change in plans.
What the fuck?!
Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, guys, easy.
Weapon discharged, it's okay.
It's okay,
it's all under control.
Relax. Relax, relax, guys.
Got it all under control.
I'll let you know if I hear
anything else. All right?
You guys have a good night.
I'll see you in a little bit.
It's Shane.
You know what to do.
Shit.
- Yeah?
- One of the SUVs just left.
Guessing they're coming for you.
Looks like
we're both up shit's creek.
Yeah, that's
really helpful. Thanks.
Now don't lose hope, Agent Rosa.
You know the playbook.
Right now they're gonna try
and use my girl as insurance.
Let's see how far they get.
It's time for me to bring
out my fucking toys.
Aye. We're gonna
have some fun.
I like playing.
Do you?
Are you ready?
It's fucking time.
Focus on what's coming your way.
I can handle
the rest of them here.
Oh, yeah?
Like you handled that guy
that snuck up on you earlier?
Why do you care
if I live or die?
I took an oath
to protect and serve.
I know that might sound
corny to you.
But that's something
I believe in.
Touching. Truly.
All right, we're gonna
focus on you first.
I'll deal with my shit
as it comes.
And just how do you plan on keeping
me alive from wherever you are?
All right,
I'm gonna be your eyes.
You just need to trust me
and listen to me.
You think you could do that?
You're not a good listener.
Any other option?
Not if you want to get out
of here in one piece.
Such a fuckin' cliché fact,
you know that?
Okay, let's begin.
All right.
What have we here?
Okay.
You got three of them
by the garage.
But you can't just go
in there with your AK,
it's too loud.
I think I got
something for that.
Wow, Eddie!
You do know that's an
illegal firearm, don't you?
Well, I don't always
play by the rules.
I'm ready.
Okay, he's heading your way.
Hide, hide, get down, go!
All right, just stay there.
He's coming around.
Just stay there.
He's coming around
the front of the truck.
On my mark... Now.
What was that?
That's one down.
Nice shot, Eddie.
Okay, you got a couple
headed your way.
Okay.
All right, all right.
Stay there. Stay right there.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Stay there.
Good, they're moving around
the front of the truck.
All right, on my mark.
Now.
Very nice.
Very nice, Eddie.
That makes three.
All clear.
Hello... Junior.
How about we handle this
diplomatically?
Shall we?
And how do you
propose we do this?
You simply delete
any evidence you have on me.
- Mm. And what's in it for me?
- I'll let you live.
Well, that's very nice
of you, Junior.
What more could you want?
Nothing...
from a piece of shit,
dirty cop like you.
You know, you're very
brave for a man who's all alone.
Oh, I'm not alone.
- There are other agents in here.
- Ah, come on.
Now, you and I both know
that's not true.
- Yeah.
- But my guys are.
So what, are you gonna send
your rent-a-cops in here
to attack a secure wire room?
You mean a wire room
that my rent-a-cops
have the keys to?
No, no, no.
Cindy, is that you?
She can't come to
the phone right now.
Fuck you, cunt.
Let her go.
You're here for me.
Please, help me!
Baby, baby...
This is taking
too much time as it is.
So you know how this goes.
Come out, she lives.
You don't, she dies.
You won't do nothing.
You have five seconds.
I've taken proper shits
that bother me more than you.
Five...
Four...
- Three...
- Okay, fuck!
I'm in the garage.
Eddie, I'm sorry for earlier.
It's okay. I'm gonna
come find you. Okay?
I'm gonna come fuckin'
find you. I've got ya.
- Don't you worry.
- No, no, no...
Holy fuck.
Cindy!
Fuck it!
You motherfucking fucking cunt!
You're fucking dead when I get
my hands on you, you hear me?
You're fucking dead!
You fucking hear me?!
Fucking dead!
I'll fuckin' get ya!
They killed her!
They fucking killed her!
Yeah, I know. I know, Eddie.
You gotta stay focused,
all right?
There's some guys come...
Oh, shit.
All right, all right,
change of plans.
I need you to hide, All right?
Can you do that?
I'm gonna gut
these fuckers like fish.
Hey, the pool house.
There's a basement.
- Get to the pool house basement.
- That's your plan?
Hide in a fucking basement,
like a rat?
For now. Go! Go!
Justin, there's been a breach.
I gotta get you to a safe
location now. Let's go.
Yeah, I can't do that, Mike.
I saw what you did downstairs.
Ah, Justin, goddamn it.
See, now that's...
that's really unfortunate,
because, you know,
I wasn't gonna kill you.
I really liked you, man.
But now?
Come on, Justin,
put the gun down.
I promise to make it quick
and painless.
Scout's honor.
Hey, Boy Scout.
Goddamn it, Mike!
Why'd you make me do that?
You have no idea what's coming.
Junior...
he ain't gonna stop
until you're dead.
Burn the whole world down
to get what you got in here.
Where are the others?
You know the answer to that.
And that...
That ain't gonna hold 'em off.
It held you off.
You got lucky.
But you ain't gonna
get lucky four more times.
Yeah, maybe not.
But help is coming.
Sorry I won't be around...
to see who gets here first.
- Fuck!
- Where are you?
We got him.
Man down.
I repeat, man down.
- Do not fire.
- No!
No.
Fuck!
Okay.
What the...?
- Hey.
- You still there, Fed?
Yeah, I'm still here.
I thought you were dead.
Ah, you care about me, do ya?
Let's not get crazy.
How are things your end?
I'm good... for now.
Good. We're making progress.
We're a team.
Look at that.
Hold on.
What's the status?
Well, his status ain't so good.
Ah, Special Agent Rosa.
Impressive.
Yeah, just a little warm up
while I wait for you.
I looked you up, Agent.
From Secret Service duty
to just a lower wire room grunt.
Ironic, going
from protecting senators
to trying to keep
that scum Eddie alive.
Yeah, well, a job's a job.
Well, Agent, looks like
you failed at your duties again.
You know, it seems to be
a pattern for you.
Disappointment
follows you around.
Oh...
My apologies.
I hate to be
the bearer of bad news.
Your target's dead.
Seems like the coward
was hiding in the basement.
Why do they always
hide in the basement?
Seems like your case is closed.
Oh, no, our case
is just ramping up.
We got a new target.
You.
I'm not too concerned.
You should be.
Okay. You there?
You at the house yet?
You're one ballsy
son of a bitch, you know that?
Yeah, I know, I've been told.
He's gonna destroy you.
Yeah, he's definitely gonna try.
You need to know when
to stop, when to give up.
Now is that time.
Your sacrificing your job
and your life. For what?
A worthless investigation?
You don't know what we have.
I know that if you had
something, I'd be in cuffs by now.
There's more to it.
Like you're trying to be a hero,
trying to prove something.
Was Daddy a cop?
Was that it?
Are you trying
to make him proud?
Oh, fuck off.
Or maybe you're just
trying to right a wrong,
seeking a little redemption.
We've all been there.
You don't know me, asshole.
Oh, but I think I do,
Special Agent Rosa.
How is it a smart guy like you
ends up in a shitty wire room?
What did you fuck up so badly
that you'd need to fix
by rescuing me?
Hey, you'd be dead
if it wasn't for me.
Don't try and get in my head.
There's no room for you in here.
Apologies.
But there must be some reason
why you risked everything.
What is it the Feds
want so badly,
they're willing to risk an entire
investigation to get it, huh?
What is it that I have
that everyone is...
The list!
The fucking list.
It doesn't exist.
Sorry.
You risked everything
for a rumor.
Oh, no, it's much bigger
than that now.
List or no list...
I'm gonna see this thing
through to the end.
And how does this end,
Special Agent Rosa?
- I haven't thought it through yet.
- But I have.
You're gonna help me
get out of here alive.
And then I'm gonna pull
a Keyser Soze,
ride into the sunset.
Poof! I'm fucking gone.
If you do,
I'll be coming for you.
Yeah? Will ya?
You promise?
Oh, yeah. I promise.
Goddamn it.
I'm beginning to love
that hoo-rah attitude.
Right, let's get
our fucking skates on.
All right, let's do it.
All right.
There are three downstairs
in the main structure.
One heading to the basement now.
Get out of sight.
Okay, hold right there.
Wait. Wait.
Okay, now.
Fuck you.
There's another one
coming. Move.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Steady. Don't move.
Don't fucking move.
Now. Go.
All right, Eddie.
Nice. Very nice.
You got some skills.
The rest are all upstairs.
At the top of the stairs
go left,
get the one in the bathroom.
Be quiet, right there.
All right, all right.
All right, there's two more
in the front entrance.
It's, uh... it's also
where they killed Cindy.
So prepare yourself.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You fuckin' stay right there.
Keep your fuckin' hands
down, missy.
Did you really think
I was gonna let her live?
Do you really think
I'm gonna let you?
Fuck.
I'm fuckin' sorry, baby.
I'm fuckin' sorry.
Feel better?
Spiritually
fuckin' enlightened, yeah.
That's it for downstairs, right?
All right,
the rest are upstairs.
Okay.
Why're you stopping?
What are you waiting for?
How many, and where?
Two in the hallway,
one in the master bedroom.
I truly appreciate
your help, Fed.
This is where
I bid you farewell.
No, you mother...
fucker... What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
What the hell?
It's time for me
to saddle up my horse.
See you on the other side, Rosa.
God...
Do not engage.
Hold in the stairwell.
Reinforcements en route.
Hold on.
I'm almost there.
Hey, hey, you got any guns here?
Why the fuck do you need guns?
Do you have any guns?
Yes or no?
There's a safe in the office.
Fuck.
What the hell have you done?
Don't point that at me.
Open the safe.
Jesus Christ.
Come on. I'm not
playing games.
- Open it.
- I'm not playing either.
- Come on.
- All right.
Just calm down, all right?
I am calm, open it.
Mm-hmm... 72...
Jesus Christ.
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you fuckin' with me, Shane?
Open it!
Back up.
Bingo.
You wanna tell me
what's going on?
Fuck if I know.
You called me.
- Are you one of them?
- Why do you think that?
Well, after you
ran out of here earlier,
then I see you down there
having a smoke with Mike,
the security guard who tried to
fucking kill me.
You think I'm corrupt?
After the day I had today.
The day that you
brought on yourself.
- I ought a...
- I'm not with him.
I was meeting my buddy.
Yet you decided to go
have a smoke. Huh?
Waiting for a cab.
- You didn't drive your car to work?
- I was going drinking.
Okay. Okay.
You're still dumb as a rock.
All right, I'm sorry, all right?
I fucked up, all right?
It's been a little crazy
around here.
If you're done, explain this.
Why are the guards
trying to kill you?
- They're with Junior.
- Junior?
How the fuck do you know that?
Yeah, I'll explain it to you.
But there's more comin',
all right?
More?
What have you gotten into?
- A fuckin' mess.
- Yeah, you're a mess.
Hey, I called Eddie
to save him for you,
- for your fucking list.
- Mm-hmm.
You've been on this case for
a year and have done nothing.
I've been on it for three
hours and I busted it wide open.
- You should be thanking me.
- "Busted wide open."
That's an interesting take.
Oh, fuck. Here they come.
They're coming, let's go.
Come on.
Shit.
Those our guards?
One, two,
three, four, five, six...
We got eight slugs.
- You got your Glock?
- Not when I'm drinking.
Shit. Here, take this.
What about Nour?
Does she carry?
She'll walk right
into this fuckin' mess.
Fuck, we gotta call her.
My phone is toast, these
landlines are shot to shit.
What about your phone?
Battery died.
How many drinks did you have?
Just enough. At least
we're-we're safe in here.
We're not,
the security guys have keys.
We need to barricade that door.
Hey, give me a hand
with this shit.
Come on, come on, let's go.
What's it feel like?
What does what feel like?
Knowing everyone
wants to kill you.
Ready?
Son of a bitch.
Shane!
The glass is
bulletproof, asshole.
Yeah, no shit.
Well...
this really isn't the
face-to-face you expected, is it?
Open the door.
I can't do that.
Justin!
Hey, let her go, asshole.
You know what it would cost.
Whatever he wants, don't do it.
Open the door, drop your gun,
or I'll splatter her brains
all over this goddamn window.
Slowly. Now!
All right.
Get your ass over here.
- Ah, slowly.
- Okay.
Don't you try nothing, either.
Typical hero shit.
Always wanna be
the savior of others.
So predictable.
Is that the evidence
over there? In one of those?
Then take your ass over there,
you know what to do.
Take her ass with you, too.
Slowly.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Pull up my files.
Now!
Hurry up!
Even if I delete this, there's
still gonna be evidence on you.
Look, you two
will be dead shortly.
You let me worry about that.
Motherfucker.
You know...
If you just would a listened
to my instructions,
we could a ended this
a long time ago.
And what,
you would a let us live?
'Course not.
That's 'cause you're
a traitorous piece of shit.
Sticks and stones,
Special Agent Rosa.
Sticks and stones.
Who the fuck did I just shoot?
And what the fuck
happened in here?
The kid broke my rule.
He destroyed the wire room.
From the looks of things, I'd
say he broke more than just one.
Hey, I'm sorry
about your wire room.
But it's not just about the room,
right? It's about the investigation.
I'm not sure the brass
are gonna feel the same way.
Oh, they will...
once they find out we got
everything it takes to close this case.
And how do you figure
we can close the case?
He found Junior.
Yeah. Also known as
Deputy Sheriff Roberts.
Uh, that's something
I didn't expect to hear.
Yeah, there's a lot
of explaining to do.
Obviously,
but we can't close the case
because he's dead
and he wasn't the target
of the investigation.
Well, the original target
is also dead.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Uh, wait, I'm sorry,
Eddie's dead?
Yeah.
He blew himself up
along with all the others.
Jesus...
The list.
Hey, we'll find it.
It'll be in one of his devices,
forensics can pull it.
Hey, I hate to break it
to you guys.
There is no list.
It doesn't exist.
And how do you know that?
Eddie.
I really wish you
would start explaining
what the fuck went on tonight.
Hey, it's all on tape,
assuming we could get
any of this shit to work.
What the...
For your sake,
let's hope it does.
He saved the case,
not the world.
Good point.
Plus, let's not forget
you are directly responsible for the
death of the target of the investigation,
ss well as a multi-million
dollar wire room.
Yeah, I guess I'm just not
cut out for wire room duty.
Too much action for me.
What took you so long?
Yeah, what did take you so long?
I, uh, couldn't find parking.
See?
I told you, parking
around here is a bitch.
No, you're right,
it's pretty bad.
- They probably towed my car.
- I mean, yeah, probably.
- Yeah, the meter expired hours ago.
- Expensive.
No, don't tell me that.
We don't make a lot.
You've reached Homeland Security
Investigation Special Agent Justin Rosa.
Please leave a message.
I'm not sure
if you're still listening,
or still alive for that matter,
but if you are,
I'm looking forward to you
making good on your promise.
Now, I'm texting you something that'll
ensure you keep your job after tonight.
Because let's face it,
every villain needs a hero.
It's been fun.
See you soon,
Special Agent Rosa.