SIREN WAILS
Can't we shut that ruddy thing up?
If wishes were kisses... Hostile 36,
confirm. Able Victor Charlie down.
26 and 41 detailed to intercept.
41?
That's... that's Reg's squadron.
Sir. How many?
Looks like a dozen Heinkel at least,
sir. With Messerschmitts flanking.
Out of range? Normally, sir, yes.
Well, then.
Time to roll out the secret weapon!
http://www.addic7ed.com/
BUZZER
< Amy...
Winston Churchill.
Doctor?
Is it you? Oh, Winston,my old friend!
Ah, every time!
What's he after? TARDIS key, of course.
Think of what I could achieve with
your remarkable machine, Doctor!
The lives that could be saved!
Ah, doesn't work like that.
Must I take it by force?
I'd like to see you try.
At ease.
You rang?
So you've changed your face, again.
Yeah, well, had a bit of work done.
Got it, got it, got it!
Cabinet War Rooms, right?
Yup. Top secret heart of the
War Office, right under London.
You're late, by the way.
Requisitions, sir. Excellent.
Late? I rang you a month ago.
Really? Sorry.
Sorry, it's a Type 40 TARDIS.
I'm just running her in.
Something the matter, Breen?
You look a little down in the dumps.
No, sir. Fine, sir.
Action this day, Breen!
Action this day!
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, sir, got another
formation coming in, Prime Minister.
Stukas, by the look of them. We shall go up top then, Group
Captain! We'll give 'em what for!
Coming, Doctor? Why?
I have something to show you.
We stand at a crossroads, Doctor.
Quite alone,
with our backs to the wall.
Invasion is expected daily.
So I will grasp with both hands
anything that will give us an
advantage over the Nazi menace.
Such as?
Follow me.
Wow! Doctor, this is
Professor Edwin Bracewell.
Head of our Ironsides Project.
How d'you do?
Oh, Doctor...
Doctor, it's...
History.
Ready, Bracewell? Aye-aye, sir.
On my order! Fire!
What was that? That wasn't human,
that was never human technology.
That sounded like...
Show me! Show me what that was!
Advance! Our new secret weapon!
What do you think? Quite something,
eh? What are you doing here?
I am your soldier.
What?
I am your soldier. Stop this.
Stop now!
You know who I am,
you always know.
Your identity is unknown.
Perhaps I can clarify things here,
this is one of my Ironsides.
Your what?
You will help the Allied cause
in any way that you can?
Yes. Until the Germans
have been utterly smashed?
Yes. And what is your ultimate aim?
To win the war!
They're Daleks!They're called Daleks! They are
Bracewell's Ironsides, Doctor! Look!
Blueprints, statistics, field-tests,
photographs. He invented them!
Invented them? Oh, no, no, no!
Yes! He approached one of our
brass hats a few months ago.
Fella's a genius.
A Scottish genius, too.
Maybe you should listen to... Shh!
He didn't invent them!
They're alien. Alien?
And totally hostile!Precisely. They will win me the war!
Why won't you listen? Why call me in
if you won't listen to me?!
When I rang you a month ago,
I must admit, I had my doubts.
The Ironsides seemed too
good to be true. Yes! Right!So destroy them! Exterminate them!
But imagine what I could do with a
hundred! A thousand! I am imagining.
Amy, tell him.
Tell him what? About the Daleks!
What would I know about the Daleks?
Everything. They invaded your world, remember?
Planets in the sky, you don't forget that!
Amy...
Tell me you remember the Daleks.
Nope, sorry.
That's not possible.
And 6... 2357, over!
2357, over!
So they're up to something.
But what is it?
What are they after?
Well, let's just ask, shall we?Amy... Amelia!
Can I be of assistance?
Oh. Yes. Yes!
See, my friend reckons
you're dangerous.
That you're an alien. Is it true?
I am your soldier.
Yeah. Got that bit. Love a squaddie. What else, though? Please excuse me.
I have duties to perform.
Winston, Winston, please.
We are waging total war, Doctor!
Day after day, the Luftwaffe pound
this great city like an iron fist.
Wait till the Daleks get started. Men, women and children slaughtered.
Families torn apart. Wren's churches
in flame. Yeah? Try the Earthin flames!
I weep for my country,
I weep for my empire.
It is breaking my heart.
But you're resisting, Winston! The whole world
knows you're resisting! You're a beacon of hope.
But for how long?
Millions of innocent lives will be
saved if I use these Ironsides now!
Can I be of assistance?
Shut it! Listen to me. Just listen!
The Daleks have no conscience.
No mercy. No pity.
They are my oldest
and deadliest enemy.
You cannot trust them!
If Hitler invaded hell, I would give
a favourable reference to the Devil!
These machines will be our salvation!
SIREN
Oh, the all-clear.
We are safe. For now.
Doctor, it's the all-clear.
Are you OK?
What does hate look like, Amy?
Hate?
It looks like a Dalek.
And I'm going to prove it.
Would you care for some tea?
That would be very nice. Thank you.
All right, Prof!
The PM's been filling me in.
Amazing things, these Ironsides of yours.
Amazing. You must be very proud of them.
Just doing my bit. Not bad for a Paisley boy.
Yes, I thought I detected a familiarcadence, my dear. How did you do it?
Come up with the idea? How does the
muse of invention come to anyone?
But you get a lot of these
clever notions, do you?
Well, ideas just seem
to teem from my head!
Wonderful things!
Like... let me show you.
Some musings on the potential of
hypersonic flight.
Gravity bubbles that could sustain life outside of
the terrestrial atmosphere! Came to me in the bath!
And are these your ideas or theirs?
No, no, no, no. These robots are
entirely under my control, Doctor.
They are..... Thank you... .. the
perfect servant, and the perfect warrior.
I don't know what you're up to, Professor, but
whatever they've promised, you cannot trust them!
Call them what you like,
the Daleks are death!
Yes, Doctor. Death to our enemies!
Death to the forces of darkness,
and death to the Third Reich!
Yes, Winston,
and death to everyone else too!
Would you care for some tea?
Stop this! What are you doing here?
What do you want?
We seek only to help you.
To do what? To win the war.
Really? Which war?
I do not understand. This war? Against the Nazis?
Or your war? The war against
the rest of the Universe?
The war against
all life-forms that are not Dalek?
I do not understand.
I am your soldier.
Oh, yeah? OK.
OK, soldier, defend yourself!Doctor, what the devil...?!
You do not require tea?
Stop it! Prime Minister, please!
Doctor, please, these machines
are precious. Come on!
Fight back! You want to, don't you?
You know you do! I must protest!
What are you waiting for?
You hate me. You want to kill me.
Well, go on! Kill me.
Kill me! Doctor, be careful!
Please desist from striking me.
I am your soldier.
You are my enemy!
And I am yours!
You are everything I despise!
The worst thing in all creation.
I've defeated you time and time
again, I've defeated you.
I sent you back into the void! I
saved the whole of reality from you!
I am the Doctor!
And you are the Daleks!
Correct. Review testimony.
'I am the Doctor.
And you are the Daleks!'
Testimony? What are you
talking about, testimony?
Transmitting testimony now.
Transmit what, where?
Receiving testimony now.
'I am the Doctor!
'And you are the Daleks!'
Progenitor activated.
Testimony accepted!
Get back! All of you! Marines!
Marines! Get in here!
Stop it! Stop it, please!
What are you doing?
You are my Ironsides!We are the Daleks!
But I created you! No.
We created you!
Victory! Victory! Victory!
What just happened, Doctor?
I wanted to know what they wanted.
What their plan was.
I was their plan!
Hey! >
Commencing Phase Two.
The Progenitor is activated!
It begins!
"Testimony accepted!"
That's what they said! My testimony. Don't beat yourself up.
What do we do? Is this what we donow? Chase after them? This is what
I do. It's dangerous, so wait here.
What, so you mean I've got to stay safe
down here in the middle of the London Blitz?
Safe as it gets around me.
What does he expect us to do now?
KBO, of course.
What? Keep buggering on!
Bingo!
Prime Minister.
Yes? Signal from RDF, sir. Unidentified object. Hanging inthe sky, Captain Childers says.
We can't get a proper fix, though. It's too far up. What do you think,
Miss Pond?
The Doctor's in trouble
and now we know where he is.
Yeah. Cos he'll be on that ship,won't he? Right in the middleof everything. Exactly!
EXPLOSIONS AND GUNFIRE
Oi! Put that light out!
The final phase commences, channel
all reserve power to Progenitor.
How about that cuppa now, then?It is the Doctor! Exterminate!
Wait, wait, wait, I wouldn't if
I were you! TARDIS self-destruct.
And you know what that means.
My ship goes, you all go with it.
You would not use such a device. Try me.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah. No scans!
No nothing! One move and I'll
destroy us all, you got that?
TARDIS bang-bang, Daleks boom!
Good boy.
This ship's pretty beaten up -
running on empty, I'd say, like you.
When we last met, you were
at the end of your rope. Finished.
One ship survived.
And you fell back through time, yes?
Crippled? Dying?
We picked up a trace.
One of the Progenitor devices.
Progenitor?
What's that when it's at home?
It is our past. And our future.
Ohhh, that's deep. That is deep for
a Dalek. What does it mean, though?
It contains pure Dalek DNA, thousands
were created, all were lost, save one.
OK, but there's still one thing I don't get, though
- if you've got the Progenitor, why build Bracewell?
It was... necessary.
But why?
I get it. Oh, I get it!
I get it. Oh, ho, this is rich!
The Progenitor wouldn't recognise you, would it? It
saw you as impure, the DNA is unrecognisable as Dalek.
A solution was devised.
Yes, yes, yes. Me. My testimony.
So you set a trap, you knew that the Progenitor
would recognise me. The Daleks' greatest enemy!
It would accept my word.
My recognition of you.
No, no, no. What are you doing?
Withdraw now, Doctor,
or the city dies in flames.
Who are you kidding? This ship is a wreck,
you don't have the power to destroy London.
Watch as the humans
destroy themselves.
What the...?
No!
The generators won't switch off!
The lights are on all
across London, Prime Minister!
Has to be them.
Has to be the Daleks.
The Germans can see every inch
of the city. We're sitting ducks.
Get those lights out
before the Germans get here!
Confirm, Squadron 244
and 56 mobilised.
Emergency, emergency, 109?
109, confirm?
Thousands will die if we
don't get those lights out now.
German bombers sighted
over the Channel, sir.
ETA 10 minutes, sir. Here they come.
Get a message to Mr Attlee.
War Cabinet meeting at 0300.
If we're all still here. We can'tjust sit here! We've got to takethe fight to the Daleks!
How? None of our weapons
are a match for theirs.
Oh, look, we must have something.
Oh! Staring us in the face! A gift!
From the Daleks!
Turn those lights off now. Turn London off or
I swear I will use the TARDIS self-destruct!
Stalemate, Doctor.
Leave us, and return to Earth.
Oh, that's it? That's your
great victory? You leave?
Extinction is not an option.
We shall return to our own time
and begin again.
No, no, no! I won't let you
get away this time! I won't!
WHOOSH
THRUMMING
We have succeeded -
DNA reconstruction is complete.
Observe, Doctor,
a new Dalek paradigm!
The Progenitor has fulfilled
our new destiny. Behold!
The restoration of the Daleks!
The resurrection of the master race!
Bracewell! Put the gun down!
My life is a lie,
and I choose to end it.
In your own time, Paisley boy.
Because right now we need your help. But those creatures...
My Ironsides!
They made me?
I... I can remember things.
So many things. The last war.
The squalor and the mud and
the awful, awful misery of it all.
What am I? What am I?What you are, sir, is either
on our side, or theirs.
Now, I don't give a damn
if you're a machine, Bracewell...
Are you a man?
Listen to me. I understand.
Really, I do.
Look, there is a spaceship up there
lighting up London like a Christmas tree.
Thousands of people will die tonight
if we don't stop it, and you're the
only one who can help take it down.
I am? You're alien technology.
You're as clever as the Daleks are.
So start thinking!
What about rockets?
You got rockets? Cos you said gravity whatsits,
hypersonic flight, some kind of missile.
This isn't a fireworks party, Miss
Pond! We need proper tactical...
A missile... or...?
Or what? We could send
something up there, you say?
With a gravity bubble, yes.
Theoretically it's possible we could
actually send something into space.
Bracewell... It's time to think big!
All hail the new Daleks!
Yes, you are inferior!
Yes. Then prepare.
We are ready!
Cleanse the unclean!
Total obliteration! Disintegrate!
Blimey, what do you do to the oneswho mess up? You are the Doctor!
You must be exterminated!
Don't mess with me, sweetheart!
'Advancing bombers approaching in strike formation.
Incendiary bombs have hit the East End of London. '
At last! Are they ready?
I hope so. But in the meantime...
This will pick up
Dalek transmissions.
'We are the paradigm
of a new Dalek race. '
It's him! It's the Doctor!
Scientist, Strategist, Drone.
Eternal. And the Supreme.
Which would be you, I'm guessing? Well, nice paintjob.
I'd be feeling pretty swish if I looked like you.
'Pretty "supre-eme. "'He's got company. New company. We've got to hurry up!
PHONE RINGS
Yes? Right. Right, thanks!.. Readywhen you are, Prime Minister.
Splendid! Spaceship'sexact co-ordinates located!
Go to it, Group Captain! Go to it!
Broadsword to Danny Boy!
Scramble! Scramble! Scramble!
Question is, what do we do now?
Either you turn off your clever machine or I'll
blow you and your new paradigm into eternity.
And yourself.
Occupational hazard.
Scan reveals nothing! TARDIS
self-destruct device non-existent!
All right, it's a Jammy Dodger,
but I was promised tea!
SIREN
Alert!
Unidentified projectile approaching!
Correction. Multiple projectiles!
What have the humans done?
I don't know. Explain!
Explain! Explain!
Danny Boy to the Doctor!
Are you receiving me? Over.
Oh, Winston! You beauty!
Danny Boy to the Doctor!
Come in. Over.
Loud and clear, Danny Boy! Big dish.
Side of the ship. Blow it up! Over!
Exterminate the Doctor!
You heard him, Group Captain!
Target that dish!
Send in all we've got!
4-4 to Danny Boy, target
the dish and stop that signal.
Over. Understood, sir. Over.
'You can count on us! Over. '
Oh, good luck, lads!
OK, chaps, let's put London back
under cover of darkness. Tally ho!
Cover my back, going in close!
Pull out, pull out.
We've lost Jubilee, sir! Over.
Beam still active, sir.
Then send them in again!
'Flintlock's down sir, and the
dish seems to be protected. Over. '
Shields intact, pulse still active.
Danny Boy to the Doctor...
only me left now.
Anything you can do, sir? Over.
The Doctor to Danny Boy...
The Doctor to Danny Boy.
I can disrupt the Dalekshields, but not for long. Over. Good show, Doctor, go to it.
Over.
'Going in, wish me luck. Over. '
Shields de-activated!
Energy pulse destroyed!
Direct hit, sir!
Thank the Lord!
Do your worst, Adolf!
Danny Boy to the Doctor...
going in for another attack.
The Doctor to Danny Boy. The Doctor
to Danny Boy. Destroy this ship! Over.
What about you, Doctor?
I'll be OK.
Doctor! Call off your attack!
Ah-ha, what? And let you scuttle
off back to the future? No fear.
This is the end for you.
The final end! Call off the attack,
or we will destroy the Earth.
I'm not stupid, mate!You've just played your last card!Bracewell is a bomb.
You're bluffing. Deception's second nature to
you. There isn't a sincere bone in your body.
There isn't a bone in your body!
His power is derived
from an Oblivion Continuum!
Call off your attack,
or we will detonate the android.
No! This is my best chance ever! The last of the
Daleks! I can rid the Universe of you, once and for all!
Then do it.
But we will shatter the planet below!
The Earth will die screaming!
And if I let you go,
you'll be stronger than ever.
A new race of Daleks.
Then choose, Doctor!
Destroy the Daleks or save the Earth.
Begin countdown
of Oblivion Continuum!
Choose, Doctor! Choose! Choose!
The Doctor to Danny Boy.
The Doctor to Danny Boy. Withdraw.
Say again, sir. Over.
Withdraw! Return to Earth.
Over and out. But sir...!
There's no time, you have
to return to Earth now! Over!
The Doctor has failed. His
compassion is his greatest weakness.
Daleks have no such weakness.
Doctor!
Ow! Sorry, Professor. You're a bomb!
An inconceivably massive Dalek bomb.
What? There's an Oblivion Continuum inside you
- a captured wormhole that provides perpetual power.
Detonate that, and the Earth will bleed
through into another dimension! Now keep down!
Detonation sequence activated.
Time corridor establishing...
Time jump in thirty rels!
Well? I dunno, I dunno, I dunno!
Never seen one up close before!
So, what, they've wired him up todetonate? Not wired him up! He is
a bomb. Walking, talking, exploding!
The moment that flashes red. There's... a blue wire or something
you have to cut, isn't there?
There's always a blue wire. Or a red one. You're not helping!It's incredible.
He talked to us about his memories.
The Great War...
Someone else's stolen thoughts,
implanted in a positronic brain.
Tell me about it. Bracewell!
Tell me about your life!
Doctor, I really don't thinkthis is the time! Tell meand prove you're human.
Tell me everything.
Countdown proceeding.
My family ran the Post Office.
It's a little place just near
the abbey. Just by the ash trees.
There used to be eight trees but...
but there was a storm.
And your parents? Come on! Tell me!Good people. Kind people.
They... They died. Scarlet fever. What was that like? How did it feel?
Please... How did it make you
feel, Edwin? Tell me! Tell me now!
It hurt. It hurts, Doctor, so badly.
Like a wound.
It was worse than a wound.
Like I'd been emptied out.
There was nothing. Good. Remember
it now, Edwin! The ash trees
by the Post Office and your mum and dad and losing
them and men in the trenches you saw die... Remember it!
Feel it, because you're human. You're not like
them. You are not like the Daleks! It hurts!
Doctor, it hurts so much! Good!
Good! Good! Brilliant! Embrace it.
That means you're alive! They cannot explode that
bomb, you're a human being! You are flesh and blood!
They cannot explode that bomb!
Believe it!
You are Professor Edwin Bracewell!
And you, my friend, are a human being!
It's not working, I can't stop it!
Hey... Paisley.
Ever fancied someone
you know you shouldn't?
W... What?
Hurts, doesn't it?
But kind of a good hurt.
I really shouldn't talk about her.
Oh. There's a her.
What was her name? Dorabella.
Dorabella. It's a lovely name,
it's a beautiful name.
What was she like, Edwin?
Oh... Such a smile.
And her eyes...
Her eyes were so blue...
Almost violet.
Like the last touch of sunset
on the edge of the world...
Dorabella...
- Oblivion Continuum... inactive.
- Impossible!
Time jump imminent! Prepare!
Welcome to the human race.
You're brilliant,
you're brilliant... And you...
Now.
Gotta stop them! Stop the Daleks!
Wait! Doctor! Wait... Wait.
It's too late.
You will never defeat us, Doctor,
we will return. We will return!
Gone. They've gone.
No, no, no! They can't! They
can't have got away from me again!
No, I can feel it,
my mind is clear.
The Daleks have gone.
Doctor. It's OK! You did it.
You stopped the bomb.
Doctor?
I had a choice.
And they knew I'd choose the Earth.
The Daleks have won.
They beat me. They've won.
But you saved the Earth.
Not too shabby, is it...?
Is it? No.
It's not too shabby.
It's a brilliant achievement,
my dear friend. Here, have a cigar!
No...
So, what now, then?
I still have a war to run, Miss Pond.
Prime Minister... Oh, thank you.
They hit the Palace and St Paul's
again. Fire crews only just saved it.
Is she OK? What?
She looks very upset.
Oh, Miss Breen?
Her young man didn't
make it, I'm afraid.
Just got word.
Shot down over the Channel.
Where's the Doctor?Tying up loose ends.
I've taken out all the
alien tech Bracewell put in.
Won't you reconsider, Doctor? Those
Spitfires would win me the war in 24 hours!
Exactly. But why not? Why can't
we put an end to all this misery?
Oh, it doesn't work like that,
Winston. It's gonna be tough.
There are terrible days to come.
The darkest days. But you can do it.
You know you can. Stay with us,
and help us win through!
The world needs you. The worlddoesn't need me. No?
The world's
got Winston Spencer Churchill.
It's been a pleasure, as always.
Too right.
Goodbye, Doctor.
Oh, shall we say adieu? Indeed.
Goodbye, Miss Pond.
It's.. it's been amazing.
Meeting you. I'm sure it has!
Oi, Churchill!
TARDIS key. The one you
just took from the Doctor.
Oh, she's good, Doctor.
As sharp as a pin!
Almost as sharp as me!
Hmm...
KBO!
I've been expecting you, Doctor.
I knew this moment had to come.
Moment?
It's time to de-activate me.
Is it...?
Oh... yeah.
You have no choice.
I'm Dalek technology.
Can't allow me to go pottering around
down here where I have no business.
No, you're dead right, Professor.
100% right. And by the time
I get back here in...
what, ten minutes? More like 15.
Fifteen minutes, yeah, that's
exactly what I'm going to do.
You are going to be so de-activated.
It's going be like you've never
even been... activated.
15 minutes? More like 20, if I'm honest. Once Pond
and I see to the urgent thing we've got to see to.
The... the... See?
Very well, Doctor.
I shall wait here and
prepare myself.
That thing we've got to do. Gonna take half an
hour, realistically, isn't it, Doctor? Easily!
So no running off, that's
what I'm saying.
Don't go trying to find that little Post Office
with the ash trees or that girl... What was her name?
Dorabella. Dorabella. On no account
go looking for her.
Mind you, you can get a lot
done in half an hour.
Thank you, thank you, Doctor!
Come along, Pond!
So, you have enemies then?Everyone's got enemies.
Yeah, but mine's the woman outside
Budgens with the mental Jack Russell.
You've got, like,
you know, arch-enemies.
Suppose so.
And here's me thinking we'd just be running
through time, being daft and fixing stuff.
But no. It's dangerous.
Yup. Very.
Is that a problem?
I'm still here, aren't I?
You're worried about the Daleks. I'm
always worried about the Daleks.
It'll take time, though, won't it?
There's still not many of them.
They'll need a while
to build themselves up.
It's not that.
There's something else.
Something we've forgotten.
Or rather you have.
Me? You didn't know them, Amy.
You'd never seen them before.
And you should have done.
You should.
River? Follow that ship.
What do you know of the weeping
angels? But it's just a statue.
Until you turn your back.
Stone angel amongst stone statues.
Perfect hiding place.
We're all in terrible danger. Keep looking! It can't
move if you're looking. Doctor! Don't blink, Amy,
don't even blink!The time will be upon us.
The time of angels.
Impossible.
There's no mistake, this is 1963.
What... or WHO
could have done this?
Exterminate!
Witness the might of the Daleks!