Oh, that's not gonna do.
You, you know you're
gonna make me late.
I tried to tell you.
I can't be with you anymore.
I, I don't have time for this.
I mean it, Amanda.
Not tonight.
See, you think you can
just order me around.
I'm fed up with it.
Just go to the party
and have a good time.
I love you.
No.
No?
Nobody says no to me.
I have given you everything.
That's why I'm leaving
with what I came in with.
Nobody leave me, James!
James, come back!
James.
Keep the change.
Hi, sweetie.
Oh.
Ah, come on, you'll
love it, I promise.
Oh.
Okay, for later.
Oh, so sweet.
Bye.
One of these days.
I love volunteering but I wish
I could just take
all the puppies home.
Oh, by the way, um, I gotta
cancel dinner tonight.
Work called me in.
What's the job?
Private party at the Vandertin.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm gonna tell 'em
I can't make it.
We are having a date night.
Oh, no, it's, I
mean is it good pay?
Just the base pay.
Well, it's at the Vandertin...
tips alone might be worth it.
It's fine.
We can do dinner tomorrow.
- Calli, we...
- No.
- Don't have to.
- No, I know,
but you need the money.
You're gonna finish school
so we can finally open our
doggie daycare day spa.
Plus I hate to
get in between you
and your Gentlemen
Caller ladies.
If you ever want me to
stop just let me know.
I can always find
something else.
Well, while they
are getting Lance,
I'm getting Ben, the real thing.
And that's all that matters.
Plus I trust you.
Call you tonight.
Okay.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh, whoa
Hi. Two sex
on the beach, please
♪ Ooh, ooh
Ooh, does this not remind you
of our first junior
high dance, huh?
Yeah.
♪ Ooh, ooh
What's wrong, man?
You don't seem yourself
tonight, Lance.
It's Calli.
Dude, what did I tell
you? The first rule of GC.
No attachments, not here.
You asked.
Hey, you, we're dancing.
Got it?
Of course I wanna dance
with the lady of the hour.
Be right with you.
Okay.
When I hired you on you said,
you could handle this.
So handle it.
♪ Give it a try
♪ 'Cause I've been changing
♪ Now it's getting crazy
Hey, what's she drinking?
♪ If you think you can take it
Yeah I gotchu.
♪ We can give this a try ♪
♪ I'm afraid
♪ You've mistaken me
I think this can
wait until Monday
when I'm in the
office, governor.
Okay, talk soon.
Politicians.
Vodka rocks with
a twist of lemon.
I asked the bartender
what you were drinking,
and I decided to do the same.
You're a pleaser, I like that.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh
I'm Lance.
Amanda.
♪ Hey, babe
So how do you know
the bride to be?
I'm an executive recruiter.
Headhunter.
She's a client of mine.
Was a client of mine.
The company I placed her with,
well, she's marrying the CEO.
So now you can add matchmaker
to your job description, huh?
Wow, smart, funny, and sexy.
I usually hope for
two out of three.
Would you like to dance?
♪ It's time
♪ To let go
♪ Give up
♪ Control
♪ Tonight
You're a good dancer.
Mom always wanted
a Broadway star.
You got skills as well.
♪ It's all just
this fantasy world ♪
And that's the abridged
story of how I got taken
from my mother, placed
in multiple foster homes,
then graduating
cum laude from AU,
and now sitting in a high rise
doing $10 million worth
of business a year.
You're a true inspiration.
Now the clock strikes midnight.
Well, I had a wonderful evening.
You know I hate for it to end.
I had wonderful time.
How do I pay the tip?
Is it cash, credit?
Bitcoin?
It's through the app.
Okay.
It's been a real pleasure.
It has been.
A thousand dollars?
Mm-hmm.
A thousand dollars
and she didn't ask
for anything in return?
Not a thing.
And even if she did you know
what my answer would be.
That you have a girlfriend,
a longterm girlfriend.
I'd say I can't,
it's company policy.
Since you're awake.
I'm sorry,
but Lance is unavailable.
Well, I'll pay double.
It's for a very important
business dinner.
When a gentleman has
been reserved,
he is unavailable.
Well, maybe you could
just talk to the client.
I can't do that.
Look you're being unreasonable.
If you could just call
Lance and talk to him.
I'm sorry, I can't
help you with your request.
Is there anything
else I can do for you?
I need help help
tracking someone down.
A guy?
I was just hoping you
could cross reference it
with some of your contacts.
Is it a guy?
Because you've always been
my little problem solver.
Answer the question.
Don't get snippy.
It's a potential client.
And yes, he's a man.
I feel like you've used up
all your favors with me, Sis.
You're done doing favors for me?
When we were little kids, being
dragged from home to home,
with Mom after Dad left,
did I ever track
favors with you?
You know I protected
you from some real crap.
Not once did I ever say
"Sorry, you're all
out of favors."
Who do you need me to find?
So his real
name is Ben Howard.
He rents a duplex
over in Decatur.
He's up to his neck
in student loans.
Recently dropped out
of veterinary school.
Took the job with
Gentlemen Caller
in February working part-time,
but I guess you already
knew that, huh, Sis?
Oh, my God, Lance.
Amanda, hey.
God, it's so crazy.
I was just out here
shopping on my lunch break
and I thought I'd
grab something to eat.
So is this place good?
Oh, it's, uh, great.
Um, I just have to say the
tip you left the other night
it was beyond generous.
Well, it was the
only way that I knew
how to show my appreciation
for a perfect evening.
Well, uh, I don't have any
plans are you with anyone?
- Oh, about that, um, I...
- Hey, babe!
Hey.
Oh, sorry, I didn't
mean to interrupt.
I'm Amanda.
I was just saying hi.
I'm Calli.
How do you know... Ben?
Ben?
I don't know Ben, I know Lance.
Oh.
We met last weekend.
He charmed me all evening.
The tip.
I'm gonna get going before
this is anymore awkward
than it already needs to be.
Oh, but quick question.
Ben, are you working
full-time right now?
Uh, no, no, I'm...
I'm actually trying to
complete my veterinary degree,
well, I was and then I wasn't.
It was a lot of
starting and stopping.
Because of money?
I don't mean to be personal,
I just lost my house
manager, and I'm hiring.
I need somebody that can
handle my personal business
while I'm working.
Oh, um, well, I've,
I've never really done
anything like that before.
Well, at the party you
knew what I was ordering
before I had even ordered it,
so I need someone with
that kind of instinct.
So he would be working
at your house, or...?
The role is house manager.
But I'm willing to be
flexible with your schedule
if you wanna get your degree.
Starting salary is 100K.
Um, I'm sorry, did
you say a hundred thousand?
Before overtime.
And for you peace of mind
the Gentlemen Caller rules and
regulations can still apply.
Can I, uh, can I let you know?
Sure.
Give me a call.
Have a lovely lunch.
Uh, thanks.
It's hard to beat a hundred
thousand pros...
and all that it could do.
Look, I know the
money's important
but she's, like,
throwing this at you.
Hey, it's not just me
who's benefiting
here, you are too.
And I'm not just talking
about the clinic.
We could travel, first class.
But I've always loved
our low-budget getaways.
But we could pamper ourselves.
Take that trip too Bali, hmm?
Okay, but I just can't stop
thinking about how odd it is
that she ran into you
and magically had this
amazing job opportunity.
She just happened to be passing
by while she was shopping.
She was just as
shocked as I was.
You weren't there.
Look, I think I
need to take this.
Look, it's just a job.
I can always quit.
This could set us up for the
life we've always dreamed of.
All right.
I guess you'd be
stupid not to take it.
As long as the Gentlemen
Caller rules still apply.
You're the best.
No way.
Good morning.
Right on time.
Dad always said, "It's
better to be 30 minutes early
than five minutes late."
I like that.
Let me show you around.
Dry cleaning goes in
and comes out daily.
I have an account.
I'll get you a credit
card for your expenses.
Also please familiarize
yourself with everything.
Know what goes where.
And if anything is old
and needs to be
replaced, replace it.
If it needs to be throw
out, throw it out.
Are you gonna take notes?
Like pen and paper?
Like on your phone.
I just hate repeating myself.
Ah. Take things down.
Got it.
So...
I'm gonna take care of you and
you're gonna take care of me.
Show you around.
Dinner's at seven.
I want the special
from Terranea.
Get yourself whatever you want.
Um, oh, you, you want me
to have dinner with you?
Consider it a working dinner.
If there's anything
that you need
to vent about, just let me know.
Or if there's anything
that I wanna talk
to you about then you listen.
Okay.
I've told my staff that I'm
gonna be working from home
for the next few weeks.
I hope you're up for this.
Here we go, Ben.
Hey, there.
What happened to the whole
"it's better
to be 30 minutes early"?
Oh, um, they screwed
up the entire order,
so I had to redo
the whole thing.
Well, I wish you would have
communicated that with me
so I wasn't just
sitting here waiting.
Relationships survive or
die based on communication.
Um, I'll do better next time.
Great.
That's all I wanted to hear.
This one's for you.
Is everything okay?
Do you want us to
eat from these?
What are we, street people?
Plates are in the kitchen.
I'll be right back.
Here we go.
See isn't this nice?
Uh-huh.
Would you like some wine?
Oh, um, I'm working.
Well, it's at the end of the day
so you should relax, unwind.
Live a little.
Sure, I'd love some wine.
Cheers.
And I left you a list
of events to RSVP to.
Plus one on all of them,
so get your suit ready.
I'm your plus one?
Gentlemen Caller rules, no?
I just thought we moved
passed that type of thing.
And I just thought you
understood the role
that you would be playing here.
But if not I guess here is
your first and last paycheck.
Things have been going so great.
And to think I even gave you
what pro athletes
call a sign on bonus.
You know what?
Plus one thing is a non-issue.
I'll get my suit
pressed and ready.
Makes me so happy to hear.
Uh, about your car.
Oh, she gets the job done.
I can't have you representing
me around town in that.
Well, uh, can't exactly
afford a new car quite yet.
Take the car in the
garage, use it as your own.
Enjoy it.
And don't let me see
that thing again.
Ooh.
Ben?
What do you think?
You bought a car?
No, no, Amanda gave it to me.
-It's, she-
-What, wait, a gift?
No, no, no, just to use
while I'm out doing errands.
It's her second car.
Wanna go for a drive?
Ben, I've hardly
seen you all week,
and we've only talked twice.
I know, I know, but I've
just found my groove
with this new job, okay?
I'll, I'll be better.
There is also this.
What is?
$5,000?
How about a late dinner tonight?
Well, I would love that,
but I've heard that a lot
the last couple weeks.
Tonight, I promise.
Now come on, let's go.
Wait, I'm a mess.
Let me at least shower.
I don't have that long.
Come on.
Do you need to be somewhere?
No, not at all.
But if you're finished, I can
clear your plate if you'd like.
Yes, please.
Did you have someone in my car?
I noticed some dirt on the mat.
I had to drop a couple
of things off at Calli's
and I took her for a
ride around the block.
She was working in the garden
and must've had some dirt
on her shoes or something.
Well, I would appreciate
it if you don't take
your girlfriend for
joyrides in my car.
Got it.
One more thing, could
you turn on the hot tub?
'Cause I'd like to take a soak.
Sure.
You, uh, need anything
else before I go?
I thought you didn't
have to be anywhere.
There's a spare suit
in the guest bedroom.
Why don't you just hop in?
As lovely as that
sounds I'm pretty tired,
I just wanna go home.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause I wanted to discuss
your future, set up a road map.
Get you set for success when
you're done working with me.
How do you mean?
Well, it's gonna have to wait
until you're not so tired.
How about I sit
for a few minutes?
Would that work?
Are you trying to
bargain with me?
So is that what you really
wanna do, you wanna be a vet?
Help sick and dying animals?
Yeah, yeah, I've, I've wanted
to ever since I was kid.
Ever since we lost
my lab, Hutch.
Ah, Hutch.
Well, as my plus
one to these events
you know you're gonna
meet a lot of people.
A lot of money people
who like to invest in things
like sick and dying animals.
Would they, they
invest in a clinic?
Well, if it's a
rescue center too.
But I'm not gonna just let
you use me and run off,
so if I do this I want you
to give me every effort.
And then I will
give you everything
that you've ever dreamed of.
How about you give
me a foot massage?
Uh, Amanda, that, that's not,
that's not something that
I'm comfortable with.
Respect yourself.
Know your limits.
Know when to compromise
and when not to.
Can I, uh, go now?
See ya tomorrow.
Goodnight, Amanda.
God, I've missed you.
I've missed you too.
Maybe in the morning
I'll make you my special
blackberry brie omelet.
I would love that.
And maybe I could
take you shopping.
Can't you ignore it?
I give her a year, she
gives us everything.
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
Amanda had a break-in.
-  Ben!
- Hey, I...
Someone busted
through the window
downstairs by the pool.
Okay, and, and the
police are on their way?
Yes, but I need you.
I'm all right, don't worry.
Okay, good, I'll, I'll be
there as fast as I can.
Hurry.
It's fine, just go.
Yeah.
Let me know everything's okay.
Will do.
The police say,
it was an attempted
smash and grab.
They ran off when they
realized I was home.
I guess I was really lucky.
I'll get a broom and a dustpan.
You know I was thinking maybe
you could stay the night
tonight in the guest bedroom.
Well, I, I got...
I, I don't feel safe.
Yeah, probably wouldn't make
sense to go home, come back.
What a relief.
You know I think I'm gonna
have drink, settle my nerves.
You want one?
No, thanks.
I just wanna clean
up and go to sleep.
You know I was thinking...
The police are right,
my security system's old
and it's on the fritz.
I want someone out
here first thing.
Sure, I'll get on it.
Then that means I'm
gonna have strange men
in my house during the day
and what about at night?
I'll get the window replaced
and the locks changed.
Yeah, but the security system's
probably not gonna
be in place then.
Then we can hire private
security until they're finished.
And have strangers in my house.
You know I'm not gonna
be able to sleep.
I want somebody that
I'm comfortable with.
Somebody that I can
be myself around.
Somebody that I can trust.
You want me to live here
while the security
system goes in?
Well, I can't think of a
better solution, can you?
- Yeah.
- Look, this is my house
and I need to feel safe,
and in order to do
that I need you.
Please?
Oh, yeah, we can
do a lot in here.
We can insulate it,
make it soundproof.
A safe room with all the
amenities you're used to having.
Not some closet.
Shoot.
- Who is it?
- Calli.
But we can talk later.
Please go ahead.
Thanks.
Hey, Calli.
This all sounds really good,
but can I get some
additional features?
What were you thinking?
You've already
asked for the works.
Well, these are features
that only I wanna know about.
Can you do something like that?
I'm here to serve my client,
not my client's assistant.
Oh, and, uh, the longer
this takes the better.
You're moving in with her!
Just on
a temporary basis.
Just until the work's
finished, which won't be long.
What, what do you even know
about the break-in
at this point?
This whole thing just
feels... convenient.
Calli, please.
Look, I'm sorry I ran out, okay?
I'll call you back
when I know more.
Bye.
So what's the timeframe?
Well, I mean the motion
detectors, the sensors,
that'll be pretty quick.
Roughly a week.
But everything else
a few weeks tops.
- Thanks for coming.
- You bet.
Have a nice day.
Ben.
Come here.
Is everything okay?
Do you like Sam?
Do you think he can follow
through with his promise?
It's just this timeframe.
Nearly a month?
You know how contractors
are, if it's not longer.
When you asked me
to move in with you
I, I thought it might be for a
few days, a week at the most.
Of course, every
hour on this property
you'll be getting paid.
Just think of the overtime.
Thanks, but it's not about
the money at this point.
Hmm.
It's the girlfriend.
Maybe, maybe she
could stay here too.
Where does she live?
Little Five Points.
Well, it's not far.
If you wanna spend two
nights a week with her,
and well, I'll just
stay in a hotel.
I'm willing to work with you.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
What are you doing here?
I was picking up
lunch for Amanda,
but I wanted to come
by and talk in person.
Because you're
moving in with her.
A couple of weeks.
- A month at most.
- A month?
Yeah, it takes that long
to get everything installed.
Hopefully it'll just
be two to three weeks.
I know the whole
thing.
Look, I've tried
to be understanding
with all of this.
And you've been
nothing but great.
Okay, things are weird, I know,
but she's willing to let me
stay here on the weekends.
Oh, how nice of her.
Look, just the thought
of you living with her...
when I want you
living with me, here.
Are you, are you
asking me to move in with you?
Yes.
You can move out
of your place now
and it's a waste of money
at this point anyway,
and then at the end of the month
you can move in here, with me.
I love it.
It's something we should
have done a long time ago.
I'll ignore her.
Come here.
It's not gonna stop is it?
It's fine, just go.
We're gonna pick
this up later, okay?
We better.
Okay.
Perfect.
Now you can control
pretty much everything
from any device in the
house that's connected,
including all the iPads
and the TVs in the house.
You need me to walk you
through everything again?
I've got it.
You know I make
myself available 24/7
to all of my clients.
I said I've got it.
Hi.
Where have you been?
Picking up your dress
and my suit for tonight.
Well, if neither of you
have any thing else,
it's been a pleasure.
Thank you.
Is everything okay?
Thought you'd be happy all this
work was finally wrapped up.
When are you gonna be
wrapped up and out of here?
This weekend, that's
been the plan.
Fine.
Why don't you get on with it?
I'll make sure
you're not disturbed.
Hey, beautiful.
Hey.
I just wanted to call
and tell you how excited
I am for this weekend.
Me too.
Man, has Amanda grown extra
moody these last few days.
Oh, have I?
Look, she's a raging narcissist.
It's
probably a blow to her ego
that you're moving
out of her mansion
into my sweet little abode.
I never told her that
we're moving in together.
She just knows that
I'm moving out.
Really, you never told her?
What's it got to do with her?
What was that?
I'm not sure, it might
have been Amanda.
Let me go check.
I love you.
I love you too.
Enter.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Why wouldn't it be?
I just, just thought
I heard a scream.
Wasn't me.
Had to of been some kind of
feedback from the new system.
All right.
Okay, um, can I
get you anything?
Just peace and quiet.
So if you have errands to
do outside of the house,
why don't you do those.
Sure.
♪ I believe
Okay, it's game time.
So I'm gonna take you around,
introduce you to a lot
of important people.
And all you have to do
is make them feel like
they're number one,
just like you do with me.
Don't forget to smile.
Okay, let's do it.
What?
Oh, what a night.
You were absolutely marvelous.
It was fun.
You know you just
have this "it" factor
where everyone falls
in love with you.
I think you're gonna
have multiple offers
on your startup venture.
Yeah, yeah, those ladies
from the South
Eastern Venture Fund
they, they really responded
to the rescue shelter
aspect of the clinic.
I still have lots of energy.
I thought I would get a drink.
Care to join me?
No thanks.
Come on.
Sure, why not.
You know I can't wait to
tell Calli all about this.
The rescue shelter idea
it, it was hers.
You really love her don't you?
Yeah, yeah, I do.
Actually when I move
out this weekend
I'm moving in with her.
You don't say?
And I plan on asking
her to marry me.
Congratulations.
Thanks for a great night.
To you and... Calli.
Don't you just love mornings
when you can sleep in?
I mean we did drink quite a bit
but we still managed
to have fun.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, you weren't saying
that last night.
This was a mistake.
Don't you realize last night
was combination of tensions
that have just been
building between us,
and it, well, it
finally erupted.
No, no, no, we, we were
in the dinning room...
toasting me and Calli.
And yet, here we are.
You know after that drink
something just came over you.
No.
No, no. I, I don't believe it.
Footage.
I wanna see the footage.
There isn't any
because you had me
turn off the security system.
It was actually really quite.
You didn't want anyone
to find out about it.
No, no, I, I couldn't have.
I'll just tell her myself.
Good luck.
She'll never forgive you.
I didn't cheat.
I didn't.
I'll see you when you get back.
Calli.
It's just me I need to...
What?
Pictures!
Ben, she sent me pictures!
What?
I swear I don't
remember any of it.
I should have known.
I don't know what
happened, okay?
You've gotta believe me, please.
Is that why you slept with her?
- Calli, please...
- Out!
So I was thinking
we could take a trip
anywhere you wanna go.
Away from here.
The mood's still fresh, right?
I'd rather be homeless
than spend one more minute
in this house with you!
Ben, don't be that way.
I take it the news didn't
land well with Calli.
'Cause you made sure
she knew on your terms.
'Cause everything is
always under your terms.
Look, I'm just trying
to get you to see
that you and I we're,
we're great together.
This is your home.
It, it's only natural that
we take the next step.
Like you've always planned.
I didn't plan this.
Right.
As soon as I get out of here
I'm gonna get tested.
For what?
What did you put in
that drink last night?
Nothing.
Would you stop packing?
Look, you have
everything you need.
Where are you gonna go?
Harrison will let
me crash at his
until I can find
a place of my own.
Fine, be that way.
You'll come looking
for me soon enough.
Where is it?
You mean this.
Give it to me.
Amanda, give it to me.
Amanda!
Give it to me!
You gave it to me last night!
This isn't funny, Amanda!
You're hurting me!
Sorry.
You know what, keep it.
I don't want it.
This isn't how you earn
something like that.
No wonder you're alone.
You're pathetic.
Sorry.
Ben.
Amanda!
You guys broke up?
Yeah, three days ago.
This is the first I'm
hearing about that.
I'm not surprised.
He's probably too busy
with his new girlfriend.
What?
Just, it's a long story.
You should really call him.
No, I've been trying, and
he's not answering his phone
or, or his text messages.
So he hasn't called you
to pick up his stuff yet?
No, not yet.
Don't you think
that's a problem?
Hey, it's Ben.
By now you should
know what to do.
Hey, it's me.
I have your stuff here,
and I'd like to not
be looking at it,
so, if you can call me
back and let me know
what to do with it?
I hope you're okay.
Give me a call.
Good morning.
Get me out of this.
Oh, good, you're up.
You can't do this, Amanda.
Do what?
Take care of you.
You think I'm gonna have
anything you make for me?
Well, I made it
with love and care.
Just like you've given me.
Oh, Ben.
Come on.
No.
I mean look, see?
Mmm, it's delicious.
Calli!
It's a soundproof room.
She can't hear you, nobody can.
Now just be a good boy
'cause I'd hate for
anything to happen to her.
Hello.
Amanda.
Yes.
Do I know you?
You know who I am.
Oh, um, wait it's Kerry.
Calli.
Oh, right.
Uh, well, how can I help you?
I was wondering if Ben was here.
I hadn't seen him several days.
You haven't?
No, why? Should I be worried?
He left in quite a huff.
Didn't say a word about
where he was going.
Let me show you.
I'd rather be homeless
than spend one more minute
in this house with you!
Ben,
don't be that way.
And then there's this.
And that's the last
time I saw him.
Maybe he made good
on his promise.
You're welcome to take a
look around if you'd like.
That's okay.
I've taken enough of your time.
I just hate it when things
go messy and ugly don't you?
You will let me know if and when
you hear from him won't you?
Yes.
I'll show you out.
That's okay, I'll
show myself out, thanks.
Amanda was the last
person who saw him.
What do we know about her?
Well, I know she's a
successful businesswoman.
- Uh-huh.
- And...
well what did you
pick up at the party?
I didn't talk to her.
She was locked in on
him the entire time.
What do you mean "locked in"?
She was loving the attention
that he gave her, right,
but it's all cosplay.
A guy doesn't go to a strip club
thinking the strippers
are actually into him.
If he does he's delusional.
Maybe she is.
Delusional?
Yeah.
You said she was a highly
successful businesswoman.
Just because you can
make a lot of money
does not mean you're
playing with a full deck.
No.
Why did you drag
me all the way out here?
I got a computer notification.
Someone's looking into us.
Do you remember that client
I had you look into
a couple months ago?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, seems like
he's not the golden child
that I thought he was gonna be.
He and some partners, they're
trying to blackmail me,
well, us.
- What do they have?
- Nothing.
Wait, can they
connect me to the bar?
Is there a, a photo or a
video from the outside?
I mean I, I was wearing
a mask, but...
I don't think they
have any evidence.
At least none that I know of.
But we can't have
them snooping around.
Look, we love each other,
we protect each other,
that's a brotherly,
sisterly relationship.
All right, so you have plan?
I need your password.
Don't make this any harder
than it needs to be.
I've been taking
good care of you,
washing you, feeding
you, entertaining you.
Entertaining me?
If you're gonna be that way...
go ahead, watch.
Is that Calli's?
Just give me the
password to your phone.
Wait, what, what's
he's gonna do?
Stop him.
It's up to you.
Password.
Give me the password.
Stop him!
Here ya go.
Thanks.
Find anything?
Just some of this here.
Stuff about her company.
Nothing
about her background?
Not really.
Times running out.
Okay, okay, okay.
5-7-5-7.
Stop him!
Hold.
Get him out of there.
One moment.
5-7-5-7.
Ah.
What are you doing?
I'm making you looking
presentable, silly.
It's Ben.
-  Ben?
- Yo, hey, man.
I'm, I'm here, we're
nervous about you.
Where are you?
That, that doesn't matter.
But I appreciate the concern.
I, I just need some time
to figure things out, okay?
Are you okay?
Like where did you go?
Did you not hear me?
Leave me alone.
It's not worth it.
I don't want you
tracking me down.
I don't wanna be found.
I just wanna move on with
the rest of my life, okay?
Goodbye.
Ben, what?
Marvelous job.
Get him out of there.
Should I, shouldn't I?
You promised.
I'm just kidding.
But just know I
can have my friend
go back there anytime.
Any... time.
You can go.
He didn't look well.
That can't be right.
It looked like a hostage video.
And he refused to
tell us where he was.
Maybe he just doesn't
wanna be found.
No, he said, "It's
not worth it."
That's strange, right?
Like almost like a warning.
What's not worth us finding him?
What else can we do?
Go to the cops.
We've had quite a
night, haven't we?
I think we deserve this,
don't you?
Why are you doing that?
I mean this is Dom.
What is it?
I just
followed them
to the police station.
No, that,
that can't be.
Just wait.
What kind of coded
message did you send?
You didn't do your job!
They went to the police!
Nothing, nothing, I swear.
Okay?
Went to the cops? I...
This isn't as bad as you think.
Might, might even
be beneficial, okay?
If they tell the police
that they've been searching
for me, all right,
and I, I told them that,
that I didn't wanna be found,
they'll be laughed
out the station.
And that, that'll
be the reality check
they need to stop their search.
Maybe you're right.
And I'm sorry about
the champagne.
Maybe I could have one.
Mmm.
It's good.
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
I've just been so
tired and lonely.
Lonely?
But I'm here.
You're in your office
working all day.
I spend my days all
alone in here... with these.
Maybe we can figure out
a way to change that,
and set you free.
I'll be right back.
I'm sorry you felt so alone.
My leg, my leg.
Sorry, sorry.
See isn't this nice?
Ta-dah!
I made you breakfast.
Like a real breakfast,
not smoothies.
I thought you deserved
it after last night.
I mean we can't keep going
on living like this forever.
How will we ever
start a life together?
I made your favorite,
blackberry brie omelet.
I can't wait to try.
Probably not as good as
you could have done but.
It's gonna be nice not to
eat like a street person.
That's cute.
Mm, mm.
This is really good.
I normally use a
little bit more basil.
But you did a really good job.
It's really nice of you to say.
Uh, I brought some mimosas.
To new beginnings.
New beginnings.
Um, sorry.
I'll get it.
I need a phone now.
You don't think
I'm stupid enough
to bring a phone in here do you?
Let's go.
You're not gonna make it far.
Maybe I just finish
you off now, huh?
Crawl my way out of here.
Ben, you're not a killer.
You're a pleaser, that's why
we make such a good team.
Look, we need to figure
out a compromise,
so that we quit having these
little minor flare ups.
You don't think that I
wouldn't cover all of my bases
in case you misbehaved, do you?
What did you do?
You didn't respect our promise,
so now I have to call my friend.
Don't, don't.
Please no.
Our threats
didn't scare them off.
After the bar I swear
I would never do
anything like that again.
You promised.
But if what they have comes
out I won't give you up.
Uh, I can, I can, um, I'll say
that I killed James myself.
I can mount a defense about
how he was abusive to you and...
No one's gonna buy that.
The accusations
alone could ruin me,
could ruin everything
I ever built.
That means I would never
be able to help you.
There has to be another way.
I wish there was.
When we pull this off
the investigation's
gonna be focused
on someone else.
It's not gonna be you,
it's not gonna be me.
It'll be the co-conspirator.
You know we have to do this.
For us.
With the way the police
dismissed us the other night
it's lucky that he emailed us
or else I don't think we
would have ever found him.
What do you think he wants
to do this dinner for anyway?
It's a complete 180
from that phone call.
Well, he seemed to hint
that he wanted to apologize,
or explain himself a bit.
I think Amanda really
screwed with his head,
which is why I'm making
his favorite dinner.
What time did he say he
was coming over again?
Any minute.
All right.
You want me to take
this trash out?
That'd be great, thanks.
It's right out back.
All right.
Harrison?
Harrison!
Harrison.
I'm calling the police!
911 emergency.
I've just been attacked!
And he's trying to
break into my house!
- What is the address?
- 147 Parkview Lane.
I forgot about that damn alarm.
I got it off in time.
Walker, what are you doing?
We're, we're supposed
to meet later tonight.
Uh, change of plans.
You're hurt.
Yeah, the girl fought back.
But it's done?
Yeah.
Why don't you go get some sleep?
It couldn't
have been him.
Couldn't have been who?
Ben.
Ben?
My boyfriend.
My, my ex-boyfriend.
Know where we can find him?
No.
He was, um, staying in
Marshall Hills...
with his boss.
His boss?
Amanda Roberts.
What are
you doing here?
Move!
Help me, please help!
- How could I be so stupid?
- Help!
Help!
- You're not stupid.
- You just lie all the time.
That is the blackmailer!
Then why is he chained
to your bed, huh?
He found out about
the plan, okay?
He was, he was gonna tell.
Stop lying!
This was never about us.
It was about you
and what you want!
He was using me for my money.
He was enabling his friends
to steal it from me.
This is so messed up.
It can be fixed.
We can't be fixed!
We are who we are.
And you need to let him go.
I don't
need to do anything.
Open the door.
No.
- Give me the code!
- Stop it!
If you're not gonna
help me just leave.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Walker.
- Get out of the way!
- No.
I said, "Get out of the way!"
Stop!
Walker.
I didn't mean it.
Sorry, brother.
Sorry.
Too bad it had to come to this.
No.
No, you couldn't have.
You left me no choice.
It's on you.
What did you do?
Tragically Calli and
your friend Harrison
were murdered last
night in her house.
No, no, no.
I hate you!
Just kill me.
I love you.
I could never hurt you.
But I'd be careful with
what you're about to say
'cause you're wanted
for two murders.
They're not gonna believe you
just 'cause you got a knife.
You mean the murder weapon
with your fingerprints on it?
But I wouldn't
just rely on that.
See...
somebody was in the
area driving your car
fitting your description,
wearing your clothes.
Oh and, last of all,
somebody had sent an email
from your email
address requesting
that they meet at her house.
I don't wanna
see you behind bars,
but if I can't have
you, no one can.
It's your choice.
You can everything that
you've ever dreamed of
or you can spend the rest
of your life behind bars.
Maybe you just need a
little bit of time to think.
I can wait.
Help!
Hello.
Can I help you?
- Amanda Roberts?
- Yes.
I'm Detective Fisher.
This is Detective Moreno.
We understand that Ben
Howard works for you.
He did.
Why did something happen?
We don't know.
We just have a few
questions to ask you.
When was the last
time you saw him?
A week ago.
Wednesday, Thursday,
you know the days they
kinda blend together.
Is there a problem?
So last
week Wednesday or Thursday?
Did something happen?
His girlfriend was attacked
along with another man in
Little Five Points last night.
That's horrible.
Do you think he was involved?
We just need to talk to him.
Well, I'm sorry I, I honestly
don't know where he is.
So let me ask you, it's
a personal question,
but, uh, did you have a
relationship with Mr. Howard?
Oh, the pictures.
You must have seen the phone.
Yeah, that wasn't
my finest hour.
I, I don't know
what came over me.
Yes, we had a
brief relationship.
Now, he encouraged me
take those pictures
and send them to her.
I think he was trying
to make her jealous.
I don't know, I don't
know why I let myself
get so used like that.
Was he abusive?
Not exactly.
I would say he's
more, um, domineering.
But if you think that
I think it's possible
he could kill two people.
Not two, just one.
The girlfriend survived.
Oh, what a relief.
And we never said that
he killed anyone, ma'am.
We're just asking questions.
I'm sorry, I wish I could help.
♪ You are, you are,
you are, you are, you ♪
- You here alone?
- Yes.
♪ Most wanted girl in America
Pocket dial.
♪ You are
I guess I forgot to lock it.
♪ You are, you are
You know I called a
tech person to come out,
and it's just this
thing is so glitchy.
Sorry about that.
Thank you.
No, no!
No!
Why are you trying to hurt me?
No, no, no!
We shouldn't hurt one another.
See if you hurt me then
I'm gonna have to hurt you.
I don't wanna hurt you.
But if you love me,
I'm gonna give you all
the love in the world.
I'm sorry if I caused
you extra pain yesterday.
It's okay.
I understand the
position I put you in.
So?
It's perfect.
That makes me so happy to hear.
You know I worked
and I worked on this.
I, I don't think
I can eat anymore, though...
I'm full.
You, you've hardly
eaten anything.
Not exerting any energy.
Well, when you start
to behave a bit,
we can see about getting
you some exercise.
Why me?
What's that?
Why did you pick me?
I didn't pick
you, silly, you picked me.
You approached me,
you romanced me,
and then you won my heart.
You really won my heart.
And now I'm gonna win yours.
Blackberry brie?
She...
No, no!
Ben!
It's Calli!
Ben?
Ben, are you in here?
Ben!
Calli, I know you're in here.
Where is he?
What are you doing
breaking into my house?
I know he's here.
I saw the brie
omelet in the trash.
Yeah, well, you're
gonna be arrested
because the police
are on their way.
Good, I'm counting on it.
And when they get here
I'm gonna have them
search every single
room in this house.
You wouldn't like
that would you?
What's behind that door?
What are you doing?
I'm letting the police know
that it's a false alarm.
You know what, Calli?
You're right, he is here.
Wanna see?
- Ben.
- Calli?
- You're alive?
- She told me you were dead.
- Oh, my God!
What did she do to you?
Has she kept you chained up
like that this whole time?
Calli, watch out!
Calli!
No, get off her!
Hey, I'm home.
How was your day?
How's your leg?
Good.
Just lumping around here.
These are for you.
What is this?
Dang it.
We practiced this.
I whistle you come out.
Just hold on one sec.
Don't move a muscle.
Right back.
Oh, my God.
Is she ours?
All ours, and uh...
Is this...?
Oh, my God.
Ben.
Calli Gordon, will you marry me?
Yes.
A thousand percent yes.
Hey, there.
Extra basil.
You remembered.
He remembered.